{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a dead end.\", \"target\": \"dead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"死胡同\", \"phrase\": \"dead end|死胡同\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a dead end.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"dead end|死胡同\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I rest a bit?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's at her side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旁边\", \"phrase\": \"at her side|在她身边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a bit drunk.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on your side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一边\", \"phrase\": \"on your side|在你一边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good deal.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good deal|划算\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big deal|大事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"big deal|大事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a bus.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"乘坐\", \"phrase\": \"take a bus|乘坐公交车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's try it out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"try out|尝试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on our own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"on our own|独自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat so fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"eat fast|吃快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let me down.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let down|失望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't pull my leg!\", \"target\": \"pull\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拉弄\", \"phrase\": \"pull my leg|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't pull my leg!\", \"target\": \"leg\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"腿\", \"phrase\": \"pull my leg|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave me a cold.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"感冒\", \"phrase\": \"a cold|感冒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave me a cold.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"感冒\", \"phrase\": \"a cold|感冒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a big eater.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big eater|大吃家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a bit lively.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's my Mr. Right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确的\", \"phrase\": \"Mr. Right|天选之子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can do it alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"alone|独自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sat by his side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旁边\", \"phrase\": \"by his side|在他旁边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sat next to him.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next to|在...旁边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on Tom's side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一边\", \"phrase\": \"on side|在...一边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hot out here.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在外面\", \"phrase\": \"out here|在这里外面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's on the house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"on the house|赠送\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"to lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a bit pale.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|稍微\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Use it or lose it.\", \"target\": \"lose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"失去\", \"phrase\": \"lose it|失去它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's it made of?\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"由...制成\", \"phrase\": \"made of|由...制成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are in my way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"in my way|挡我的路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you out of bed?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of|在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I see that one?\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"that one|那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I see this one?\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"this one|这个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come in, it's open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开着的\", \"phrase\": \"it's open|它是开着的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let him down.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let down|让...失望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For here, or to go?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"to go|去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a long neck.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long neck|长脖子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a little pale.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little pale|脸色有点苍白\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am six feet tall.\", \"target\": \"feet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"英尺\", \"phrase\": \"six feet|六英尺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can help you out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"help out|帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of fun|很多乐趣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a flat tire.\", \"target\": \"flat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"平的\", \"phrase\": \"flat tire|轮胎漏气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a flat tire.\", \"target\": \"tire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轮胎\", \"phrase\": \"flat tire|轮胎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him run away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"逃跑\", \"phrase\": \"run away|逃跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call Tom back.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call back|回电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call Tom back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"call back|回电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"call back|回电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm losing my grip.\", \"target\": \"grip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"控制力\", \"phrase\": \"losing my grip|失去控制\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take it easy.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take the bus.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"乘坐\", \"phrase\": \"take the bus|乘坐公交车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I open the box?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the box|打开盒子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I pay by check?\", \"target\": \"check\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"支票\", \"phrase\": \"pay by check|用支票支付\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She sat next to me.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next to|在...旁边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"in a hurry|匆忙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big deal|大事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lid won't open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"won't open|打不开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has an old car.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old car|旧车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom made fun of me.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We didn't break in.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打破\", \"phrase\": \"break in|闯入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What a lot of pens!\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is it made of?\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"由...制成\", \"phrase\": \"made of|由...制成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You did a good job.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good job|干得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't drop this cup.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"掉落\", \"phrase\": \"drop this cup|掉落这个杯子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't stand near me.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"stand near|站近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get out of my house.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"get out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a round face.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"圆的\", \"phrase\": \"round face|圆脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a round face.\", \"target\": \"face\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸\", \"phrase\": \"round face|圆脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has his own room.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own room|自己的房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is my old friend.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old friend|老朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is my old friend.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old friend|老朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is taking a walk.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在进行\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is taking a walk.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is telling a lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"telling a lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's doing his best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"doing his best|尽最大努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a high fever.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high fever|高烧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live too far away.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太远\", \"phrase\": \"far away|太远了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live too far away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"far away|遥远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上周\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm dying of thirst.\", \"target\": \"dying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"渴死\", \"phrase\": \"dying of thirst|渴死\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a bit tired.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点也不\", \"phrase\": \"not a bit|一点也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sad without you.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without you|没有你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of fun|很多乐趣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's as cold as ice.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷\", \"phrase\": \"as cold as ice|冷如冰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's as cold as ice.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"as cold as ice|冷如冰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"call it a day|收工\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"call it a day|收工\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"keep in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"keep in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My dad will kill me.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"kill me|杀了我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My home is far away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"far away|遥远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now it's your serve.\", \"target\": \"serve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发球\", \"phrase\": \"your serve|你的发球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She did not turn up.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出现\", \"phrase\": \"turn up|出现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She went for a walk.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"go for a walk|去散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of my room.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...外面\", \"phrase\": \"stay out of|待在...外面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That is not my line.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"行, 领域\", \"phrase\": \"my line|我的领域\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The door won't open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"won't open|不会打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is an ice cube.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"ice cube|冰块\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is my own bike.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"my own|我的自己的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't tie a tie.\", \"target\": \"tie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"系\", \"phrase\": \"tie a tie|系领带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't tie a tie.\", \"target\": \"tie\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"领带\", \"phrase\": \"tie a tie|系领带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom hid in the shed.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": null, \"zh\": null, \"phrase\": null}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is 30 years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"30 years old|三十岁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can count on it.\", \"target\": \"count\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"count on|依靠\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have a good job.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good job|好工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A cup of tea, please.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"cup of tea|一杯茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you busy at work?\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"at work|在工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I hold your hand?\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握住\", \"phrase\": \"hold your hand|握住你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I hold your hand?\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"hold your hand|握住你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you ride a horse?\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑\", \"phrase\": \"ride a horse|骑马\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you ride a horse?\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑\", \"phrase\": \"ride a horse|骑马\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come and take a look.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"take a look|看一看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come and take a look.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"take a look|看一看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you eat out often?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在外面\", \"phrase\": \"eat out|外出吃饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know Tom well?\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"know well|了解\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat like a pig.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"eat like a pig|像猪一样吃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat like a pig.\", \"target\": \"pig\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猪\", \"phrase\": \"like a pig|像猪一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't go to extremes.\", \"target\": \"extremes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"极端\", \"phrase\": \"go to extremes|走极端\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the room.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave the room|离开房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't try to stop me.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阻止\", \"phrase\": \"stop me|阻止我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came to my rescue.\", \"target\": \"rescue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"救援\", \"phrase\": \"to my rescue|向我伸出援手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is full of energy.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"充满的\", \"phrase\": \"full of energy|精力充沛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He likes to watch TV.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"watch TV|看电视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put away his toys.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"放好\", \"phrase\": \"put away|收拾好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He reads a good deal.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good deal|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He reads a good deal.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大量\", \"phrase\": \"a good deal|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was out of breath.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of breath|气喘吁吁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a bit energetic.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|稍微\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought an old lamp.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old lamp|旧灯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't do it either.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"can't do it either|也不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't shut it down.\", \"target\": \"shut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"shut down|关机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't do it alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"alone|独自地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found it by chance.\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"by chance|偶然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of cats.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to do my best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do my best|尽力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know her very well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very well|很好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I left the door open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开着的\", \"phrase\": \"left the door open|门开着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like you very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live in a big city.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big city|大城市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I said open the door.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the door|打开门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I said open the door.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"open the door|打开门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a lot of buses.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I study French a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took a look around.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"took a look around|环顾四周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to rent a car.\", \"target\": \"rent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"租借\", \"phrase\": \"rent a car|租车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ring.\", \"target\": \"ring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"give a ring|打个电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm an office worker.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"office worker|办公室职员\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a flat tire.\", \"target\": \"flat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"平的\", \"phrase\": \"flat tire|轮胎漏气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a flat tire.\", \"target\": \"tire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轮胎\", \"phrase\": \"flat tire|轮胎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like a duck.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a piece of cake.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一块\", \"phrase\": \"piece of cake|小菜一碟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a piece of cake.\", \"target\": \"cake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蛋糕\", \"phrase\": \"piece of cake|小菜一碟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a waste of time.\", \"target\": \"waste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"waste of time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's clean our room.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打扫\", \"phrase\": \"clean our room|打扫我们的房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary came on her own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"on one's own|独自地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I go out to play?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I hold your hand?\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握住\", \"phrase\": \"hold your hand|握住你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I hold your hand?\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"hold your hand|握住你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My home is your home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"your home|你的家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No news is good news.\", \"target\": \"news\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"消息\", \"phrase\": \"good news|好消息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No news is good news.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good news|好消息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No news is good news.\", \"target\": \"news\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"消息\", \"phrase\": \"good news|好消息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one can stop time.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阻止\", \"phrase\": \"stop time|阻止时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a pure heart.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心\", \"phrase\": \"pure heart|纯洁的心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a round face.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"圆的\", \"phrase\": \"round face|圆脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a round face.\", \"target\": \"face\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸\", \"phrase\": \"round face|圆脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is wearing a hat.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"is wearing|穿着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's as busy as Tom.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙碌的\", \"phrase\": \"as busy as|像汤姆一样忙碌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's my best friend.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best friend|最好的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of the rain.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"stay out of|待在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of the rain.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"stay out of|待在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tell me when to stop.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"to stop|停止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a lot of cash.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The job is half done.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一半的\", \"phrase\": \"half done|完成了一半\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The well has run dry.\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"干涸\", \"phrase\": \"run dry|干涸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The well has run dry.\", \"target\": \"dry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"干的\", \"phrase\": \"run dry|干涸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom looks a bit sick.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|稍微\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sure talks a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom turned up the TV.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"turned up|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was all worn out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"精疲力尽\", \"phrase\": \"worn out|精疲力尽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom works on his own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"on his own|独自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We can seat you soon.\", \"target\": \"seat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"安排座位\", \"phrase\": \"seat you|安排座位\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We can't sit idly by.\", \"target\": \"sit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"sit idly by|袖手旁观\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We knew it all along.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一直\", \"phrase\": \"all along|始终\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We took a wrong turn.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"wrong turn|错误的方向\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We took a wrong turn.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"转弯\", \"phrase\": \"wrong turn|错误的方向\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who has the edge now?\", \"target\": \"edge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"have the edge|占优势\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can bank on that.\", \"target\": \"bank\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"bank on|依靠\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can bank on that.\", \"target\": \"bank\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"bank on|依靠\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can hold my hand.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握住\", \"phrase\": \"hold my hand|握我的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can hold my hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"hold my hand|握住我的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You live in my heart.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心\", \"phrase\": \"my heart|我的心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may use this car.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use this car|使用这辆车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bird told me.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"told me|告诉我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I open the window?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the window|打开窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I turn off the TV?\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you open a window?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open a window|打开窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't call me anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"call me anymore|再也不给我打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't keep me waiting.\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"keep me waiting|让我等待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let the dog out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"let out|放出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't step in the mud.\", \"target\": \"step\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"踩\", \"phrase\": \"step in|踩进\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't walk home alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"walk alone|独自走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't waste your time.\", \"target\": \"waste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every dog has his day.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his day|他的日子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Fur coats are on sale.\", \"target\": \"sale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"促销\", \"phrase\": \"on sale|打折\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get out of this house.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"get out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Grab hold of the rope.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"grab hold of|抓住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He broke his left arm.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"左边的\", \"phrase\": \"left arm|左臂\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came to pick me up.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡\", \"phrase\": \"pick me up|接我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can swim very fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"very fast|非常快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He drives his own car.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"his own car|他自己的车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave it a new name.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new name|新名字\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had to stay in bed.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"stay in bed|卧床\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a sharp tongue.\", \"target\": \"sharp\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"锋利的;尖锐的\", \"phrase\": \"sharp tongue|尖刻的舌头\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a sharp tongue.\", \"target\": \"tongue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"舌头\", \"phrase\": \"sharp tongue|尖舌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at driving.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good at|擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at driving.\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"good at driving|擅长驾驶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is like his father.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like his father|像他的父亲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He picked up the book.\", \"target\": \"picked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"picked up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He reads a great deal.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大量\", \"phrase\": \"a great deal|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am 30 years old now.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"30 years old|三十岁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am near the station.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the station|在车站附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought it last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought it last week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can open the window.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the window|打开窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I caught the last bus.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last bus|末班车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got out of the taxi.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"got out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to stay at home.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"stay at home|待在家里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of sheep.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard a car pull up.\", \"target\": \"pull\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拉\", \"phrase\": \"pull up|拉上来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran away in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"in a hurry|匆忙地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom can't win.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't win|不能赢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I threw away my shoes.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"扔掉\", \"phrase\": \"threw away|扔掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a little money.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little money|一点钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like another beer.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another beer|另一杯啤酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm moving next month.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个月\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've run out of money.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"run out of|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it near your house?\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near your house|在你的房子附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time for a break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"time for a break|休息时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let in some fresh air.\", \"target\": \"fresh\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新鲜的\", \"phrase\": \"fresh air|新鲜的空气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let the bird fly away.\", \"target\": \"fly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"飞\", \"phrase\": \"fly away|飞走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's eat out tonight.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"eat out|外出吃饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I open the window?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the window|打开窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please give me a call.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give me a call|给我打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please give me a call.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"give me a call|给我打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Red is out of fashion.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of fashion|过时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Say it in another way.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"in another way|以另一种方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She hit the ball hard.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"用力地\", \"phrase\": \"hit hard|用力击打\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She lives in New York.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"New York|纽约\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made a man of him.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"man of him|使他成为男子汉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy has come home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"come home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sky is light blue.\", \"target\": \"blue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"蓝色\", \"phrase\": \"light blue|浅蓝色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They made fun of Mary.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a Chinese fan.\", \"target\": \"fan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风扇\", \"phrase\": \"Chinese fan|中文风扇\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had a heat stroke.\", \"target\": \"heat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"heat stroke|中暑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a good memory.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good memory|好记性\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom likes me the most.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"the most|最\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom set the bird free.\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自由的\", \"phrase\": \"set free|释放\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We all like you a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a lot to drink.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have time to spare.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"have time|有时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have time to spare.\", \"target\": \"spare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"剩余\", \"phrase\": \"to spare|剩余\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We ran short of money.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短缺的\", \"phrase\": \"ran short of|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We should do our best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do our best|尽最大努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll have to go back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"go back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going back home.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"go back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going back home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"back home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Well, let's get going!\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"get going|开始行动\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What did you find out?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"find out|查明\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why can't we talk now?\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can not|不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are going too far.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太远\", \"phrase\": \"too far|太远了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must do your best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do your best|尽最大努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're a mean old man.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老\", \"phrase\": \"mean old man|刻薄的老人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're in big trouble.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big trouble|大麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're my best friend.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best friend|最好的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fox is a wild animal.\", \"target\": \"wild\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"野生的\", \"phrase\": \"wild animal|野生动物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are they all like this?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like this|像这样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you free right now?\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can we talk in private?\", \"target\": \"private\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"私人的\", \"phrase\": \"in private|私下地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you hurry up a bit?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"hurry up a bit|快点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can't we work this out?\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"work out|想办法\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can't we work this out?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"work out|想办法\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you turn it down?\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关小声\", \"phrase\": \"turn down|调小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you hear the click?\", \"target\": \"click\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"点击声\", \"phrase\": \"hear the click|听到点击声\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you see him go out?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you drink green tea?\", \"target\": \"green\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"绿色的\", \"phrase\": \"green tea|绿茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you drink green tea?\", \"target\": \"green\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"绿色的\", \"phrase\": \"green tea|绿茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to come in?\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come in|进来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't begin without me.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"begin without me|开始没有我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't start without me.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without me|没有我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get a grip on yourself.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"控制住\", \"phrase\": \"get a grip on|控制住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get a grip on yourself.\", \"target\": \"grip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"控制住\", \"phrase\": \"get a grip on|控制住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give me a little money.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little money|一点钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give me back my wallet.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"give back|归还\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ate the whole apple.\", \"target\": \"whole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"whole apple|整个苹果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He blew out the candle.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"熄灭\", \"phrase\": \"blew out|吹灭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He died of lung cancer.\", \"target\": \"lung\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"肺\", \"phrase\": \"lung cancer|肺癌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He earns a good salary.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good salary|薪水好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a good appetite.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good appetite|胃口好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He hid behind the door.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind the door|在门后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is bound to succeed.\", \"target\": \"bound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注定\", \"phrase\": \"be bound to|注定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is crazy about jazz.\", \"target\": \"crazy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疯狂的\", \"phrase\": \"crazy about|对...着迷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looks down on women.\", \"target\": \"looks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看不起\", \"phrase\": \"looks down on|看不起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He runs as fast as you.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as|像...一样快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sang some old songs.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old songs|老歌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took out some coins.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿出\", \"phrase\": \"took out|拿出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was in good spirits.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good spirits|好心情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was in good spirits.\", \"target\": \"spirits\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"精神\", \"phrase\": \"good spirits|心情好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's out taking a walk.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在进行\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's out taking a walk.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am in touch with him.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"in touch with|与...联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am leaving next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ate lunch in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"in a hurry|匆忙地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought her a new car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new car|新车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't figure him out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"弄明白\", \"phrase\": \"figure out|弄明白\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't put up with it.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忍受\", \"phrase\": \"put up with|忍受\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I drank a cup of water.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"cup of water|一杯水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I envied his new house.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new house|新房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got on the wrong bus.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"wrong bus|错误的公交车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I grew up near a river.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near a river|在河边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had my wallet stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"had my wallet stolen|钱包被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a pair of shoes.\", \"target\": \"pair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"pair of shoes|鞋子一双\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard the phone ring.\", \"target\": \"ring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"响铃\", \"phrase\": \"phone ring|电话铃响\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I liked Tom right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立刻\", \"phrase\": \"right away|立刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to hit the sack.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打\", \"phrase\": \"hit the sack|上床睡觉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to hit the sack.\", \"target\": \"sack\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"hit the sack|上床睡觉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a woman in black.\", \"target\": \"black\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑色\", \"phrase\": \"in black|穿着黑色的衣服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a woman in black.\", \"target\": \"black\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑色\", \"phrase\": \"in black|穿着黑色的衣服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want some fresh eggs.\", \"target\": \"fresh\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新鲜的\", \"phrase\": \"fresh eggs|新鲜的鸡蛋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to ride a horse.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑\", \"phrase\": \"ride a horse|骑马\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was right behind you.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind you|在你后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you'd slow down.\", \"target\": \"slow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"慢下来\", \"phrase\": \"slow down|慢下来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to rent a car.\", \"target\": \"rent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"租借\", \"phrase\": \"rent a car|租车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be right with you.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"马上\", \"phrase\": \"right with you|马上就来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you up later.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call up|打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have another beer.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another beer|另一杯啤酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like an apple.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me try another one.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another one|另一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me try another one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"another one|另一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's cross the street.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"cross the street|过马路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's start right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"马上\", \"phrase\": \"right away|马上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a break now.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a break now.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's try to get along.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相处\", \"phrase\": \"get along|相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's try to get along.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起相处\", \"phrase\": \"get along|相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lie on your right side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"侧面\", \"phrase\": \"right side|右侧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I open my eyes now?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open my eyes|睁开眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house is your house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"your house|你的房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one came except Tom.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except Tom|除了汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"OK, you two, follow me.\", \"target\": \"follow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跟随\", \"phrase\": \"follow me|跟随我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please add up the bill.\", \"target\": \"add\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"加\", \"phrase\": \"add up|加起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please add up the bill.\", \"target\": \"bill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"账单\", \"phrase\": \"add up the bill|结账\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please give me a break.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give me a break|给我一个机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please give me a break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"give me a break|给我一个休息的机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the TV.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the TV.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Put on your good shoes.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good shoes|好鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Shall I close the door?\", \"target\": \"close\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"close the door|关门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She asked him for help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"for help|寻求帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She can sing very well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"sing well|唱得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She got out of the car.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"get out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She got out of the car.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"get out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She had a little money.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little money|一点儿钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a little bread.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made a good speech.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good speech|好演讲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She woke up on her own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"自己\", \"phrase\": \"on her own|独自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's correct for sure.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"当然\", \"phrase\": \"for sure|确定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of my kitchen.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"stay out of|待在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy had a red face.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"red face|红脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy had a red face.\", \"target\": \"face\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸\", \"phrase\": \"red face|红脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bus will take time.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rain is letting up.\", \"target\": \"letting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"letting up|停止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rear gate was open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"打开的\", \"phrase\": \"rear gate was open|后门是打开的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The snow was knee deep.\", \"target\": \"knee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"膝盖\", \"phrase\": \"knee deep|膝盖深\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The snow was knee deep.\", \"target\": \"deep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"深的\", \"phrase\": \"knee deep|膝深\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The wheel doesn't turn.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"转动\", \"phrase\": \"turn|转动\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They are having a chat.\", \"target\": \"chat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"聊天\", \"phrase\": \"have a chat|聊天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They eat a lot of rice.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is very good soil.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good soil|好土\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This room is too small.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"too small|太小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom broke up with Mary.\", \"target\": \"broke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分手\", \"phrase\": \"broke up with|与...分手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a big appetite.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big appetite|大胃口\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a twin brother.\", \"target\": \"twin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"双胞胎的\", \"phrase\": \"twin brother|双胞胎兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has to stay behind.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在后面\", \"phrase\": \"stay behind|落后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a Boston native.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"本地人\", \"phrase\": \"Boston native|波士顿本地人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a real good man.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"real good|真的好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a very good man.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very good|非常好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is on his way here.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on his way|在他的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is out of his mind.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of|在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is out of his mind.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"out of his mind|疯了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is out of his mind.\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心智\", \"phrase\": \"out of his mind|神志不清\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is taking a shower.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在做\", \"phrase\": \"taking a shower|洗澡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is very much alone.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom let out a big sigh.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"let out|释放\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom let out a big sigh.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big sigh|叹息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom let out a big sigh.\", \"target\": \"sigh\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"叹息\", \"phrase\": \"big sigh|叹息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom picked up a pencil.\", \"target\": \"picked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"picked up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom picked up the book.\", \"target\": \"picked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"picked up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom threw in the towel.\", \"target\": \"towel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"毛巾\", \"phrase\": \"threw in the towel|认输\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We gave the car a push.\", \"target\": \"push\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推\", \"phrase\": \"give a push|给…一个推力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to do our best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do our best|尽最大努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to do our best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do our best|尽最大努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We help each other out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"help out|帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We helped them as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We helped them as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We like to play soccer.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play soccer|踢足球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We met her by accident.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"偶然\", \"phrase\": \"by accident|偶然地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's in front of you?\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where's the phone book?\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话本\", \"phrase\": \"phone book|电话簿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where's the phone book?\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书本\", \"phrase\": \"phone book|电话簿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who are you looking at?\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"looking at|看着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you drive me home?\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"drive me home|送我回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are my best friend.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best friend|最好的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can take today off.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take off|休息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have a good memory.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good memory|好记性\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You look just like Tom.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"look like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You look like a monkey.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"look like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You made a wise choice.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做出了\", \"phrase\": \"made a choice|做出了选择\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You sing like an angel.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like an angel|像一个天使\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You sing like an angel.\", \"target\": \"angel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天使\", \"phrase\": \"like an angel|像天使一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A glass of wine, please.\", \"target\": \"glass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玻璃杯\", \"phrase\": \"glass of wine|一杯酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are those two going out?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you good at cooking?\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good at|擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you here to see Tom?\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see Tom|看汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ask him what to do next.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"接下来\", \"phrase\": \"what to do next|接下来做什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Bear his advice in mind.\", \"target\": \"bear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记住\", \"phrase\": \"bear in mind|记在心里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Bear his advice in mind.\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心智\", \"phrase\": \"bear in mind|记在心里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beauty is but skin deep.\", \"target\": \"skin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"皮肤\", \"phrase\": \"skin deep|皮毛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beauty is but skin deep.\", \"target\": \"deep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"深的\", \"phrase\": \"skin deep|表面的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I get my money back?\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"get back|取回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you eat raw oysters?\", \"target\": \"raw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生的\", \"phrase\": \"raw oysters|生蚝\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Choose the one you like.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the one|其中的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Choose the one you like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like|喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Choose the one you like.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the one|其中的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Choose the one you like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like|喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you shut the door?\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"shut the door|关门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a soup bowl?\", \"target\": \"soup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汤\", \"phrase\": \"soup bowl|汤碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a soup bowl?\", \"target\": \"soup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汤\", \"phrase\": \"soup bowl|汤碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't add too much salt.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太多的\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't go out after dark.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't make a fool of me.\", \"target\": \"fool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"傻瓜\", \"phrase\": \"make a fool of|犯傻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't quit your day job.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白天\", \"phrase\": \"day job|日间工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you miss anything?\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"miss anything|想念任何东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Draw a line from A to B.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"draw a line|画一条线\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a lot of vegetables.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give Tom back his money.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"give back|归还\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give me a dozen oranges.\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"a dozen|一打\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give me a ring tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"ring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"戒指\", \"phrase\": \"give a ring|给…打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give us a ride downtown.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乘坐\", \"phrase\": \"give us a ride|带我们去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give us a ride downtown.\", \"target\": \"downtown\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"市中心\", \"phrase\": \"downtown|市中心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Grab a hold of the rope.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"grab a hold of|抓住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can read well enough.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"read well|读得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can read well enough.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"well enough|足够好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He didn't keep his word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"keep his word|信守承诺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't eat raw fish.\", \"target\": \"raw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"生的\", \"phrase\": \"raw fish|生鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't look his age.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"look his age|看起来年龄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He found me a good seat.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good seat|好座位\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He glanced at his watch.\", \"target\": \"glanced\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看了一眼\", \"phrase\": \"glanced at|看了一眼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a lot of hobbies.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a test next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has no eye for women.\", \"target\": \"eye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"eye for|眼光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is hard to deal with.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"处理\", \"phrase\": \"deal with|处理\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He keeps his room clean.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"干净的\", \"phrase\": \"keeps his room clean|保持房间干净\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left ten minutes ago.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"ten minutes|十分钟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ordered a cup of tea.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"cup of tea|茶杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ordered a cup of tea.\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"cup of tea|一杯茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He reads a lot of books.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He stuck to his promise.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坚持\", \"phrase\": \"stuck to|坚持\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wants a book to read.\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"to read|阅读\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He went out of the room.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"went out|出去了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His story can't be true.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't|不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about taking a rest?\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"taking a rest|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about taking a rest?\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"taking a rest|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did your weekend go?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"过\", \"phrase\": \"go|过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I asked him point-blank.\", \"target\": \"point\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"直接地\", \"phrase\": \"point-blank|直接地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I asked him point-blank.\", \"target\": \"blank\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"直接的\", \"phrase\": \"point-blank|直接的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I baked some apple pies.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"apple pies|苹果派\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't give up smoking.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放弃\", \"phrase\": \"give up|放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't give up smoking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吸烟\", \"phrase\": \"give up smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't live without TV.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"live without|没有...活\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't put up with him.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忍受\", \"phrase\": \"put up with|忍受\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like rock music.\", \"target\": \"rock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"摇滚\", \"phrase\": \"rock music|摇滚乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't see much of him.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太…了\", \"phrase\": \"not much|不多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want it anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a bath every day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of regrets.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have just eaten lunch.\", \"target\": \"eaten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃过\", \"phrase\": \"have eaten|吃过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hid in the tall grass.\", \"target\": \"tall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"tall grass|高草\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hid in the tall grass.\", \"target\": \"grass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"草\", \"phrase\": \"tall grass|高草\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope we stay in touch.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"stay in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope we stay in touch.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"stay in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like my job very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like tennis very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I missed the last train.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last train|末班车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must be getting close.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"越来越近\", \"phrase\": \"getting close|越来越近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I played here last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I take a bath every day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a piece of candy.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一块\", \"phrase\": \"piece of candy|糖块\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to eat apple pie.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"apple pie|苹果派\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to eat ice cream.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to eat ice cream.\", \"target\": \"cream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奶油\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't see him anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see you next month.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下个月的\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll treat you to sushi.\", \"target\": \"treat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"请客\", \"phrase\": \"treat you to|请你吃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm dripping with sweat.\", \"target\": \"sweat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汗水\", \"phrase\": \"dripping with sweat|汗流浃背\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm eating french fries.\", \"target\": \"fries\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"薯条\", \"phrase\": \"french fries|炸薯条\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm just looking around.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"looking around|四处看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not good at drawing.\", \"target\": \"drawing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"画画\", \"phrase\": \"good at drawing|擅长画画\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not tired right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm shivering with cold.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"寒冷\", \"phrase\": \"with cold|与寒冷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry to bother you.\", \"target\": \"bother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打扰\", \"phrase\": \"bother you|打扰您\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure Tom can't swim.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't swim|不会游泳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It didn't cross my mind.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"cross my mind|过我的脑海\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It may freeze next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to tell lies.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"tell lies|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to tell lies.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"tell lies|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep an eye on the bags.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看守\", \"phrase\": \"keep an eye on|看守\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep an eye on the bags.\", \"target\": \"eye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"keep an eye on|关注\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep it in a cool place.\", \"target\": \"cool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"凉爽的\", \"phrase\": \"cool place|凉爽的地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's all pray together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"pray together|一起祈祷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's all stay in touch.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"stay in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's all stay in touch.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"stay in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's all stay in touch.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"stay in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's all stay in touch.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持联系\", \"phrase\": \"stay in touch|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's drop by his house.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"drop by|顺便拜访\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one came except Mary.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except Mary|除了玛丽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one ran ahead of him.\", \"target\": \"ahead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在前面\", \"phrase\": \"ran ahead|跑在前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Oil will float on water.\", \"target\": \"float\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"漂浮\", \"phrase\": \"float on|漂浮在...之上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please hold on a moment.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等候\", \"phrase\": \"hold on|稍等\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Put it back on the desk.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"放回\", \"phrase\": \"put back|放回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Put it out of your mind.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...脑海中抹去\", \"phrase\": \"put out of mind|从...脑海中抹去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She cried her heart out.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心\", \"phrase\": \"heart out|尽情哭泣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She cried her heart out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"cry out|哭喊\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She got wet to the skin.\", \"target\": \"wet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"湿的\", \"phrase\": \"wet to the skin|湿透了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She got wet to the skin.\", \"target\": \"skin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"皮肤\", \"phrase\": \"to the skin|直到皮肤\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is dressed in white.\", \"target\": \"dressed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿戴\", \"phrase\": \"dressed in|穿着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She liked him right off.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立刻\", \"phrase\": \"right off|立刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made him a new coat.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new coat|新外套\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made him a new suit.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new suit|新套装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took care of my dog.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"took care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was about to go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was dressed in wool.\", \"target\": \"dressed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿戴\", \"phrase\": \"dressed in|穿着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of my business.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"stay out of|待在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That book is a new book.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new book|新书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That book is a new book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"new book|新书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The airport is close by.\", \"target\": \"close\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"近\", \"phrase\": \"close by|附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The radio is a bit loud.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|有点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The toilet is backed up.\", \"target\": \"backed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"堵塞的\", \"phrase\": \"backed up|堵塞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train has pulled in.\", \"target\": \"pulled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拉\", \"phrase\": \"pulled in|到达\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's a back entrance.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"后部的\", \"phrase\": \"back entrance|后门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They got out of the car.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"get out|出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This apple is too small.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"too small|太小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tickets are on sale now.\", \"target\": \"sale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出售\", \"phrase\": \"on sale|出售中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't get over Mary.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"克服\", \"phrase\": \"get over|克服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got out of the jeep.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"got out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got out of the taxi.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"got out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has his own bedroom.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own bedroom|自己的卧室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom headed out the door.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"headed out|出发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a little worried.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is coming next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is taking a day off.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在做\", \"phrase\": \"taking a day off|休一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is taking a day off.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"day off|休息一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is thirty years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"thirty years|三十年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom just shook his head.\", \"target\": \"shook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摇了摇\", \"phrase\": \"shook his head|摇了摇头\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom picked up the knife.\", \"target\": \"picked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"picked up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom played with his dog.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his dog|他的狗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put down his pencil.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放下\", \"phrase\": \"put down|放下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom ripped out the page.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...中取出\", \"phrase\": \"ripped out|撕出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sat on a tree trunk.\", \"target\": \"tree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"tree trunk|树干\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's hands are shaking.\", \"target\": \"shaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"颤抖\", \"phrase\": \"hands are shaking|手在颤抖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the flame down low.\", \"target\": \"low\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"低\", \"phrase\": \"down low|降低\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We bought a round table.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"圆的\", \"phrase\": \"round table|圆桌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We didn't bring it back.\", \"target\": \"bring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带回来\", \"phrase\": \"bring back|带回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We didn't bring it back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"bring back|带回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had to live together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"live together|一起生活\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We made it out of there.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"made it out|成功逃脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Well begun is half done.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"well begun|善始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Well begun is half done.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一半\", \"phrase\": \"half done|半完成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Well begun is half done.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"well begun|善始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Well begun is half done.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一半\", \"phrase\": \"half done|半完成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Were you out last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you driving at?\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图表达\", \"phrase\": \"driving at|意图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you driving at?\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图表达\", \"phrase\": \"driving at|意图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you driving at?\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图表达\", \"phrase\": \"driving at|意图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you driving at?\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图表达\", \"phrase\": \"driving at|意图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you getting at?\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"在试图\", \"phrase\": \"getting at|在试图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you looking at?\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"looking at|看着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you looking at?\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"looking at|看着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What does PTA stand for?\", \"target\": \"stand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"代表\", \"phrase\": \"stand for|代表...的意思\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What does it sound like?\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听起来\", \"phrase\": \"sound like|听起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What does it sound like?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"sound like|听起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is aspirin made of?\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"由...制成\", \"phrase\": \"made of|由...制成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When it rains, it pours.\", \"target\": \"pours\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"倾泻\", \"phrase\": \"it pours|下倾盆大雨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where are you right now?\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where can I catch a bus?\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"catch a bus|乘坐公交车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where's the dining room?\", \"target\": \"dining\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐厅\", \"phrase\": \"dining room|餐厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can start right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在就\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have done very well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"done well|做得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must pay in advance.\", \"target\": \"advance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"提前\", \"phrase\": \"pay in advance|预付\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You ought not to go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should check it out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"check out|查看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should go in person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"in person|亲自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should not go alone.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go alone|独自去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should not go alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"go alone|独自去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should see a doctor.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see a doctor|看医生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better not go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A light bulb gives light.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"light bulb|灯泡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A light bulb gives light.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"light bulb|灯泡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Add a tiny pinch of salt.\", \"target\": \"salt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盐\", \"phrase\": \"pinch of salt|一撮盐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you also from Boston?\", \"target\": \"also\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"also from|也来自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you coming next week?\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you looking for work?\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"looking for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you looking for work?\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"looking for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you making fun of me?\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"making fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you ready to proceed?\", \"target\": \"proceed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"proceed with|继续进行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you writing a letter?\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"writing a letter|写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you writing a letter?\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"writing a letter|写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At last, the bus stopped.\", \"target\": \"stopped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停了\", \"phrase\": \"stopped|停了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beauty is only skin deep.\", \"target\": \"skin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"皮肤\", \"phrase\": \"skin deep|表皮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beauty is only skin deep.\", \"target\": \"deep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"深的\", \"phrase\": \"skin deep|表面的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Big fish eat little fish.\", \"target\": \"fish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鱼\", \"phrase\": \"big fish|大鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Big fish eat little fish.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eat little fish|吃小鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Big fish eat little fish.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"little fish|小鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Big fish eat little fish.\", \"target\": \"fish\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鱼\", \"phrase\": \"little fish|小鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I come to your place?\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"your place|你的地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I come to your place?\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"your place|你的地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I pay by credit card?\", \"target\": \"credit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信用卡\", \"phrase\": \"credit card|信用卡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you help me a little?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you hold on a second?\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等一下\", \"phrase\": \"hold on|等一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you hold on a second?\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"秒\", \"phrase\": \"hold on a second|等一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you pass me the milk?\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"递过\", \"phrase\": \"pass me|递给我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you turn the TV down?\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn down|调低\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come in, the door's open.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"door's open|门是开着的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come in, the door's open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开着的\", \"phrase\": \"door's open|门是开着的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I park my car here?\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停车\", \"phrase\": \"park my car|停车我的车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you drive Tom home?\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回家\", \"phrase\": \"drive home|开车回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a cell phone?\", \"target\": \"cell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手机\", \"phrase\": \"cell phone|手机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you plan to stay long?\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"长久地\", \"phrase\": \"stay long|停留很久\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you speak French well?\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"speak well|说得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you think it's a trap?\", \"target\": \"trap\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"陷阱\", \"phrase\": \"a trap|陷阱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want some company?\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"company|公司\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Dog is man's best friend.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best friend|最好的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't be a penny-pincher.\", \"target\": \"penny\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"便士\", \"phrase\": \"penny-pincher|吝啬鬼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't make fun of people.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't rush into marriage.\", \"target\": \"rush\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"冲动\", \"phrase\": \"rush into|贸然进入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you want to go out?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you want to go out?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Food shouldn't be wasted.\", \"target\": \"wasted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"be wasted|被浪费\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always keeps his word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"keeps his word|信守承诺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I walked together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"walked together|一起走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He behaved like a madman.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"behaved like|表现得像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came back last August.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个月\", \"phrase\": \"last August|上个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He cut the envelope open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"打开的\", \"phrase\": \"cut open|切开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He drank a cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯\", \"phrase\": \"cup of coffee|咖啡杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had his wallet stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"had his wallet stolen|钱包被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had to clean his room.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打扫\", \"phrase\": \"clean his room|打扫房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is armed to the teeth.\", \"target\": \"armed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"武装\", \"phrase\": \"armed to the teeth|武装到牙齿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is armed to the teeth.\", \"target\": \"teeth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"牙齿\", \"phrase\": \"armed to the teeth|武装到牙齿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He jumped onto the table.\", \"target\": \"onto\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...上面\", \"phrase\": \"jumped onto|跳到...上面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows a lot of people.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lives next door to us.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lives next door to us.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looked after the baby.\", \"target\": \"looked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看顾\", \"phrase\": \"looked after|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looked left and right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向右\", \"phrase\": \"left and right|向左向右\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looks like a good boy.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good boy|好孩子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looks like his father.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He married a pretty girl.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"漂亮的\", \"phrase\": \"pretty girl|漂亮的女孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may have lost his way.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"迷失\", \"phrase\": \"lost his way|迷失方向\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He missed the last train.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last train|末班车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put on clean trousers.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"干净的\", \"phrase\": \"clean trousers|干净的裤子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put on the black coat.\", \"target\": \"black\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑色\", \"phrase\": \"black coat|黑色外套\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put on the black coat.\", \"target\": \"coat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"外套\", \"phrase\": \"black coat|黑色外套\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put on the red jacket.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"red jacket|红色夹克\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He slept well last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He swam across the river.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"swam across|游过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took off his overcoat.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"took off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took out his passport.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿出了\", \"phrase\": \"took out|拿出了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took out his passport.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿出\", \"phrase\": \"took out|拿出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He tried to kill himself.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"kill himself|自杀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He walked past the house.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"经过\", \"phrase\": \"walked past|走过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was held in captivity.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被关押\", \"phrase\": \"held in captivity|被囚禁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His clothes are worn out.\", \"target\": \"worn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"破旧的\", \"phrase\": \"worn out|破旧的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His clothes are worn out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"worn out|破旧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His patience is worn out.\", \"target\": \"worn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"磨损的\", \"phrase\": \"worn out|耗尽的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His patience is worn out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"worn out|耗尽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His work is washing cars.\", \"target\": \"washing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"washing cars|洗车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hunger is the best sauce.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best sauce|最好的调味品\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hunger is the best sauce.\", \"target\": \"sauce\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"酱汁\", \"phrase\": \"best sauce|最佳调味品\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hunger is the best sauce.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best sauce|最好的调味品\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hunger is the best sauce.\", \"target\": \"sauce\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"酱汁\", \"phrase\": \"best sauce|最佳调味品\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am able to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am able to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I asked him to wait here.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等\", \"phrase\": \"wait here|在这里等\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought a pair of shoes.\", \"target\": \"pair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"双\", \"phrase\": \"pair of shoes|鞋子一双\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought a pair of shoes.\", \"target\": \"shoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋子\", \"phrase\": \"pair of shoes|鞋子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't get over my cold.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"克服\", \"phrase\": \"get over|克服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't keep up with Tom.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跟上\", \"phrase\": \"keep up with|跟上...的进度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't keep up with you.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跟上\", \"phrase\": \"keep up with|跟上...的节奏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't live without you.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"live without|活不下去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I did that all on my own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"on my own|独自地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't eat chicken skin.\", \"target\": \"chicken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸡\", \"phrase\": \"chicken skin|鸡皮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like you anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't love you anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feel like another beer.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another beer|另一杯啤酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get a kick out of life.\", \"target\": \"kick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐趣\", \"phrase\": \"get a kick out of|从...中获得乐趣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get a kick out of life.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...中获得乐趣\", \"phrase\": \"get out of|从...中获得乐趣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get what you're saying.\", \"target\": \"saying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"what you're saying|你在说什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a hole in my jeans.\", \"target\": \"hole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞\", \"phrase\": \"hole in my jeans|裤子上的洞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got my notebook stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"got stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got on the wrong train.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"wrong train|错误的火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had some calls to make.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"to make|去做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a bit of bad news.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of homework.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I helped her wash dishes.\", \"target\": \"wash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"wash dishes|洗碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know how to set a trap.\", \"target\": \"trap\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"陷阱\", \"phrase\": \"set a trap|设下陷阱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you still miss me.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"miss me|想念我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to ride on trains.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"乘坐\", \"phrase\": \"ride on trains|乘坐火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him on my way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him on my way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I read a book last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him cross the road.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"cross the road|过马路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I drank too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you went too far.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太远\", \"phrase\": \"went too far|走得太远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried to call Tom back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"call back|回电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I used to eat like a pig.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"eat like a pig|像猪一样吃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I used to eat like a pig.\", \"target\": \"pig\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猪\", \"phrase\": \"like a pig|像猪一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I walked along the river.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"沿着\", \"phrase\": \"walked along|沿着...走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want Tom put in prison.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put in prison|入狱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go ice skating.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"ice skating|滑冰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was lonely without her.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without her|没有她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will not eat ice cream.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will not eat ice cream.\", \"target\": \"cream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奶油\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I worked hard last month.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个月\", \"phrase\": \"last month|上个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd better get back home.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"get back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to pay by check.\", \"target\": \"check\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"支票\", \"phrase\": \"pay by check|用支票支付\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be there right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"马上\", \"phrase\": \"right away|马上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll stay here for a bit.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一会儿\", \"phrase\": \"for a bit|一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll treat you to dinner.\", \"target\": \"treat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"请客\", \"phrase\": \"treat you to dinner|请你吃饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm as hungry as a horse.\", \"target\": \"horse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"hungry as a horse|饥肠辘辘\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm as hungry as a horse.\", \"target\": \"horse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"hungry as a horse|饥肠辘辘\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to take a bath.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"take a bath|洗澡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm playing football now.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在玩\", \"phrase\": \"playing football|踢足球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm running out of ideas.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"running out|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry to trouble you.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"trouble you|麻烦你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry to trouble you.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"trouble you|麻烦你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm very tired right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is this a duty-free shop?\", \"target\": \"duty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"免税\", \"phrase\": \"duty-free|免税\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is this a duty-free shop?\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"免税的\", \"phrase\": \"duty-free|免税的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It really comes in handy.\", \"target\": \"comes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"派上用场\", \"phrase\": \"comes in handy|派上用场\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It really comes in handy.\", \"target\": \"handy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"方便的\", \"phrase\": \"comes in handy|派得上用场\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was beginning to snow.\", \"target\": \"snow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雪\", \"phrase\": \"beginning to snow|开始下雪\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a dog-eat-dog world.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"dog-eat-dog world|弱肉强食的世界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a dog-eat-dog world.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"dog-eat-dog|弱肉强食\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a dog-eat-dog world.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"dog-eat-dog world|弱肉强食的世界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a dog-eat-dog world.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"dog-eat-dog world|弱肉强食的世界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a little cold today.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little cold|有点儿冷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's pitch black outside.\", \"target\": \"pitch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"漆黑\", \"phrase\": \"pitch black|漆黑一片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to take a bath.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"take a bath|洗澡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep this lesson in mind.\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心智\", \"phrase\": \"in mind|记在心里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me have a look at it.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"have a look|看一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's do it another time.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another time|另一个时候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's do it another time.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another time|另一个时候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get together again!\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"get together|聚会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's have a short break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"short break|短暂休息\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a short break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I see you in private?\", \"target\": \"private\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"私人的\", \"phrase\": \"in private|私下地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in his room.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his room|他的房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My front teeth stick out.\", \"target\": \"stick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伸出\", \"phrase\": \"stick out|突出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My front teeth stick out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向外\", \"phrase\": \"stick out|突出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My job is washing dishes.\", \"target\": \"washing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗 (xǐ)\", \"phrase\": \"washing dishes|洗碗 (xǐ wǎn)\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My job is washing dishes.\", \"target\": \"washing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗 (xǐ)\", \"phrase\": \"washing dishes|洗碗 (xǐ wǎn)\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My purse has been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"has been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My watch has been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"has been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please fill in this form.\", \"target\": \"fill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"填写\", \"phrase\": \"fill in|填写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please fill in this form.\", \"target\": \"form\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"表格\", \"phrase\": \"fill in form|填写表格\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please knock on the door.\", \"target\": \"knock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"敲\", \"phrase\": \"knock on the door|敲门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please knock on the door.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"knock on the door|敲门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please put your shoes on.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put on|穿上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please put your shoes on.\", \"target\": \"shoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋子\", \"phrase\": \"put on shoes|穿鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take off your hat.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn on the radio.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"turn on|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn on the radio.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"turn on|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn on the radio.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"turn on|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please wait on him first.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等候\", \"phrase\": \"wait on|服侍\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pride goes before a fall.\", \"target\": \"goes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"先行\", \"phrase\": \"goes before|先行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pride goes before a fall.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"跌倒\", \"phrase\": \"goes before a fall|骄兵必败\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pride goes before a fall.\", \"target\": \"goes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"先行\", \"phrase\": \"goes before|先行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pride goes before a fall.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"跌倒\", \"phrase\": \"goes before a fall|骄兵必败\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pride goes before a fall.\", \"target\": \"goes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"先行\", \"phrase\": \"goes before|先行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pride goes before a fall.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"跌倒\", \"phrase\": \"goes before a fall|骄兵必败\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Say which you would like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She goes to night school.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"night school|夜校\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She had a new dress made.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"made dress|连衣裙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is at work right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is hard up for money.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"hard up|拮据\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She left here in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"in a hurry|匆忙地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She left here right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立刻\", \"phrase\": \"right away|马上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She looks like a teacher.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made me a nice dress.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"漂亮的\", \"phrase\": \"nice dress|漂亮的裙子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She talked as she walked.\", \"target\": \"walked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"walked|走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wrote a lot of poems.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's wearing high heels.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high heels|高跟鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's wearing high heels.\", \"target\": \"heels\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋跟\", \"phrase\": \"high heels|高跟鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Should I cancel the call?\", \"target\": \"cancel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取消\", \"phrase\": \"cancel the call|取消电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stand back from the rope.\", \"target\": \"stand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"站开\", \"phrase\": \"stand back|站开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stand back from the rope.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向后\", \"phrase\": \"stand back|退后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ten years is a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bell hasn't rung yet.\", \"target\": \"rung\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"响过\", \"phrase\": \"hasn't rung yet|还没有响\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The door was kicked open.\", \"target\": \"kicked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"踢\", \"phrase\": \"kicked open|踢开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The door was kicked open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"打开的\", \"phrase\": \"kicked open|踢开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The game ended in a draw.\", \"target\": \"draw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"平局\", \"phrase\": \"in a draw|平局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The plan was carried out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"carried out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sky is full of stars.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"满的\", \"phrase\": \"full of stars|星光满天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sky is full of stars.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"满的\", \"phrase\": \"full of stars|星光满天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sun sets in the west.\", \"target\": \"west\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西\", \"phrase\": \"in the west|在西边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sun sets in the west.\", \"target\": \"west\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西\", \"phrase\": \"in the west|在西边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a dead-end alley.\", \"target\": \"dead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"死胡同的\", \"phrase\": \"dead-end alley|死胡同\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a dead-end alley.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尽头\", \"phrase\": \"dead-end|死胡同\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked me stay behind.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在后面\", \"phrase\": \"stay behind|留下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom ate a slice of pizza.\", \"target\": \"slice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一片\", \"phrase\": \"slice of pizza|披萨一片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought the new album.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new album|新专辑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can swim pretty well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"pretty well|相当好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom drank my apple juice.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"apple juice|苹果汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom fell asleep in class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"in class|在课堂上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has his own problems.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own problems|自身的问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is able to swim well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"swim well|游得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom made a bet with Mary.\", \"target\": \"bet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"赌注\", \"phrase\": \"make a bet|打赌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom needs to stay behind.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在后面\", \"phrase\": \"stay behind|留下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took a step backward.\", \"target\": \"step\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"步骤\", \"phrase\": \"take a step|迈出一步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took a step backward.\", \"target\": \"backward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向后\", \"phrase\": \"step backward|向后退\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took the clock apart.\", \"target\": \"apart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"分开\", \"phrase\": \"took apart|拆开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's out of the country.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of|在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Wash your face and hands.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"face and hands|脸和手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We buy eggs by the dozen.\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"by the dozen|一打地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We go to school together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"go together|一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had some chicken soup.\", \"target\": \"chicken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸡\", \"phrase\": \"chicken soup|鸡汤\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have run out of cream.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"run out|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must make a new start.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new start|新的开始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must make a new start.\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"make a start|开始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We ordered too much food.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We ordered too much food.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We talked over the phone.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"over the phone|在电话里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're just like brothers.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like brothers|像兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're just like brothers.\", \"target\": \"brothers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"兄弟\", \"phrase\": \"like brothers|像兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've run short of money.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短缺的\", \"phrase\": \"run short of|缺乏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where are you guys going?\", \"target\": \"guys\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"伙计们\", \"phrase\": \"you guys|你们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who wants a slice of pie?\", \"target\": \"slice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一片\", \"phrase\": \"slice of pie|一块馅饼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't you rest a bit?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you give me a light?\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"a light|一点光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to quit smoking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"quit smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to wait in line.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"wait in line|排队\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to wait in line.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"队伍\", \"phrase\": \"in line|排队\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You spend too much money.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got a lot of guts.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got a lot of guts.\", \"target\": \"guts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"勇气\", \"phrase\": \"have guts|有勇气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Your son has come of age.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come of age|成年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Your tie has come undone.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解开\", \"phrase\": \"come undone|解开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Your time is running out.\", \"target\": \"running\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"running out|时间不多了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Your time is running out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"running out|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fork fell off the table.\", \"target\": \"fell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"掉落\", \"phrase\": \"fell off|掉落\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All at once, he spoke out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"spoke out|说出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you going to use this?\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use this|使用这个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Buy milk on your way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on your way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I fix you a hot drink?\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热的\", \"phrase\": \"hot drink|热饮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I have a look at that?\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"have a look|看一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you put me up tonight?\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"容纳\", \"phrase\": \"put up|收留\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you go out last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"昨晚的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do it as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do it as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do not read while walking.\", \"target\": \"walking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"行走\", \"phrase\": \"while walking|边...边...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do what you think is best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"what is best|什么是最好的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a lot of pens?\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you like to drink wine?\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"drink wine|葡萄酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you take me for a fool?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"take me for|把我当作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to come along?\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come along|一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to come along?\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"come along|一起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave me here alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"here alone|在这里独自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the door open.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave the door|离开门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the door open.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"leave the door open|留下门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the door open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开着的\", \"phrase\": \"leave the door open|让门开着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let the dog come in.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进来\", \"phrase\": \"come in|进来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let your guard down.\", \"target\": \"guard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警惕\", \"phrase\": \"let your guard down|放松警惕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't look down on others.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看不起\", \"phrase\": \"look down on|轻视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Good luck. You'll need it.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"need it|需要它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hang on till I get to you.\", \"target\": \"hang\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等候\", \"phrase\": \"hang on|等一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hang on till I get to you.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"hang on till|坚持到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hang up your coat, please.\", \"target\": \"hang\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"挂\", \"phrase\": \"hang up|挂起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He began to look for work.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"look for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He complains all the time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"all the time|一直\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He extended his right arm.\", \"target\": \"extended\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伸出\", \"phrase\": \"extended his arm|伸出他的手臂\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He extended his right arm.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"right arm|右臂\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He goes to school on foot.\", \"target\": \"foot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脚\", \"phrase\": \"on foot|步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had a book in his hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"in his hand|在他手中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had his hair cut short.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"剪\", \"phrase\": \"cut short|剪短\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had his hair cut short.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"cut short|剪短\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He hid it behind the door.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind the door|在门后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is old enough to drive.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"old enough|足够老\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is old enough to drive.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive|驾驶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is old enough to drive.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"old enough|足够老\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is old enough to drive.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive|驾驶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sat next to the stream.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next to|在...旁边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sat next to the stream.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next to|在...旁边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He will make you eat dirt.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eat dirt|吃土\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's good at flying kites.\", \"target\": \"flying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放风筝\", \"phrase\": \"flying kites|放风筝\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's sleeping like a baby.\", \"target\": \"sleeping\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"sleeping like a baby|像个婴儿一样睡着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's sleeping like a baby.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like a baby|像个婴儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's sleeping like a baby.\", \"target\": \"baby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婴儿\", \"phrase\": \"like a baby|像个婴儿一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His hat isn't on straight.\", \"target\": \"straight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"直地\", \"phrase\": \"on straight|戴正\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His request is as follows.\", \"target\": \"follows\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"如下\", \"phrase\": \"as follows|如下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do we get out of here?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"get out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much are a dozen eggs?\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"a dozen eggs|一打鸡蛋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I almost laughed out loud.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"laugh out loud|大声笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I almost laughed out loud.\", \"target\": \"loud\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"大声地\", \"phrase\": \"laugh out loud|大声笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am going to play tennis.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play tennis|打网球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am watering the flowers.\", \"target\": \"watering\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浇水\", \"phrase\": \"watering the flowers|浇花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I asked her out on a date.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"asked her out|请她出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought a red sports car.\", \"target\": \"sports\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运动\", \"phrase\": \"sports car|运动汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought a red sports car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"sports car|跑车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can do without his help.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"do without|没有...就...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can do without his help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"without help|无需帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can take care of myself.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can take care of myself.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't ask Tom right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't shake off my cold.\", \"target\": \"shake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"shake off|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not love him anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feel bad enough already.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"bad enough|足够糟糕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave her a lift to town.\", \"target\": \"lift\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顺风车\", \"phrase\": \"gave her a lift|给她搭顺风车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a new pair of shoes.\", \"target\": \"pair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"双\", \"phrase\": \"pair of shoes|鞋子一双\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a high temperature.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high temperature|高烧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of bad teeth.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of questions.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have low blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"low\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"低的\", \"phrase\": \"low blood pressure|低血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have low blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"blood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血液\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have low blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"pressure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血压\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know how to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know how to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know how to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like this color as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made his son a new suit.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new suit|新套装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him on his way home.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his way home|他的回家的路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him on his way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on his way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him on his way home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"way home|回家的路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I neither drink nor smoke.\", \"target\": \"neither\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"既不...也不...\", \"phrase\": \"neither...nor...|既不...也不...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I quit smoking a year ago.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"quit smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran as fast as possible.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快地\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as possible|尽可能快地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran as fast as possible.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快地\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as possible|尽可能快地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw it with my own eyes.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own eyes|自己的眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw it with my own eyes.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"own eyes|自己的眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw it with my own eyes.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own eyes|自己的眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw it with my own eyes.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"own eyes|自己的眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I see a cat chasing a dog.\", \"target\": \"chasing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"追逐\", \"phrase\": \"chasing a dog|追逐一只狗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I speak English every day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每天\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I spoke to Tom last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I take a bath every night.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every night|每晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you look like Tom.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"look like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you look like Tom.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"look like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to eat out tonight.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"eat out|外出吃饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you out of my room.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to sleep on it.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"sleep on it|考虑一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was fired without cause.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without cause|没有理由\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was trying to kill time.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"消磨\", \"phrase\": \"kill time|消磨时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was trying to kill time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"kill time|消磨时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was very busy last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will see them next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you up tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call up|打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you up tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call up|打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll show you around town.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"show around|带...参观\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll try harder next time.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下次\", \"phrase\": \"next time|下次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a high school student.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"high school|高中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm counting on your help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"counting on help|依靠帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm drinking orange juice.\", \"target\": \"orange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"橙色的\", \"phrase\": \"orange juice|橙汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad I could help out.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help out|帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad I could help out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"help out|帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm happy if you're happy.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"you're happy|你很高兴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to go back home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to go back home.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"go back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to go back home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"back home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is Tom going to dump Mary?\", \"target\": \"dump\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"倾倒;倒掉\", \"phrase\": \"dump Mary|倾倒玛丽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is death the only way out?\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方法\", \"phrase\": \"way out|出路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is death the only way out?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"way out|出路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it still far from here?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still far|仍然很远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it true Tom can't swim?\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't swim|不会游泳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is your family doing well?\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"doing well|一切都好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It depends on the context.\", \"target\": \"context\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语境\", \"phrase\": \"in the context|在语境中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It depends on the context.\", \"target\": \"context\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语境\", \"phrase\": \"in the context|在语境中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It doesn't sound like Tom.\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听起来\", \"phrase\": \"sound like|听起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It doesn't sound like Tom.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"sound like|听起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is wrong to tell a lie.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"tell a lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is wrong to tell a lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"tell a lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is wrong to tell a lie.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"tell a lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is wrong to tell a lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"tell a lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a quarter past eight.\", \"target\": \"quarter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"四分之一\", \"phrase\": \"a quarter past eight|八点一刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a quarter past eight.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"过了\", \"phrase\": \"quarter past|四点过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to quit smoking.\", \"target\": \"quit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒\", \"phrase\": \"quit smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just a play on words.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游戏\", \"phrase\": \"play on words|文字游戏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just a play on words.\", \"target\": \"words\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词语\", \"phrase\": \"play on words|文字游戏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to hit the sack.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打\", \"phrase\": \"hit the sack|上床睡觉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to hit the sack.\", \"target\": \"sack\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"hit the sack|上床睡觉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary likes milk very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I see your claim tags?\", \"target\": \"claim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"索赔\", \"phrase\": \"claim tags|索赔标签\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I see your claim tags?\", \"target\": \"tags\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"标签\", \"phrase\": \"claim tags|索赔标签\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My apartment is near here.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near here|在附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My brother is watching TV.\", \"target\": \"watching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"watching TV|看电视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car burns a lot of gas.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house has a small yard.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"small yard|小院\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house is fully insured.\", \"target\": \"fully\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全地\", \"phrase\": \"fully insured|完全保险\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother is a good woman.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good woman|好女人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My passport's been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My passport's been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My passport's been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My phone was out of order.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不在服务\", \"phrase\": \"out of order|失修\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My phone was out of order.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顺序;秩序\", \"phrase\": \"out of order|失灵\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One of your tires is flat.\", \"target\": \"flat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"平的\", \"phrase\": \"is flat|是平的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Out of sight, out of mind.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of sight|视线之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Out of sight, out of mind.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of sight|视线之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Out of sight, out of mind.\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心智\", \"phrase\": \"out of mind|心中无念\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't interrupt me.\", \"target\": \"interrupt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打断\", \"phrase\": \"interrupt me|打断我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please fill out this form.\", \"target\": \"fill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"填写\", \"phrase\": \"fill out|填写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please fill out this form.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"填写\", \"phrase\": \"fill out|填写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take a deep breath.\", \"target\": \"deep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"深的\", \"phrase\": \"deep breath|深呼吸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take off your coat.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the light.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Roll up your right sleeve.\", \"target\": \"roll\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卷起\", \"phrase\": \"roll up|卷起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Roll up your right sleeve.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"right sleeve|右袖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"See you again next Monday.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next Monday|下周一\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She called me many a time.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"many a time|多次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She called me many a time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"many a time|多次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She cut the apple in half.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一半\", \"phrase\": \"in half|对半\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a very quick mind.\", \"target\": \"quick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"快的\", \"phrase\": \"quick mind|快速的头脑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has an eye for beauty.\", \"target\": \"eye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"eye for beauty|对美的鉴赏力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is a really good girl.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"really good|真的好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is really a good girl.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good girl|好女孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She likes music very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She lived for a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tried to kill herself.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"kill herself|自杀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tried to kill herself.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"kill herself|自杀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She turned down the radio.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关小\", \"phrase\": \"turned down|调小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was injured in a fall.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"跌倒\", \"phrase\": \"in a fall|在跌倒中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was run over by a car.\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撞\", \"phrase\": \"run over|撞倒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wears a lot of makeup.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wept the entire night.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"entire night|整夜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay right here and relax.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"就在这里\", \"phrase\": \"right here|就在这里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take a breath and hold it.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"hold it|屏住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take any train on track 5.\", \"target\": \"track\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轨道\", \"phrase\": \"on track|在轨道上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take the road on the left.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"左边的\", \"phrase\": \"on the left|在左边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That girl is good-looking.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good-looking|好看的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That girl is good-looking.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"好看\", \"phrase\": \"good-looking|好看的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby was sound asleep.\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"安静的\", \"phrase\": \"sound asleep|沉睡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car was going forward.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在行驶\", \"phrase\": \"going forward|前进\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car was going forward.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向前\", \"phrase\": \"going forward|前进\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The economy is picking up.\", \"target\": \"picking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"好转\", \"phrase\": \"picking up|好转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The price of meat dropped.\", \"target\": \"dropped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下降了\", \"phrase\": \"dropped|下降\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The workers are on strike.\", \"target\": \"strike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"罢工\", \"phrase\": \"on strike|罢工\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The worst is already over.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"already over|已经结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are no clean plates.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"干净的\", \"phrase\": \"clean plates|干净的盘子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were lots of people.\", \"target\": \"lots\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"lots of people|很多人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They can't hear me either.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"can't...either|也不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sank ten enemy ships.\", \"target\": \"enemy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"敌人的\", \"phrase\": \"enemy ships|敌舰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is easy to read.\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"easy to read|容易读\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is easy to read.\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"easy to read|容易读\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This happens all the time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"all the time|一直\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This job pays pretty well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"pays well|薪水高\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throw the ball back to me.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"throw back|扔回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought a dozen donuts.\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"a dozen|一打\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought a new notebook.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new notebook|新笔记本\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought a plane ticket.\", \"target\": \"plane\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞机\", \"phrase\": \"plane ticket|机票\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought a plane ticket.\", \"target\": \"ticket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"票\", \"phrase\": \"plane ticket|机票\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom climbed over the wall.\", \"target\": \"climbed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爬过\", \"phrase\": \"climbed over|爬过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom cried for a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a heart condition.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心脏\", \"phrase\": \"heart condition|心脏病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a little depressed.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little depressed|有点儿沮丧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a very good person.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very good|非常好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a very good singer.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very good|非常好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is being held captive.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被拘留\", \"phrase\": \"being held captive|被拘留\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is in the living room.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"起居的\", \"phrase\": \"living room|客厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is in the living room.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"living room|客厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is out of the country.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of|在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is out of your league.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of your league|不在你的水平之上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is out of your league.\", \"target\": \"league\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"联盟; 联赛\", \"phrase\": \"out of your league|不在同一水平上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows a lot of people.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows a lot of people.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom may have left already.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"have left already|已经离开了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom showed us his new car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new car|新车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to make friends.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"make friends|交朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's car has been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"has been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's hands felt like ice.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"felt like ice|感觉像冰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's hands felt like ice.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"like ice|像冰一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"True love never grows old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"grows old|变老\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Try to avoid overdoing it.\", \"target\": \"avoid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"避免\", \"phrase\": \"avoid overdoing it|避免过度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the key to the right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向右\", \"phrase\": \"to the right|向右\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Wait for a bit in the car.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一会儿\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Waiter, I'd like to order.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"点餐\", \"phrase\": \"to order|点餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a lot of furniture.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a party last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have a big supermarket.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big supermarket|大超市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to pull the weeds.\", \"target\": \"pull\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拔\", \"phrase\": \"pull the weeds|拔除杂草\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'd better get a move on.\", \"target\": \"move\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"移动\", \"phrase\": \"get a move on|行动起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'd better sit down here.\", \"target\": \"sit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"sit down|坐下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're next-door neighbors.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"相邻的\", \"phrase\": \"next-door neighbors|邻居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're next-door neighbors.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"next-door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're next-door neighbors.\", \"target\": \"neighbors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邻居\", \"phrase\": \"next-door neighbors|隔壁邻居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're running out of time.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"running out of|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Were you tired last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What did you open it with?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open it with|用什么打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is the exchange rate?\", \"target\": \"exchange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汇率\", \"phrase\": \"exchange rate|汇率\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What time is it right now?\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's your mother tongue?\", \"target\": \"tongue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"舌头\", \"phrase\": \"mother tongue|母语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whatever will be, will be.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will be|将会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When did you last see Tom?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上次\", \"phrase\": \"last see|上次看见\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where were you last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"昨晚的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who wants a piece of cake?\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一块\", \"phrase\": \"piece of cake|蛋糕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will six o'clock suit you?\", \"target\": \"suit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"适合\", \"phrase\": \"suit you|适合你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will six o'clock suit you?\", \"target\": \"suit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"适合\", \"phrase\": \"suit you|适合你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you pass me the salt?\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"递过\", \"phrase\": \"pass me|递给我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are selling him short.\", \"target\": \"selling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卖\", \"phrase\": \"selling short|短线卖空\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are selling him short.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"selling short|卖空\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can no longer hurt me.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"no longer|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have a way with women.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方法\", \"phrase\": \"way with|与...相处的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must not eat too much.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eat too much|吃太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must not eat too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should take that away.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿走\", \"phrase\": \"take away|拿走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should take that away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"take away|带走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should've turned left.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"转弯\", \"phrase\": \"turned left|向左转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better go in person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"in person|亲自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better take it easy.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better take it easy.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're on the right track.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确的\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|在正确的轨道上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're on the right track.\", \"target\": \"track\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轨道; 路线\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|走在正确的道路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're on the right track.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确的\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|在正确的轨道上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're on the right track.\", \"target\": \"track\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轨道; 路线\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|走在正确的道路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you able to play organ?\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩，演奏\", \"phrase\": \"play organ|演奏器官\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you able to play organ?\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩，演奏\", \"phrase\": \"play organ|演奏器官\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you going out tomorrow?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you going to come back?\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"come back|回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you going to come back?\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"come back|回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you going to stay long?\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"长久地\", \"phrase\": \"stay long|待很久\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you ready to order now?\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"点餐\", \"phrase\": \"to order|点餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Basketball is a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Bring your student ID card.\", \"target\": \"id\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"身份证\", \"phrase\": \"student ID card|学生证\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I have a bit more milk?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can she endure a long trip?\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long trip|长途旅行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I see you in private?\", \"target\": \"private\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"私人的\", \"phrase\": \"in private|私下地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you stop saying that?\", \"target\": \"saying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"stop saying|停止说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you go to see a doctor?\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see a doctor|看医生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you belong to any clubs?\", \"target\": \"clubs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"俱乐部\", \"phrase\": \"belong to clubs|属于俱乐部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you drink a lot of milk?\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have any light beer?\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"轻的\", \"phrase\": \"light beer|淡啤酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have to make dinner?\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"make dinner|做晚饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Doing that won't take long.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take long|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Doing this is a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't beat around the bush.\", \"target\": \"beat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打\", \"phrase\": \"beat around the bush|拐弯抹角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't beat around the bush.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"beat around the bush|拐弯抹角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't beat around the bush.\", \"target\": \"bush\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灌木丛\", \"phrase\": \"beat around the bush|拐弯抹角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't stand in front of me.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't talk to me like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"talk like that|那样说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't talk to me like this.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"talk to me like this|像这样跟我说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eggs are sold by the dozen.\", \"target\": \"sold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卖\", \"phrase\": \"sold by|由...出售\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eggs are sold by the dozen.\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"by the dozen|按打\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Fill out this form, please.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"填写\", \"phrase\": \"fill out|填写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hang your coat on the hook.\", \"target\": \"hang\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"挂\", \"phrase\": \"hang your coat|挂你的外套\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hang your coat on the hook.\", \"target\": \"hook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钩子\", \"phrase\": \"on the hook|在钩子上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ate a box of chocolates.\", \"target\": \"box\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盒子\", \"phrase\": \"box of chocolates|一盒巧克力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He began to look for a job.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"look for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He caught hold of the rope.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"caught hold of|抓住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He decided to quit smoking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"quit smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He did not put up his hand.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put up|举起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He did not put up his hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"put up his hand|举手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has an eye for antiques.\", \"target\": \"eye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"eye for|眼光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a good tennis player.\", \"target\": \"tennis\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"网球\", \"phrase\": \"tennis player|网球运动员\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is driving at top speed.\", \"target\": \"top\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最高\", \"phrase\": \"top speed|最高速度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is driving at top speed.\", \"target\": \"speed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"速度\", \"phrase\": \"top speed|最高速度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ran as fast as he could.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as|像...一样快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ran away with the money.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"逃跑\", \"phrase\": \"ran away|逃跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He saw a dog near the door.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the door|在门附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He saw a dog near the door.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"near the door|在门附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sent me a birthday card.\", \"target\": \"birthday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生日\", \"phrase\": \"birthday card|生日卡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He studies Chinese as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me to wash my face.\", \"target\": \"wash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"wash my face|洗我的脸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took us back in his car.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"took us back|带我们回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was absent at roll call.\", \"target\": \"roll\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"点名\", \"phrase\": \"roll call|点名\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was absent at roll call.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"呼叫\", \"phrase\": \"roll call|点名\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was almost hit by a car.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撞击\", \"phrase\": \"almost hit|差点撞到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was seen to go upstairs.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go upstairs|上楼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was seen to go upstairs.\", \"target\": \"upstairs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"楼上\", \"phrase\": \"go upstairs|上楼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was sitting up straight.\", \"target\": \"sitting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐着\", \"phrase\": \"sitting up|坐直\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was sitting up straight.\", \"target\": \"straight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"笔直地\", \"phrase\": \"sitting straight|坐直\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a high school student.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"high school|高中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about calling it a day?\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"calling it a day|收工\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is four times six?\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"four times six|四乘以六\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is four times six?\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"倍\", \"phrase\": \"four times six|四乘以六\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much time does it take?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am just going for a walk.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"go for a walk|去散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am playing the piano now.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在弹奏\", \"phrase\": \"playing the piano|弹钢琴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can read without glasses.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without glasses|没有眼镜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't eat this much food.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太多的\", \"phrase\": \"much food|食物太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't get rid of my cold.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't get rid of my cold.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't care all that much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太...\", \"phrase\": \"not much|不多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to live alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"live alone|独自生活\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a good night's sleep.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"night's sleep|夜间睡眠\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got along with everybody.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"和...相处\", \"phrase\": \"got along with|和...相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a good night's sleep.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"night's sleep|夜间睡眠\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a long talk with her.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long talk|长时间的谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a long talk with her.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谈话\", \"phrase\": \"long talk|长时间的谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a nice chat with her.\", \"target\": \"chat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"聊天\", \"phrase\": \"nice chat|愉快的聊天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"frog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青蛙\", \"phrase\": \"frog in my throat|嗓子不舒服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"throat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喉咙\", \"phrase\": \"frog in my throat|嗓子不舒服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"frog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青蛙\", \"phrase\": \"frog in my throat|嗓子不舒服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"throat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喉咙\", \"phrase\": \"frog in my throat|嗓子不舒服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a pair of red shoes.\", \"target\": \"pair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"pair of shoes|鞋子的一双\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a pair of red shoes.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"red shoes|红鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a pair of red shoes.\", \"target\": \"shoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋子\", \"phrase\": \"red shoes|红色的鞋子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have already eaten lunch.\", \"target\": \"eaten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃过\", \"phrase\": \"have eaten|已经吃过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have high blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high blood pressure|高血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have high blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"blood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血液\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have high blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"pressure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血压\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to clean the toilet.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打扫\", \"phrase\": \"clean the toilet|打扫厕所\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go meet with Tom.\", \"target\": \"meet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"见面\", \"phrase\": \"meet with|与...见面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to the toilet.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the toilet|去洗手间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to the toilet.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the toilet|去洗手间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to the toilet.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the toilet|去洗手间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you in ages.\", \"target\": \"ages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"in ages|好久了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope you will call again.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call again|再次打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I love passion fruit juice.\", \"target\": \"fruit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"水果\", \"phrase\": \"passion fruit|百香果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I love watching talk shows.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谈话节目\", \"phrase\": \"talk shows|脱口秀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him at Tokyo Station.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"Tokyo Station|东京车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need a new pair of shoes.\", \"target\": \"pair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"双\", \"phrase\": \"pair of shoes|鞋子一双\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ripped the envelope open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"ripped open|撕开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him cross the street.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"cross the street|穿过街道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I studied around the clock.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the clock|通宵达旦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I studied around the clock.\", \"target\": \"clock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时钟\", \"phrase\": \"around the clock|昼夜不停\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I take my health seriously.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认真对待\", \"phrase\": \"take seriously|认真对待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I talked to Tom last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took a day off last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to take a break.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to take a break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was a little bit nervous.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was a little bit nervous.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was bitten by a mosquito.\", \"target\": \"bitten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb, past participle\", \"zh\": \"被咬\", \"phrase\": \"bitten by|被...咬\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was in Boston last month.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个月\", \"phrase\": \"last month|上个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I went fishing last Monday.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last Monday|上周一\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will do anything for you.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何事情\", \"phrase\": \"anything for you|为你做任何事情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will take you for a swim.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take you for a swim|带你游泳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't stay here for long.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"久\", \"phrase\": \"for long|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work best under pressure.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"work best|工作最好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work best under pressure.\", \"target\": \"pressure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"压力\", \"phrase\": \"under pressure|在压力下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would like to rent a car.\", \"target\": \"rent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"租借\", \"phrase\": \"rent a car|租车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd better do it right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to call my family.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call my family|给我的家人打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go back home with you.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"go back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go back home with you.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"back home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll open the window a bit.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a little bit concerned.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm breast-feeding my baby.\", \"target\": \"breast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"母乳喂养\", \"phrase\": \"breast-feeding|母乳喂养\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm breast-feeding my baby.\", \"target\": \"feeding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喂养\", \"phrase\": \"breast-feeding|母乳喂养\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm dying for a cold drink.\", \"target\": \"dying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"渴望\", \"phrase\": \"dying for|渴望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm dying for a cold drink.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold drink|冷饮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm dying for a cold drink.\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"饮料\", \"phrase\": \"cold drink|冷饮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to miss you, too.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"miss you|想你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not doing that anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not doing anymore|不再做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm playing volleyball now.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在玩\", \"phrase\": \"playing volleyball|打排球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been here a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've missed another chance.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another chance|又一次机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you're happy, I'm happy.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"I'm happy|我很高兴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is Tom in a lot of trouble?\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is Tom in a lot of trouble?\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of trouble|很多麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a bus stop nearby?\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"bus stop|公共汽车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a bus stop nearby?\", \"target\": \"nearby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"附近\", \"phrase\": \"nearby|附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a doctor on board?\", \"target\": \"board\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"船上\", \"phrase\": \"on board|在船上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a hospital nearby?\", \"target\": \"nearby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"附近\", \"phrase\": \"nearby|附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is your family still there?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still there|仍然在那里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems that Tom is lying.\", \"target\": \"lying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"is lying|在说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was love at first sight.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"at first sight|一见钟情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's my turn to drive next.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轮流\", \"phrase\": \"my turn|我的回合\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's raining cats and dogs.\", \"target\": \"cats\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"cats and dogs|猫狗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's raining cats and dogs.\", \"target\": \"dogs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"cats and dogs|猫狗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Just then, the bus stopped.\", \"target\": \"stopped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停了\", \"phrase\": \"stopped|停了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me buy you another one.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another one|另一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's finish up in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"in a hurry|匆忙地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's have dinner together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"together|一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's split the bill today.\", \"target\": \"split\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分摊\", \"phrase\": \"split the bill|买单\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary looks like her mother.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I have a talk with you?\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谈话\", \"phrase\": \"have a talk|谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My bicycle has a flat tire.\", \"target\": \"flat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"平的\", \"phrase\": \"flat tire|轮胎漏气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My brother can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car is at your disposal.\", \"target\": \"disposal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"处置权\", \"phrase\": \"at your disposal|由你处置\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My friends all call me Tom.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"call me|叫我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My heart's beating so fast!\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"beating fast|心跳很快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Neither Tom nor I did that.\", \"target\": \"neither\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"既不...也不...\", \"phrase\": \"neither...nor...|既不...也不...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now it's my brother's turn.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轮流\", \"phrase\": \"brother's turn|兄弟的轮流\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One's new. The other's old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old|旧的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Place it wherever you like.\", \"target\": \"wherever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"无论哪里\", \"phrase\": \"wherever you like|无论你喜欢哪里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Place it wherever you like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like it|喜欢它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't speak so fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"speak fast|说得快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't speak so fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"speak fast|说得快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't speak so fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"speak fast|说得快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please show me another one.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another one|另一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please show me another one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"another one|另一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please stop that right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take a look at this.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"take a look|看一看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take off your shoes.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take your shoes off.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please take your shoes off.\", \"target\": \"shoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋子\", \"phrase\": \"take shoes off|脱鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn down the music.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关小声\", \"phrase\": \"turn down|调小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn down the radio.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关小声\", \"phrase\": \"turn down|调小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the lights.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the lights.\", \"target\": \"lights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灯\", \"phrase\": \"turn off the lights|关灯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn out the lights.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn out|熄灭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn out the lights.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关掉\", \"phrase\": \"turn out|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn out the lights.\", \"target\": \"lights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灯\", \"phrase\": \"turn out the lights|关灯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please wait a little while.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a little while|一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Put in a little more sugar.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little more|稍微多一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Put it on one bill, please.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one bill|一张账单\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Put it on one bill, please.\", \"target\": \"bill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"账单\", \"phrase\": \"on bill|在账单上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Remember to cross your t's.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"交叉\", \"phrase\": \"cross your t's|划掉t的横\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Shall we go out for a walk?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Shall we go out for a walk?\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"go for a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave him a tender kiss.\", \"target\": \"tender\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"温柔的\", \"phrase\": \"tender kiss|温柔的吻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave him a tender kiss.\", \"target\": \"kiss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"吻\", \"phrase\": \"tender kiss|温柔的吻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave me a strange look.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"看了一眼\", \"phrase\": \"strange look|奇怪的眼神\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She goes to school on foot.\", \"target\": \"foot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脚\", \"phrase\": \"on foot|步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She had her handbag stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"had her handbag stolen|她的手提包被偷了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a rose in her hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"in her hand|在她的手中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is a very good teacher.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very good|非常好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is a well-known singer.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"well-known|知名\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She lives in a large house.\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"large house|大房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She lives next door to him.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She lives next door to him.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made a serious mistake.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯了\", \"phrase\": \"made a mistake|犯了一个错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She managed to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She married a rich old man.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old man|老头\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She married a rich old man.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old man|老头\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She plays tennis every day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She speaks a little Arabic.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was washing the dishes.\", \"target\": \"washing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"washing the dishes|洗碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was wearing long boots.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"wearing boots|穿着靴子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was wearing long boots.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long boots|长筒靴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Smoking isn't allowed here.\", \"target\": \"allowed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被允许\", \"phrase\": \"isn't allowed|不允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay put till I get to you.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"stay put|保持原地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take good care of yourself.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take good care of yourself.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good care|好好照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take good care of yourself.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take the road on the right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"on the right|在右边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That movie is worth seeing.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"worth seeing|值得看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That movie is worth seeing.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"worth seeing|值得看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The air felt a little cold.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little cold|有点儿冷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boat can still be seen.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"can still|仍然可以\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy is full of promise.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"充满\", \"phrase\": \"full of promise|充满希望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy is full of promise.\", \"target\": \"promise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"承诺\", \"phrase\": \"full of promise|充满希望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy is wearing glasses.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"is wearing|穿着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The doctor called him back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"called back|叫回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The exhibition is now open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开放的\", \"phrase\": \"now open|现在开放\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The job offer still stands.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still stands|仍然有效\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The job offer still stands.\", \"target\": \"stands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"仍然有效\", \"phrase\": \"stands still|仍然保持\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The light has turned green.\", \"target\": \"green\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"绿色\", \"phrase\": \"turned green|变成绿色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The meeting was called off.\", \"target\": \"called\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取消\", \"phrase\": \"called off|取消\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old man got in her way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"in the way|挡路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The room was full of smoke.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"满的\", \"phrase\": \"full of smoke|充满烟雾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ship went up in flames.\", \"target\": \"flames\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火焰\", \"phrase\": \"up in flames|燃燒殆盡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These figures don't add up.\", \"target\": \"add\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"加起来\", \"phrase\": \"add up|加起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They dropped out of school.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"drop out of|退出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They gave in to my opinion.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让步\", \"phrase\": \"gave in|让步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They live across the river.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在…对面\", \"phrase\": \"across the river|在河对面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They treat me like a child.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"treat...like|像...一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They're very close friends.\", \"target\": \"close\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"亲密的\", \"phrase\": \"close friends|亲密的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This car is easy to handle.\", \"target\": \"handle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"处理\", \"phrase\": \"handle|处理\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This drink is on the house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"on the house|赠送\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This house is not for sale.\", \"target\": \"sale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出售\", \"phrase\": \"for sale|待售\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't cross the border.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"越过\", \"phrase\": \"cross the border|越过边境\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom complains all the time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"all the time|一直\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom decided to stay behind.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"留下\", \"phrase\": \"stay behind|留下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom decided to stay behind.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在后面\", \"phrase\": \"stay behind|留下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't write Mary back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"write back|回信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom drank his orange juice.\", \"target\": \"orange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"橙色的\", \"phrase\": \"orange juice|橙汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom goes to school on foot.\", \"target\": \"foot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脚\", \"phrase\": \"on foot|步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had a decision to make.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"make a decision|做决定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a pretty big mouth.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"pretty big mouth|嘴巴很大\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a pretty big mouth.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big mouth|大嘴巴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a pretty big mouth.\", \"target\": \"mouth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"嘴巴\", \"phrase\": \"big mouth|大嘴巴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been gone for ages.\", \"target\": \"ages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"for ages|很久了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has low blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"low\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"低\", \"phrase\": \"low blood pressure|低血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has low blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"pressure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血压\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has made a big mistake.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big mistake|大错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom helped me fix my watch.\", \"target\": \"fix\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"fix my watch|修理我的手表\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is Mary's ex-boyfriend.\", \"target\": \"ex\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"前任的\", \"phrase\": \"ex-boyfriend|前男友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the easy-going sort.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易的\", \"phrase\": \"easy-going|随和的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the easy-going sort.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去的\", \"phrase\": \"easy-going|随和的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the easy-going sort.\", \"target\": \"sort\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"类型;种类\", \"phrase\": \"easy-going sort|随和的人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom passed away last night.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"去世\", \"phrase\": \"passed away|去世\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom showed up just in time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"in time|及时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sneaked up behind Mary.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind Mary|在玛丽后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom speaks French a little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom studies French as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom used to live near Mary.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near Mary|在玛丽附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted Mary to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants a glass of water.\", \"target\": \"glass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玻璃杯\", \"phrase\": \"glass of water|一杯水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom won't be late, will he?\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will he|他会吗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the radio up a little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Volleyball is a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Wait here till I come back.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"wait till|等候直到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We really had a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of fun|很多乐趣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We went to school together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"together|一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were driven to the wall.\", \"target\": \"driven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驱使\", \"phrase\": \"driven to the wall|被逼到绝境\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were driven to the wall.\", \"target\": \"wall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"墙\", \"phrase\": \"driven to the wall|被逼到绝境\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're almost like brothers.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like brothers|像兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're almost like brothers.\", \"target\": \"brothers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"兄弟\", \"phrase\": \"like brothers|像兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What browser are you using?\", \"target\": \"using\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"are using|正在使用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is your date of birth?\", \"target\": \"date\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"日期\", \"phrase\": \"date of birth|出生日期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's the round-trip fare?\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"圆形\", \"phrase\": \"round-trip|往返\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's the round-trip fare?\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"round-trip|往返\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where's the telephone book?\", \"target\": \"telephone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话簿\", \"phrase\": \"telephone book|电话簿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who are you calling stupid?\", \"target\": \"calling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"calling stupid|打电话给蠢货\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who does the gun belong to?\", \"target\": \"belong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"属于\", \"phrase\": \"belong to|属于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't you take a break?\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you close the window?\", \"target\": \"close\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"close the window|关上窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you pass me the salt?\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"递过\", \"phrase\": \"pass me|递给我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Wow! It's been a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are always watching TV.\", \"target\": \"watching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"watching TV|看电视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't park around here.\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停车\", \"phrase\": \"park around here|在这里停车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't park around here.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|在这里周围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You make life worth living.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"worth living|值得活着的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should give up smoking.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放弃\", \"phrase\": \"give up|放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should give up smoking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"give up smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Your sweater is inside out.\", \"target\": \"inside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在里面\", \"phrase\": \"inside out|反穿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Your sweater is inside out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向外\", \"phrase\": \"inside out|里外翻转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How do you feel?\\\" he asked.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"asked him|问他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stitch in time saves nine.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"in time|及时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stitch in time saves nine.\", \"target\": \"saves\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"节省\", \"phrase\": \"saves nine|节省九个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stitch in time saves nine.\", \"target\": \"nine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"九\", \"phrase\": \"saves nine|省九\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stitch in time saves nine.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"in time|及时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stitch in time saves nine.\", \"target\": \"saves\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"节省\", \"phrase\": \"saves nine|节省九个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stitch in time saves nine.\", \"target\": \"nine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"九\", \"phrase\": \"saves nine|省九\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An elephant has a long nose.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long nose|长鼻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you all listening to me?\", \"target\": \"listening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"listening to me|听我说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you good at calligraphy?\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good at|擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you good at mathematics?\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good at|擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Birch trees have white bark.\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"white bark|白色的树皮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Choose one from among these.\", \"target\": \"among\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之中\", \"phrase\": \"among these|在这些之中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you sign here, please?\", \"target\": \"sign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"签名\", \"phrase\": \"sign here|在这里签名\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you already eat at home?\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"at home|在家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you do this on your own?\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"自己\", \"phrase\": \"on your own|独自地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you go to the book fair?\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"book fair|书展\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you go to the book fair?\", \"target\": \"fair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"集市\", \"phrase\": \"book fair|书展\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you watch TV last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Didn't you lock up your car?\", \"target\": \"lock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"锁\", \"phrase\": \"lock up|锁好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you hear what I'm saying?\", \"target\": \"saying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"what I'm saying|我说的话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how to use this?\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use this|使用这个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you like to watch movies?\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"watch movies|看电影\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want a cup of coffee?\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯\", \"phrase\": \"cup of coffee|咖啡杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want a glass of soda?\", \"target\": \"glass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玻璃杯\", \"phrase\": \"glass of soda|一杯苏打水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to buy anything?\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy anything|买东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't walk alone after dark.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"walk alone|独自走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't walk alone after dark.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"walk alone|独自走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry. You'll make it.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成功\", \"phrase\": \"make it|成功\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get them before they get us.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get us|抓住我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get them before they get us.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get us|抓住我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Has she ever fallen in love?\", \"target\": \"fallen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坠入爱河\", \"phrase\": \"fallen in love|坠入爱河\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you washed the car yet?\", \"target\": \"washed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗过\", \"phrase\": \"washed the car|洗车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can pull strings for you.\", \"target\": \"pull\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拉\", \"phrase\": \"pull strings|动用关系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can pull strings for you.\", \"target\": \"strings\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"pull strings|动用关系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He could not breathe deeply.\", \"target\": \"deeply\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"深深地\", \"phrase\": \"breathe deeply|深深地呼吸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He did his best to help her.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do his best|尽最大努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He did his best to help her.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help her|帮助她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He failed the entrance exam.\", \"target\": \"entrance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"入口\", \"phrase\": \"entrance exam|入学考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a bit like his father.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|稍微\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a bit like his father.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"a bit like|有点像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a head taller than me.\", \"target\": \"head\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头\", \"phrase\": \"head taller|高出...一头\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is giving me a hard time.\", \"target\": \"giving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"giving me a hard time|给我难受\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is giving me a hard time.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"hard time|艰难的时刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is giving me a hard time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"hard time|艰难的时刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is just pulling your leg.\", \"target\": \"pulling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开玩笑\", \"phrase\": \"pulling your leg|开玩笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is just pulling your leg.\", \"target\": \"leg\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"腿\", \"phrase\": \"pulling your leg|开玩笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is looking forward to it.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向前\", \"phrase\": \"looking forward to|期待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is rarely in a good mood.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good mood|好心情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is rather hard to please.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取悦\", \"phrase\": \"hard to please|难以取悦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is still very much alive.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"very still|非常安静\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is still very much alive.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows how to drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made fun of me in public.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"嘲笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may be on the next train.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next train|下一班火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He really likes music a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He rushed out of the office.\", \"target\": \"rushed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"冲出\", \"phrase\": \"rushed out|冲出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He rushed out of the office.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"rushed out|冲出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said it merely as a joke.\", \"target\": \"joke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玩笑\", \"phrase\": \"as a joke|作为玩笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sometimes drops in on me.\", \"target\": \"drops\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"掉落\", \"phrase\": \"drops in|顺便来访\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me not to tell lies.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"tell lies|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took her out for a drive.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"took her out|带她出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took her out for a drive.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"for a drive|开车兜风\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He treats me like his slave.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"treats me like|像对待我一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He vowed to give up smoking.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放弃\", \"phrase\": \"give up|放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was standing at the door.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"at the door|在门边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He will be back in a second.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"be back|回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He will be back in a second.\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"秒\", \"phrase\": \"in a second|一秒钟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hello, who am I speaking to?\", \"target\": \"speaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"speaking to|和...说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her garden is a work of art.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"作品\", \"phrase\": \"work of art|艺术品\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His advice didn't help much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太...\", \"phrase\": \"not much|不多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His house was small and old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old house|旧房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hold your horses, young man.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等一下\", \"phrase\": \"hold your horses|稍等\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hold your horses, young man.\", \"target\": \"horses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"hold your horses|稍安勿躁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hold your horses, young man.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等一下\", \"phrase\": \"hold your horses|稍等\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hold your horses, young man.\", \"target\": \"horses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"hold your horses|稍安勿躁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about going for a drive?\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开车\", \"phrase\": \"going for a drive|开车兜风\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about going out tonight?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did Tom get out of jail?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"get out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I also had a very good time.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very good time|美好的时光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am blind in the right eye.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"right eye|右眼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am dying for a cold drink.\", \"target\": \"dying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"渴望\", \"phrase\": \"dying for|渴望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am dying for a cold drink.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold drink|冷饮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am going to buy a new car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new car|新车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am playing volleyball now.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在玩\", \"phrase\": \"playing volleyball|打排球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought two pairs of pants.\", \"target\": \"pairs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"双\", \"phrase\": \"pairs of pants|裤子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can swim across the river.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"swim across|游泳穿过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't do without her help.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"do without|没有...缺少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't do without her help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"her help|她的帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I could hear doors slamming.\", \"target\": \"doors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"slamming doors|砰地关门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I could hear doors slamming.\", \"target\": \"slamming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb-ing\", \"zh\": \"砰地关门\", \"phrase\": \"doors slamming|门砰地关门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I crossed the river by boat.\", \"target\": \"boat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"船\", \"phrase\": \"by boat|乘船\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't get along with her.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"和...相处\", \"phrase\": \"get along with|和...相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not know how to use it.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use it|使用它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't need to do anything.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何事\", \"phrase\": \"do anything|做任何事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want either of them.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"也不\", \"phrase\": \"either of them|他们中的任何一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I eventually got used to it.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"got used to|习惯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feel like going out today.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forget where I put my hat.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put my hat|放我的帽子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found the boy fast asleep.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"迅速地\", \"phrase\": \"fast asleep|快速地睡着了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found the boy fast asleep.\", \"target\": \"asleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"睡着的\", \"phrase\": \"fast asleep|熟睡的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave it to the little boy.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"little boy|小男孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got him to fix my bicycle.\", \"target\": \"fix\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"fix my bicycle|修理我的自行车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I guess it was our bad luck.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"bad luck|坏运气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a phone call from him.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"phone call|电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a phone call from him.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"phone call|电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a shower every night.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every night|每晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no knife to cut with.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"切\", \"phrase\": \"cut with|用...切\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to renew my passport.\", \"target\": \"renew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"更新\", \"phrase\": \"renew my passport|更新我的护照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you for ages.\", \"target\": \"ages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"for ages|很久了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard a knock at the door.\", \"target\": \"knock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"敲门声\", \"phrase\": \"knock at the door|敲门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope everything goes well.\", \"target\": \"goes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进展顺利\", \"phrase\": \"goes well|进展顺利\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope everything goes well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"goes well|进展顺利\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope it'll work next time.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下次\", \"phrase\": \"next time|下次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know Tom is looking at me.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"looking at|看着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like strawberry ice cream.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"strawberry ice cream|草莓冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like strawberry ice cream.\", \"target\": \"cream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奶油\", \"phrase\": \"strawberry ice cream|草莓冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must make up for the loss.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弥补\", \"phrase\": \"make up for|弥补\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I nearly fell off the cliff.\", \"target\": \"fell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"差点摔倒\", \"phrase\": \"fell off|从...掉落\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to renew my passport.\", \"target\": \"renew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"更新\", \"phrase\": \"renew my passport|更新我的护照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I only took a bite of bread.\", \"target\": \"bite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一口\", \"phrase\": \"a bite of bread|一口面包\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I plan to break up with her.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分手\", \"phrase\": \"break up|分手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a girl with long hair.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long hair|长发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a girl with long hair.\", \"target\": \"hair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头发\", \"phrase\": \"long hair|长发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him crossing the road.\", \"target\": \"crossing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"过\", \"phrase\": \"crossing the road|过马路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I see a woman wearing black.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"wearing black|穿着黑色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I see her sweeping the room.\", \"target\": \"sweeping\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扫\", \"phrase\": \"sweeping the room|清扫房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I stayed at home last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I stayed up late last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think he will do his best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"do his best|尽力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I visit him every other day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every other day|隔一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go to see a movie.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"go to see|去看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to see him very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want us to do it together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"do it together|一起做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was thinking that as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was very tired last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you the best of luck.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best of luck|祝你好运\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you were close to me.\", \"target\": \"close\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"亲近的\", \"phrase\": \"close to|靠近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't be home next Sunday.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next Sunday|下个星期天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't talk to him anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like a room in the back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"后部\", \"phrase\": \"in the back|在后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to buy half a cake.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一半\", \"phrase\": \"half a cake|半个蛋糕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll act as a guide for you.\", \"target\": \"guide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"向导\", \"phrase\": \"act as a guide|充当向导\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be seventeen next year.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之后\", \"phrase\": \"next year|明年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be there rain or shine.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨\", \"phrase\": \"rain or shine|风雨无阻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be there rain or shine.\", \"target\": \"shine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阳光明媚\", \"phrase\": \"rain or shine|风雨无阻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll find you a good doctor.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good doctor|好医生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll get started right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"马上\", \"phrase\": \"right away|马上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll pay you back next week.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"pay back|还款\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll pay you back next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see you next Wednesday.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next Wednesday|下周三\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a lot of questions.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've worn holes in my socks.\", \"target\": \"worn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿破\", \"phrase\": \"worn holes|穿破袜子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've worn holes in my socks.\", \"target\": \"holes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞\", \"phrase\": \"worn holes|磨损的洞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it hard to speak English?\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speak English|说英语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It happened a long time ago.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is a sheer waste of time.\", \"target\": \"waste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"waste of time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is a sheer waste of time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"waste of time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It never rains but it pours.\", \"target\": \"pours\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"倾盆而下\", \"phrase\": \"rains but it pours|下雨就下倾盆大雨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It never rains but it pours.\", \"target\": \"pours\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"倾盆而下\", \"phrase\": \"rains but it pours|下雨就下倾盆大雨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just around the corner.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the corner|转角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just around the corner.\", \"target\": \"corner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"拐角\", \"phrase\": \"around the corner|转角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's nothing to worry about.\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没什么\", \"phrase\": \"nothing to worry about|不用担心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep oil away from the fire.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"away from|远离...从\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let your hair down a little.\", \"target\": \"hair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头发\", \"phrase\": \"let your hair down|放松\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let your hair down a little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"let your hair down a little|放松一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's clear up this problem.\", \"target\": \"clear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"clear up|解决\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's clear up this problem.\", \"target\": \"clear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"clear up|解决\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many books have been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"have been stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I speak to you a minute?\", \"target\": \"minute\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"a minute|一分钟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Maybe we should open it now.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open it|打开它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mom is getting dinner ready.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"getting ready|准备好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My blood type is A positive.\", \"target\": \"positive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"积极的\", \"phrase\": \"A positive|A型阳性\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a heavy smoker.\", \"target\": \"heavy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重的\", \"phrase\": \"heavy smoker|重烟民\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in good health.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good health|身体好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house is near the school.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the school|在学校附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nature is full of mysteries.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"充满的\", \"phrase\": \"full of mysteries|充满神秘\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now shake hands and make up.\", \"target\": \"shake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握手\", \"phrase\": \"shake hands|握手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now shake hands and make up.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"shake hands|握手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now shake hands and make up.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"和解\", \"phrase\": \"make up|和解\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Oh, no! My house is on fire!\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"on fire|着火\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Open your book to page nine.\", \"target\": \"page\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"页\", \"phrase\": \"page nine|第9页\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Open your book to page nine.\", \"target\": \"page\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"页\", \"phrase\": \"page nine|第9页\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our classroom is very small.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"very small|非常小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't leave me alone.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave me alone|让我一个人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't leave me alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"leave alone|独自留下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Safety is what matters most.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"matters most|最重要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She always gets her own way.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own way|自己的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She came back an hour later.\", \"target\": \"hour\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"an hour|一个小时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She can never keep a secret.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保守\", \"phrase\": \"keep a secret|保守秘密\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She dressed like an actress.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"dressed like|穿着像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave away all her dolls.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"gave away|赠送\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave him a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave me these old coins.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old coins|旧硬币\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She grabbed him by the hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"by the hand|握着手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She greeted us with a smile.\", \"target\": \"smile\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"微笑\", \"phrase\": \"with a smile|带着微笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a lot of work to do.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has an eye for antiques.\", \"target\": \"eye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"eye for|眼光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is drunk with happiness.\", \"target\": \"drunk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"醉的\", \"phrase\": \"drunk with happiness|陶醉于幸福\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is drunk with happiness.\", \"target\": \"happiness\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"幸福\", \"phrase\": \"drunk with happiness|陶醉于幸福\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is watering the flowers.\", \"target\": \"watering\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浇水\", \"phrase\": \"watering the flowers|浇花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made a mess of the work.\", \"target\": \"mess\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"混乱\", \"phrase\": \"make a mess of|搞砸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made a mess of the work.\", \"target\": \"mess\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"混乱\", \"phrase\": \"make a mess of|搞砸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made fun of her husband.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She owns two thousand books.\", \"target\": \"thousand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"千\", \"phrase\": \"two thousand|两千\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She ran as fast as possible.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as possible|尽可能快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She ran as fast as possible.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"as possible|尽可能地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She rides a motorcycle well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"rides well|骑得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She stabbed him in the back.\", \"target\": \"stabbed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"刺伤\", \"phrase\": \"stabbed in the back|背后捅刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She stabbed him in the back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"背部\", \"phrase\": \"stab in the back|背后捅刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She thanked us for our help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"our help|我们的帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tried to commit suicide.\", \"target\": \"commit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"实施\", \"phrase\": \"commit suicide|自杀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tried to commit suicide.\", \"target\": \"commit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"实施\", \"phrase\": \"commit suicide|自杀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was accepted by Harvard.\", \"target\": \"accepted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被接受\", \"phrase\": \"accepted by|被...接受\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was almost hit by a car.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撞击\", \"phrase\": \"almost hit|差点撞到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was holding an umbrella.\", \"target\": \"holding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿着\", \"phrase\": \"holding an umbrella|拿着雨伞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was in time for the bus.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"in time|准时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was wearing a blue coat.\", \"target\": \"blue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"蓝色\", \"phrase\": \"blue coat|蓝色外套\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She won't be back till five.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"till five|直到五点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She won't be back till five.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"till five|直到五点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Singing is her strong point.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强壮的\", \"phrase\": \"strong point|强项\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Singing is her strong point.\", \"target\": \"point\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"要点\", \"phrase\": \"strong point|强项\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some gum stuck to his shoes.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"粘住\", \"phrase\": \"stuck to|粘在...上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take off your socks, please.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tears rolled down my cheeks.\", \"target\": \"rolled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"滚落\", \"phrase\": \"rolled down|滚落\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That isn't altogether false.\", \"target\": \"altogether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全地\", \"phrase\": \"altogether false|完全地错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's not altogether false.\", \"target\": \"altogether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全地\", \"phrase\": \"not altogether|并非完全\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy got his hands dirty.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"dirty hands|脏手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy got his hands dirty.\", \"target\": \"dirty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"脏的\", \"phrase\": \"got his hands dirty|弄脏了手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bus was behind schedule.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在…后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind schedule|落后于计划\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bus was behind schedule.\", \"target\": \"schedule\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间表\", \"phrase\": \"behind schedule|落后于时间表\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dog is blind in one eye.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one eye|一只眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dog is blind in one eye.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one eye|一只眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The room is fully furnished.\", \"target\": \"fully\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全地\", \"phrase\": \"fully furnished|完全地配备\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The store is closed Mondays.\", \"target\": \"closed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"关闭的\", \"phrase\": \"closed Mondays|周一关闭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is no place like home.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like home|像家一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They all burst out laughing.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"burst out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They left one after another.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"one after another|一个接一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They live in a rented house.\", \"target\": \"rented\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"出租的\", \"phrase\": \"rented house|出租的房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This car needs to be washed.\", \"target\": \"washed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗过的\", \"phrase\": \"be washed|被洗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This should be a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Those chairs are in the way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"in the way|在路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Three bulbs have burned out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"熄灭\", \"phrase\": \"burned out|烧坏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can swim as fast as you.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as|像...一样快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't speak French well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"speak well|说得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't speak much French.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太...了\", \"phrase\": \"not much|不多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom drank some orange juice.\", \"target\": \"orange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"橙色的\", \"phrase\": \"orange juice|橙汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom drank some orange juice.\", \"target\": \"juice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"果汁\", \"phrase\": \"orange juice|橙汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom finally gave up smoking.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放弃\", \"phrase\": \"gave up|放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom finally gave up smoking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"gave up smoking|放弃吸烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to sign his name.\", \"target\": \"sign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"签名\", \"phrase\": \"sign his name|签署他的名字\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to sign his name.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his name|他的名字\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave a different answer.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"different answer|不同的答案\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had a drink in his hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"in his hand|在他手中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had trouble standing up.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"had trouble|遇到麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had trouble standing up.\", \"target\": \"standing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"站立\", \"phrase\": \"standing up|站起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has high blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high blood pressure|高血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has high blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"blood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血液\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has high blood pressure.\", \"target\": \"pressure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血压\", \"phrase\": \"blood pressure|血压\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom helped me with the move.\", \"target\": \"move\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"搬家\", \"phrase\": \"with the move|和搬家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a decent sort of guy.\", \"target\": \"sort\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"类型;种类\", \"phrase\": \"sort of|类型;种类\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is about to fall asleep.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"入睡\", \"phrase\": \"fall asleep|入睡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is almost six feet tall.\", \"target\": \"feet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"英尺\", \"phrase\": \"six feet|六英尺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is already used to that.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"used to|习惯于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is drinking apple juice.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"apple juice|苹果汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is drinking apple juice.\", \"target\": \"juice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"果汁\", \"phrase\": \"apple juice|苹果汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is just a crazy old man.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old man|老头\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is not easily satisfied.\", \"target\": \"easily\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"容易地\", \"phrase\": \"not easily satisfied|不轻易满足\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put down his paintbrush.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放下\", \"phrase\": \"put down|放下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says Mary can't do that.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't do|不能做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom seems a little confused.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little confused|有点儿困惑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom slept with his shoes on.\", \"target\": \"shoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋子\", \"phrase\": \"shoes on|穿着鞋子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tore the ticket to bits.\", \"target\": \"tore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撕碎\", \"phrase\": \"tore to bits|撕成碎片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tore the ticket to bits.\", \"target\": \"bits\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"碎片\", \"phrase\": \"to bits|成碎片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to take a shower.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿;取\", \"phrase\": \"take a shower|洗澡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was completely worn out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"精疲力尽\", \"phrase\": \"worn out|精疲力尽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was making French fries.\", \"target\": \"fries\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"炸薯条\", \"phrase\": \"French fries|炸薯条\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was sent back to Boston.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"sent back|被送回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's parachute didn't open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Try and do better next time.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下次\", \"phrase\": \"next time|下次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Valuable time has been lost.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"lost time|时间损失\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Waitress, I'd like to order.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"点餐\", \"phrase\": \"to order|点餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We can change if we want to.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We get together once a year.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"get together|聚在一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We gladly accept your offer.\", \"target\": \"accept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"accept your offer|接受你的提议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We got together in the park.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"got together|聚在一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a kid just last year.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"last year|去年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had to go there together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"go together|一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We kept our fingers crossed.\", \"target\": \"fingers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手指\", \"phrase\": \"fingers crossed|交叉手指\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We kept our fingers crossed.\", \"target\": \"crossed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"交叉\", \"phrase\": \"fingers crossed|交叉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We soon caught up with them.\", \"target\": \"caught\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"追上\", \"phrase\": \"caught up with|追上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're fighting against time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"against time|与时间赛跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're friends from way back.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很久\", \"phrase\": \"way back|很久以前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're friends from way back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"way back|很久以前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Were you working last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you do for a living?\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"for a living|谋生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What goes up must come down.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下来\", \"phrase\": \"come down|下来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is it you want to know?\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to know|想知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What trips are you planning?\", \"target\": \"planning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"are planning|正在计划\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's done can't be undone.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't|不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's the idea behind that?\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind that|在...后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where is the lost and found?\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"丢失的\", \"phrase\": \"lost and found|失物招领处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where is the lost and found?\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"找到的东西\", \"phrase\": \"lost and found|失物招领处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which club do you belong to?\", \"target\": \"belong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"属于\", \"phrase\": \"belong to|属于...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who does the book belong to?\", \"target\": \"belong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"属于\", \"phrase\": \"belong to|属于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why did you try to run away?\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"run away|逃跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why did you try to run away?\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"逃跑\", \"phrase\": \"run away|逃跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you care for some tea?\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"在乎; 关心\", \"phrase\": \"care for|关心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like another beer?\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another beer|另一杯啤酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to go abroad?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go abroad|出国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you look after my cat?\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看顾\", \"phrase\": \"look after|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Yesterday he came back late.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"came back|回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can always count on Tom.\", \"target\": \"count\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"count on|依靠\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't have it both ways.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't have|不能有\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't have it both ways.\", \"target\": \"ways\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"both ways|两种方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to clean your room.\", \"target\": \"clean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打扫\", \"phrase\": \"clean your room|打扫你的房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to sweep the floor.\", \"target\": \"sweep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扫\", \"phrase\": \"sweep the floor|扫地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may leave your bag here.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave your bag|放下你的包\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You need two to make a pair.\", \"target\": \"pair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"对子\", \"phrase\": \"make a pair|组成一对\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should begin right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"马上\", \"phrase\": \"right away|马上开始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should put your coat on.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put on|穿上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You won't be late, will you?\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will you|你将\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better check this out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"particle\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"check out|查看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're your own worst enemy.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own worst enemy|自己最大的敌人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're your own worst enemy.\", \"target\": \"worst\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最坏的\", \"phrase\": \"worst enemy|最坏的敌人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got a one-track mind.\", \"target\": \"track\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轨道; 路线\", \"phrase\": \"one-track mind|单一思维\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"You talk too much,\\\" he said.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"talk too much|说太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bottle of red wine, please.\", \"target\": \"bottle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"瓶子\", \"phrase\": \"bottle of red wine|红葡萄酒瓶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bottle of red wine, please.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"red wine|红酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bottle of red wine, please.\", \"target\": \"wine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"葡萄酒\", \"phrase\": \"red wine|红酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A lot of trees were cut down.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"砍\", \"phrase\": \"cut down|砍倒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of us like you very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you coming along with us?\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"coming along|一起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you listening to English?\", \"target\": \"listening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"listening to|听...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As you sow, so will you reap.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"sow, so will you reap|种瓜得瓜，种豆得豆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be sure to pick up some milk.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"pick up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I catch a taxi near here?\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near here|在这里附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you see that small house?\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"small house|小房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you see that small house?\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"small house|小房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children need a lot of sleep.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I have a cup of coffee?\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯\", \"phrase\": \"cup of coffee|咖啡杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you call me back later?\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call me back|回电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you call me back later?\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"call back|回电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you take me to a movie?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take me to|带我去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a gift shop here?\", \"target\": \"shop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"商店\", \"phrase\": \"gift shop|礼品店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't bite on the right side.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"right side|右侧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't bite on the right side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"边\", \"phrase\": \"right side|右边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't exceed the speed limit.\", \"target\": \"exceed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"超过\", \"phrase\": \"exceed the speed limit|超过速度限制\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't exceed the speed limit.\", \"target\": \"speed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"速度\", \"phrase\": \"speed limit|速度限制\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't exceed the speed limit.\", \"target\": \"limit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"限制\", \"phrase\": \"speed limit|速度限制\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave me alone, please.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"leave alone|独自离开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't make fun of old people.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|嘲笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get off your high horse, Tom.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下来\", \"phrase\": \"get off|下来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get off your high horse, Tom.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high horse|高高在上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get off your high horse, Tom.\", \"target\": \"horse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"high horse|高傲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have a look at the world map.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"have a look|看一看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always wears dark glasses.\", \"target\": \"glasses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼镜\", \"phrase\": \"dark glasses|太阳镜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He appeared on TV last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He asked the man to help him.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help him|帮助他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can play tennis very well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"play well|打得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can speak Russian as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"speak well|说得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He earns twice as much as me.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"那么\", \"phrase\": \"twice as much|是...的两倍\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave her a piece of paper.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一块\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|纸片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave it to me for nothing.\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"什么也没有\", \"phrase\": \"for nothing|白白地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is able to swim very fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"very fast|非常快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is allergic to house dust.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"house dust|室内灰尘\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is allergic to house dust.\", \"target\": \"dust\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灰尘\", \"phrase\": \"house dust|室内灰尘\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is going to run for mayor.\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"竞选\", \"phrase\": \"run for mayor|竞选市长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at playing tennis.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打\", \"phrase\": \"playing tennis|打网球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is hard to get along with.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相处\", \"phrase\": \"get along with|相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is hard to get along with.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"和...相处\", \"phrase\": \"get along with|和...相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is not what he used to be.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"used to be|过去常常是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is up to his ears in debt.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"up to his ears|债台高筑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is up to his ears in debt.\", \"target\": \"ears\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"耳朵\", \"phrase\": \"up to his ears|债台高筑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is up to his ears in debt.\", \"target\": \"debt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"债务\", \"phrase\": \"up to his ears in debt|负债累累\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows New York inside out.\", \"target\": \"inside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"彻底地\", \"phrase\": \"inside out|里里外外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows New York inside out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"彻底地\", \"phrase\": \"inside out|里里外外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made me his own assistant.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his own|他自己的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made me his own assistant.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"his own|他自己的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may have missed the train.\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"missed the train|错过火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He played the part of Hamlet.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"角色\", \"phrase\": \"played the part|扮演角色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He prays several times a day.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"several times a day|一天几次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He set fire to his own house.\", \"target\": \"set\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"点燃\", \"phrase\": \"set fire to|点火\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He set fire to his own house.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"set fire to|纵火\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He set fire to his own house.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own house|自己的房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He traveled around the world.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the world|环游世界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wants to pay off his loan.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"pay off|还清\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Health is better than wealth.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better than|胜过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her skin is as white as snow.\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"as white as snow|像雪一样白\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her skin is as white as snow.\", \"target\": \"snow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雪\", \"phrase\": \"as white as snow|像雪一样白\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about dining out tonight?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"dining out|外出就餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do you want this handled?\", \"target\": \"handled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"处理\", \"phrase\": \"handled|处理\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is the entrance fee?\", \"target\": \"entrance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"入口费\", \"phrase\": \"entrance fee|入场费\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hurry. Please lend me a hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"lend a hand|帮忙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I advertised my car for sale.\", \"target\": \"sale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出售\", \"phrase\": \"for sale|待售\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I asked her to wait a minute.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等\", \"phrase\": \"wait a minute|等一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought a round-trip ticket.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"圆形\", \"phrase\": \"round-trip ticket|往返票\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought a round-trip ticket.\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"round-trip ticket|往返票\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought two loaves of bread.\", \"target\": \"bread\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"面包\", \"phrase\": \"loaves of bread|面包\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can do it without her help.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without her help|没有她的帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can do it without her help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"her help|她的帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't just let Tom kill me.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"let Tom kill|让汤姆杀死\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I cannot afford to buy a car.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"afford to buy|负担得起买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I cannot find fault with him.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"find fault with|挑...的毛病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I cannot speak Mandarin well.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speak Mandarin|说普通话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I cannot speak Mandarin well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"speak well|说得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not love him any longer.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"any longer|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't read newspapers much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太...了\", \"phrase\": \"not much|不多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want him to touch me.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"触摸\", \"phrase\": \"touch me|触摸我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to play anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"not anymore|再也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave up smoking a year ago.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"gave up smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave up smoking for a year.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"gave up smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got it for next to nothing.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"几乎\", \"phrase\": \"next to nothing|几乎一文不值\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got it for next to nothing.\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"什么也没有\", \"phrase\": \"next to nothing|几乎一文不值\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got slapped on both cheeks.\", \"target\": \"cheeks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸颊\", \"phrase\": \"both cheeks|双颊\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I grew up in this small town.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"small town|小镇\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no friends to help me.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help me|帮助我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to the bathroom.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the bathroom|去洗手间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope no one saw me dancing.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有人\", \"phrase\": \"no one|没有人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope this is the right one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"right one|正确的那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just can't take it anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也\", \"phrase\": \"can't take it anymore|受不了了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know this area pretty well.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"pretty well|相当好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know this area pretty well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"pretty well|相当好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must catch the first train.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"first train|第一班火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to know what you know.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"what you know|你知道什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I never drink tea with lemon.\", \"target\": \"lemon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"柠檬\", \"phrase\": \"tea with lemon|柠檬茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I only speak a little French.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe my success to his help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"his help|他的帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I paid him a visit yesterday.\", \"target\": \"visit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"paid a visit|拜访\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a horse pulling a cart.\", \"target\": \"pulling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拉\", \"phrase\": \"pulling a cart|拉车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a man get hit by a car.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"击中\", \"phrase\": \"get hit by|被击中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I swear I didn't do anything.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何事\", \"phrase\": \"do anything|做任何事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I talked him out of the idea.\", \"target\": \"talked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说服\", \"phrase\": \"talked him out of|说服他放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I talked him out of the idea.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"talk out of|说服...放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is getting ready.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"准备\", \"phrase\": \"getting ready|准备好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is getting ready.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"getting ready|准备好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I understand it more or less.\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微地\", \"phrase\": \"more or less|多多少少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like a room in the front.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in the front|在前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to order drinks now.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"点餐\", \"phrase\": \"order drinks|点饮料\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll attend the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next meeting|下次会议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll attend the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next meeting|下次会议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm as tired as tired can be.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疲惫的\", \"phrase\": \"tired as tired can be|累得不行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm blessed with good health.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good health|健康\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm blessed with good health.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good health|健康\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not very good at drawing.\", \"target\": \"drawing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"画画\", \"phrase\": \"good at drawing|擅长画画\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on my way back to Boston.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way|在路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on my way back to Boston.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"on my way back|回来的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry, I can't stay long.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"久\", \"phrase\": \"stay long|停留时间长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the tallest in our class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"our class|我们班\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"frog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青蛙\", \"phrase\": \"frog in my throat|嗓子不舒服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"throat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喉咙\", \"phrase\": \"in my throat|在我的喉咙里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"frog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青蛙\", \"phrase\": \"frog in my throat|嗓子不舒服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a frog in my throat.\", \"target\": \"throat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喉咙\", \"phrase\": \"in my throat|在我的喉咙里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a lot more to learn.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it OK if I hold your hand?\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握住\", \"phrase\": \"hold your hand|握住你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it OK if I hold your hand?\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"hold your hand|握住你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it okay if I take a break?\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a break|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a hotel around here?\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|这里附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't make any difference.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起作用\", \"phrase\": \"make any difference|没有区别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's already time to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's already time to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's no use arguing with him.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"用处\", \"phrase\": \"no use|没用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's on the tip of my tongue.\", \"target\": \"tip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顶端\", \"phrase\": \"tip of my tongue|舌尖上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's on the tip of my tongue.\", \"target\": \"tongue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"舌头\", \"phrase\": \"tip of the tongue|舌尖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I pay with a credit card?\", \"target\": \"credit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信用卡\", \"phrase\": \"credit card|信用卡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I pay with a credit card?\", \"target\": \"card\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卡片\", \"phrase\": \"credit card|信用卡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money does not grow on trees.\", \"target\": \"grow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生长\", \"phrase\": \"grow on trees|在树上生长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money does not grow on trees.\", \"target\": \"trees\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"grow on trees|在树上生长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is fifty years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"fifty years|五十岁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father's going to kill me.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"going to kill|将要杀死\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My hobby is stamp collecting.\", \"target\": \"stamp\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邮票\", \"phrase\": \"stamp collecting|集邮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My hobby is stamp collecting.\", \"target\": \"collecting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"收集\", \"phrase\": \"stamp collecting|集邮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house is five blocks away.\", \"target\": \"blocks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"街区\", \"phrase\": \"five blocks|五个街区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house is five blocks away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"blocks away|离开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My house is near the station.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the station|在车站附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My job is to wash the dishes.\", \"target\": \"wash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"wash the dishes|洗碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My job is to wash the dishes.\", \"target\": \"wash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"wash the dishes|洗碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My job is to wash the dishes.\", \"target\": \"wash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"wash the dishes|洗碗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My son is brushing his teeth.\", \"target\": \"brushing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"刷\", \"phrase\": \"brushing his teeth|刷牙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My son is brushing his teeth.\", \"target\": \"brushing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"刷\", \"phrase\": \"brushing his teeth|刷牙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No man can serve two masters.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"两个\", \"phrase\": \"two masters|两个主人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Oil is extracted from olives.\", \"target\": \"extracted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提取\", \"phrase\": \"extracted from olives|从橄榄中提取\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our supplies are running out.\", \"target\": \"running\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"running out|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our supplies are running out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"running out|耗尽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please get me hotel security.\", \"target\": \"security\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"保安\", \"phrase\": \"hotel security|酒店保安\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please make yourself at home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"at home|在家里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please put those chairs away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"put away|收起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Remember to brush your teeth.\", \"target\": \"brush\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"刷\", \"phrase\": \"brush your teeth|刷牙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Say which one you would like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She can't ride a bicycle yet.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑\", \"phrase\": \"ride a bicycle|骑自行车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She earns 30 dollars per day.\", \"target\": \"per\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"per day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave birth to twin girls.\", \"target\": \"twin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"双胞胎的\", \"phrase\": \"twin girls|双胞胎女孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a flower in her hand.\", \"target\": \"flower\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"a flower|一朵花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a flower in her hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"in her hand|在她的手中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a strong personality.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强壮的\", \"phrase\": \"strong personality|性格强\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has plenty of work to do.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"plenty of work|大量的工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She kindly showed me the way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"the way|道路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She likes to listen to music.\", \"target\": \"listen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"listen to music|听音乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She put on her hat to go out.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took a bite of the apple.\", \"target\": \"bite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"咬\", \"phrase\": \"take a bite|吃一口\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the money was stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被偷\", \"phrase\": \"was stolen|被偷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Someone is playing the piano.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"演奏\", \"phrase\": \"playing the piano|弹钢琴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop staring at me like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like that|那样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Strike while the iron is hot.\", \"target\": \"strike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打击\", \"phrase\": \"strike while the iron is hot|趁热打铁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Strike while the iron is hot.\", \"target\": \"iron\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"铁\", \"phrase\": \"iron is hot|趁热打铁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Strike while the iron is hot.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热的\", \"phrase\": \"iron is hot|铁热的时候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Such a plan is bound to fail.\", \"target\": \"bound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注定\", \"phrase\": \"bound to|注定要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Surgery is the best solution.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best solution|最佳方案\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tell me how to play the game.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play the game|玩游戏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That thought crossed my mind.\", \"target\": \"crossed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"crossed my mind|掠过我的脑海\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The accident held up traffic.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"延误\", \"phrase\": \"held up|延误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bottle smashed to pieces.\", \"target\": \"pieces\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"碎片\", \"phrase\": \"to pieces|成碎片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy made fun of the girl.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy took the radio apart.\", \"target\": \"apart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"分开\", \"phrase\": \"took apart|拆开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car got stuck in the mud.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卡住\", \"phrase\": \"got stuck|卡住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The cost of living has risen.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"cost of living|生活成本\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The cost of living has risen.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"cost of living|生活成本\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The early bird gets the worm.\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"早的\", \"phrase\": \"early bird|早起的鸟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The early bird gets the worm.\", \"target\": \"bird\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸟\", \"phrase\": \"early bird|早起的鸟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The early bird gets the worm.\", \"target\": \"gets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"gets the worm|得到蠕虫\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The girl made an awkward bow.\", \"target\": \"bow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞠躬\", \"phrase\": \"awkward bow|笨拙的鞠躬\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The girl made an awkward bow.\", \"target\": \"bow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞠躬\", \"phrase\": \"awkward bow|笨拙的鞠躬\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The hunter shot the fox dead.\", \"target\": \"dead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"死了的\", \"phrase\": \"shot dead|击毙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The idea is still in my mind.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"in my mind|在我的脑海里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The man is wanted for murder.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被通缉\", \"phrase\": \"is wanted for|被通缉犯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The road parallels the river.\", \"target\": \"parallels\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"平行于\", \"phrase\": \"parallels the river|平行于河流\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a little water left.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"剩余的\", \"phrase\": \"left|剩余的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They forgot to lock the door.\", \"target\": \"lock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"锁\", \"phrase\": \"lock the door|锁门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They gave a big party for me.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big party|大聚会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This bucket has a hole in it.\", \"target\": \"hole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞\", \"phrase\": \"hole in it|漏洞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This car runs on natural gas.\", \"target\": \"natural\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"天然的\", \"phrase\": \"natural gas|天然气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This dress is a good bargain.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good bargain|划算\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This dress is a good bargain.\", \"target\": \"bargain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"便宜货\", \"phrase\": \"good bargain|划算的价格\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a very hard mattress.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"硬的\", \"phrase\": \"hard mattress|硬床垫\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This machine is out of order.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"外\", \"phrase\": \"out of order|失修\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This machine is out of order.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顺序;秩序\", \"phrase\": \"out of order|失灵;故障\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This room is air-conditioned.\", \"target\": \"air\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"空调的\", \"phrase\": \"air-conditioned|空调的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This room is air-conditioned.\", \"target\": \"conditioned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"空调的\", \"phrase\": \"air-conditioned|空调的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always sings out of tune.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of tune|跑调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always sings out of tune.\", \"target\": \"tune\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"调子\", \"phrase\": \"out of tune|跑调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom built his own motorcycle.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"his own|他自己的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom changed into his uniform.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his uniform|他的制服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't say a single word.\", \"target\": \"single\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"单个的\", \"phrase\": \"single word|单个词\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't say a single word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词\", \"phrase\": \"single word|一个词\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom fell asleep at the wheel.\", \"target\": \"wheel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方向盘\", \"phrase\": \"at the wheel|在方向盘上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave Mary a nice present.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"nice present|漂亮的礼物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got rid of his old books.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"got rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got rid of his old books.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old books|旧书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had nowhere to return to.\", \"target\": \"return\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"返回\", \"phrase\": \"return to|回到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a high-pitched voice.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high-pitched|高音调的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has a lot to think about.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has asked us to help him.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help him|帮助他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been here since 2013.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since 2013|自2013年以来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been lying all along.\", \"target\": \"lying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"lying all along|一直说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been lying all along.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一直\", \"phrase\": \"all along|始终\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has got his own problems.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own problems|自己的问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has very broad shoulders.\", \"target\": \"broad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"宽阔的\", \"phrase\": \"broad shoulders|宽阔的肩膀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom hitched a ride to Boston.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"搭车\", \"phrase\": \"hitched a ride|搭便车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a high school student.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"high school|高中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is just a little nervous.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is quite good at cooking.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"quite good|相当好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is reading a short story.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"short story|短篇故事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't a very good driver.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good driver|好司机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom kissed Mary on the cheek.\", \"target\": \"cheek\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸颊\", \"phrase\": \"on the cheek|在脸颊上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom owns a yellow sports car.\", \"target\": \"sports\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运动\", \"phrase\": \"sports car|运动汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put a cover over his car.\", \"target\": \"cover\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盖子\", \"phrase\": \"put a cover over|把盖子盖在...上面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom quit smoking cold turkey.\", \"target\": \"quit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒掉\", \"phrase\": \"quit smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom quit smoking cold turkey.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"quit smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom quit smoking cold turkey.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold turkey|戒断\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"因为\", \"phrase\": \"since I have|因为我拥有\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little money|一点儿钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"little money|一点钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"saved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"储蓄\", \"phrase\": \"saved up|储蓄起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"for the time being|暂时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"won't have trouble|不会有麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"have trouble|有麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"living expenses|生活费用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"expenses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"费用\", \"phrase\": \"living expenses|生活费用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听起来\", \"phrase\": \"sound natural|听起来自然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"natural\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自然的\", \"phrase\": \"sound natural|听起来自然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own native language|母语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"native language|母语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"very easy|很容易\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听起来\", \"phrase\": \"sound unnatural|听起来不自然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"native language|母语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"native language|母语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see you|见到你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"today|今天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"remember from|从...记得\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"过去\", \"phrase\": \"from the past|从过去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't want to put on sunscreen, that's your problem. Just don't come complaining to me when you get a sunburn.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come complaining|抱怨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't want to put on sunscreen, that's your problem. Just don't come complaining to me when you get a sunburn.\", \"target\": \"complaining\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抱怨\", \"phrase\": \"come complaining|来抱怨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't want to put on sunscreen, that's your problem. Just don't come complaining to me when you get a sunburn.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get a sunburn|晒伤\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"term\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"术语\", \"phrase\": \"a term|一个术语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"person of color|有色人种\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"color\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"颜色\", \"phrase\": \"person of color|有色人种\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"implies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"暗示\", \"phrase\": \"implies that|暗示着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"white people|白人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"people|人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"color\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"颜色\", \"phrase\": \"person of color|有色人种\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"talking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"talking to|和...说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"never seen|从未见过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"见过\", \"phrase\": \"had never seen|从未见过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one|一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"speaks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speaks French|说法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"speaks better|说得更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"speaks\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speaks English|说英语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"usually\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"usually speak|通常说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speaks French|说法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"every evening|每个晚上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"evening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚上\", \"phrase\": \"every evening|每晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"days\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"these days|这些天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"given\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"given him|给他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"waves\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"海浪\", \"phrase\": \"tidal waves|海啸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接\", \"phrase\": \"pick her up|接她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his car|他的车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"battered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"破旧的\", \"phrase\": \"battered old car|破旧的老汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old car|旧车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"battered old car|破旧的汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"carefully\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仔细地\", \"phrase\": \"listen carefully|仔细听\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"says what|说什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conditional\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would be able to|能够\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"be able to|能够\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"bars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小节\", \"phrase\": \"few bars|少数乐句\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"money for nothing|一文不值\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"什么\", \"phrase\": \"Money for Nothing|金钱换取虚无\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you remember the time you and I went to the zoo together when you and I were in elementary school?\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"the time|时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you remember the time you and I went to the zoo together when you and I were in elementary school?\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"went to|去...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you remember the time you and I went to the zoo together when you and I were in elementary school?\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"went to the zoo together|一起去动物园\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you remember the time you and I went to the zoo together when you and I were in elementary school?\", \"target\": \"elementary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小学\", \"phrase\": \"elementary school|小学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you remember the time you and I went to the zoo together when you and I were in elementary school?\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"elementary school|小学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"even though|即使\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"even though|虽然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"native speaker|母语者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卡住\", \"phrase\": \"stuck in a traffic jam|堵在交通拥堵中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"traffic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交通\", \"phrase\": \"traffic jam|交通堵塞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"jam\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交通堵塞\", \"phrase\": \"traffic jam|交通堵塞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"tree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"tree branches|树枝\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"washed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"冲走\", \"phrase\": \"washed away|被冲走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"washed away|冲走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"pretty mad|非常生气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"find out|发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"bought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"bought is|买是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"everything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一切\", \"phrase\": \"lost everything|失去一切\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"stock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"股票\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"market\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市场\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"crash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"崩溃\", \"phrase\": \"stock market crash|股市崩盘\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to return the swimsuit for a larger size, but the clerk told him that wasn't allowed.\", \"target\": \"size\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尺寸\", \"phrase\": \"larger size|更大的尺寸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to return the swimsuit for a larger size, but the clerk told him that wasn't allowed.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"told him|告诉他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to return the swimsuit for a larger size, but the clerk told him that wasn't allowed.\", \"target\": \"allowed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"wasn't allowed|不允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"closely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"密切地\", \"phrase\": \"closely related|密切相关\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"related\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"相关的\", \"phrase\": \"closely related|密切相关\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"opportunities\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"see opportunities in disasters|在灾难中看到机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"find disasters|发现灾难\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"disasters\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灾难\", \"phrase\": \"find disasters in every opportunity|在每个机会中发现灾难\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"every opportunity|每个机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"opportunity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"opportunity in disasters|灾难中的机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"given\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被给予\", \"phrase\": \"have been given|被给予\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"两个\", \"phrase\": \"two mouths|两个嘴巴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one ear|一个耳朵\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"ear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"耳朵\", \"phrase\": \"one ear|一个耳朵\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"find out|发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"bought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"bought the painting|买了这幅画\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"told you|告诉你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"repeatedly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"反复地\", \"phrase\": \"told you repeatedly|反复地告诉你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating something|吃东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For quantities of 20 or more, we can allow you a special discount of 10% on the prices quoted.\", \"target\": \"allow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"allow you|允许你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For quantities of 20 or more, we can allow you a special discount of 10% on the prices quoted.\", \"target\": \"special\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"特别的\", \"phrase\": \"special discount|特别折扣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For quantities of 20 or more, we can allow you a special discount of 10% on the prices quoted.\", \"target\": \"discount\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"折扣\", \"phrase\": \"special discount|特别折扣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For quantities of 20 or more, we can allow you a special discount of 10% on the prices quoted.\", \"target\": \"prices\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"价格\", \"phrase\": \"quoted prices|报价\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For quantities of 20 or more, we can allow you a special discount of 10% on the prices quoted.\", \"target\": \"quoted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"报价的\", \"phrase\": \"prices quoted|报价价格\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Abraham Lincoln, the 16th president of the United States, was born in a log cabin in Kentucky.\", \"target\": \"log\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"木头\", \"phrase\": \"log cabin|木屋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Abraham Lincoln, the 16th president of the United States, was born in a log cabin in Kentucky.\", \"target\": \"cabin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小屋\", \"phrase\": \"log cabin|木屋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"small clubs|小俱乐部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"clubs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"俱乐部\", \"phrase\": \"small clubs|小俱乐部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"small cities|小城市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would hire|会雇用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"hire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"雇用\", \"phrase\": \"hire us|雇用我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep a stiff upper lip|保持镇定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"stiff\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坚定的\", \"phrase\": \"stiff upper lip|顶住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"upper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"上面的\", \"phrase\": \"stiff upper lip|硬着头皮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"lip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"嘴唇\", \"phrase\": \"stiff upper lip|嘴唇上的坚强\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"quite a bit|相当多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"rainy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"多雨的\", \"phrase\": \"rainy season|雨季\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"mid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"中间的\", \"phrase\": \"mid-June|六月中旬\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"mid\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年中\", \"phrase\": \"mid-June|年中六月|mid-July|年中七月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"There's an apostrophe missing. It's and its are different.\\\" \\\"I know. It was a typing error.\\\"\", \"target\": \"typing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"打字\", \"phrase\": \"typing error|打字错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"There's an apostrophe missing. It's and its are different.\\\" \\\"I know. It was a typing error.\\\"\", \"target\": \"error\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"typing error|打字错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"first impressions|第一印象\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"low\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"低\", \"phrase\": \"prices are low|价格低廉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"location\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"位置\", \"phrase\": \"location isn't good|位置不太好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"isn't good|不好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"afraid of|害怕...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"always be lonely|总是孤独\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"lonely\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"孤独的\", \"phrase\": \"always be lonely|总是孤独\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第二的\", \"phrase\": \"second language|第二语言\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"foreign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"外国的\", \"phrase\": \"foreign language|外语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"foreign language|外语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of|在...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周\", \"phrase\": \"twentieth week|第二十周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"pregnancy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"怀孕\", \"phrase\": \"week of pregnancy|妊娠周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In theory, there is no difference between theory and practice. But, in practice, there is.\", \"target\": \"theory\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"理论\", \"phrase\": \"in theory|理论上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In theory, there is no difference between theory and practice. But, in practice, there is.\", \"target\": \"practice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"实践\", \"phrase\": \"in practice|在实践中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In theory, there is no difference between theory and practice. But, in practice, there is.\", \"target\": \"practice\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"实践\", \"phrase\": \"in practice|在实践中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which translation of this book do you think is better, the French one or the English one?\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better one|更好的一個\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which translation of this book do you think is better, the French one or the English one?\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the French one|法国的一个; the English one|英国的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which translation of this book do you think is better, the French one or the English one?\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the English one|英语的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"been waiting|等待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"wait a little bit longer|再等一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更长的时间\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit longer|再等一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"whether we like it or not|无论我们是否喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like it|喜欢它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"some day|某一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"replace\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取代\", \"phrase\": \"replace the automobile|取代汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will tell|将告诉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"tell us the truth|告诉我们真相\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"活的\", \"phrase\": \"live frog|活青蛙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更糟的\", \"phrase\": \"nothing worse|糟糕的事情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will happen|将会发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"剩余\", \"phrase\": \"the rest of the day|一整天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's mother is a nurse at the hospital that's across the street from where Mary lives.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"across the street|穿过街道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's mother is a nurse at the hospital that's across the street from where Mary lives.\", \"target\": \"street\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"街道\", \"phrase\": \"across the street|在街对面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"head\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"负责人\", \"phrase\": \"head of the company|公司负责人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"name\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名字\", \"phrase\": \"in name only|名义上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"important decisions|重要决定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"closely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"密切地\", \"phrase\": \"closely related|密切相关\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"related\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"相关的\", \"phrase\": \"closely related|密切相关\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At lunchtime today, our usual restaurant was closed because of a funeral in the family.\", \"target\": \"closed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关闭\", \"phrase\": \"was closed|已关闭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"lending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借\", \"phrase\": \"lending me|$500|借给我$500\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"difficulty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"困难\", \"phrase\": \"making ends meet|勉强度日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"making\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"making ends meet|维持生计\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"ends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尽头\", \"phrase\": \"making ends meet|维持生计\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"meet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"满足\", \"phrase\": \"making ends meet|维持生计\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"start your life|开始你的人生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"start your life|开始你的人生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Democracy is the worst form of government, except all the others that have been tried.\", \"target\": \"form\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"形式\", \"phrase\": \"form of government|政府形式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Democracy is the worst form of government, except all the others that have been tried.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except all|除了所有\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Democracy is the worst form of government, except all the others that have been tried.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试过\", \"phrase\": \"have been tried|已经被尝试过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回家\", \"phrase\": \"go back home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"go back home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"go back home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"much energy|很多精力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't we stop arguing over these piddling matters and get to the issues at hand?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"get to|着手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't we stop arguing over these piddling matters and get to the issues at hand?\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"at hand|手边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"remove\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱掉\", \"phrase\": \"remove their shoes|脱鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"edge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"competitive edge|竞争优势\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want something to be done right, sometimes you've just got to do it yourself.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"正确地\", \"phrase\": \"to be done right|正确地完成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want something to be done right, sometimes you've just got to do it yourself.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"got to|不得不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"wait a little bit longer|再等一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更长的时间\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit longer|再等一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came back not because he was homesick, but because he was running short of money.\", \"target\": \"running\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"running short|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came back not because he was homesick, but because he was running short of money.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"running short|资金短缺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"not good at|不擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"speaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speaking it|说它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"head\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头部\", \"phrase\": \"head hunting|人才搜寻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"hunting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"招聘\", \"phrase\": \"head hunting|人才搜寻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"合适的\", \"phrase\": \"right man|合适的人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just spoken to your French teacher and he says you're doing well in his class.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"doing well|做得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just spoken to your French teacher and he says you're doing well in his class.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his class|他的课\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just spoken to your French teacher and he says you're doing well in his class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"his class|他的班级\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His dress is that of a gentleman, but his speech and behavior are those of a clown.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his speech|他的演讲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to take an examination without preparing for it.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"take an examination|参加考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to take an examination without preparing for it.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without preparing|没有准备\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Manholes are round because that way they won't accidentally fall through the hole.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"掉落\", \"phrase\": \"fall through|掉进\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Being a good conversationalist does not just mean being a good speaker of English.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good conversationalist|好的谈话者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Being a good conversationalist does not just mean being a good speaker of English.\", \"target\": \"mean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"意思是\", \"phrase\": \"does not mean|不意味着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Being a good conversationalist does not just mean being a good speaker of English.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good speaker|好说话者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"got out|出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his clothes|他的衣服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"偷走\", \"phrase\": \"had been stolen|被偷走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To the man who only has a hammer in the toolkit, every problem looks like a nail.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like a nail|看起来像钉子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"knife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"刀\", \"phrase\": \"kitchen knife|厨房刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"sharp\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"锋利的\", \"phrase\": \"sharp enough|足够锋利\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"切\", \"phrase\": \"cut the meat|切肉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"used my pocket knife|使用了我的小刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"pocket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"口袋的\", \"phrase\": \"pocket knife|袖刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"knife\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"刀\", \"phrase\": \"pocket knife|小刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"加起来\", \"phrase\": \"put together|加起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"put together|放在一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know the city, and what's more, I couldn't speak a word of the language.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speak a word|说一句话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know the city, and what's more, I couldn't speak a word of the language.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词\", \"phrase\": \"a word|一个词\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every now and then he drops in at this bookstore on his way home from the office.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on his way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good at|擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"speaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"good at speaking it|擅长说它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"permitted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被允许\", \"phrase\": \"be permitted to|被允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next weekend|下个周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"low\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"低的\", \"phrase\": \"low voice|低声\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"barely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎不\", \"phrase\": \"barely understand|几乎不明白\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"get his son|让他的儿子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his son|他的儿子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"someone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某人\", \"phrase\": \"someone else|别人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"别人\", \"phrase\": \"someone else|另一个人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"paint\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"油漆\", \"phrase\": \"paint the house|粉刷房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the time there were no native English speakers teaching in any public school.\", \"target\": \"public\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"公立的\", \"phrase\": \"public school|公立学校\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy happiness|买幸福\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go shopping|购物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"shopping\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"购物\", \"phrase\": \"go shopping|去购物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They say you shouldn't take rumors seriously, but that's easier said than done.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"easier said than done|易如反掌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"hold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"hold on|等候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建立\", \"phrase\": \"was made|被建立\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Publication of the article was timed to coincide with the professor's birthday.\", \"target\": \"timed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"安排时间\", \"phrase\": \"timed to coincide|安排时间与...同时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Publication of the article was timed to coincide with the professor's birthday.\", \"target\": \"coincide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"巧合\", \"phrase\": \"timed to coincide with|与...同时发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a native French speaker and my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"native English speaker|本地英语母语者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a native French speaker and my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"speaker\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话者\", \"phrase\": \"English speaker|英语母语者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"borrowed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借\", \"phrase\": \"borrowed from the library|从图书馆借\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"borrowed\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借\", \"phrase\": \"borrowed some new ones|借了一些新的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new ones|新的书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"ones\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"那些\", \"phrase\": \"new ones|新的那些\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a lot of work, but it's enough to keep me in the office this week.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep me|让我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"even though|即使\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"even though|虽然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"very much|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Charles Lindbergh made the first solo flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"across the Atlantic Ocean|穿过大西洋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did the best he could, but he wasn't able to get a higher grade than Mary.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"the best|最好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did the best he could, but he wasn't able to get a higher grade than Mary.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"able to|能够\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did the best he could, but he wasn't able to get a higher grade than Mary.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get a grade|获得分数\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like a native speaker|像一个母语者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"native speaker|母语者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"among\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之中\", \"phrase\": \"among teenagers|在青少年中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"大约\", \"phrase\": \"around 12 o'clock|大约12点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like a book|像一本书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"like a book|像一本书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"every step|每一步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"step\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"步骤\", \"phrase\": \"every step|每一步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"采取\", \"phrase\": \"take a step|采取一步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like turning a page|像翻一页\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"turning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻转\", \"phrase\": \"turning a page|翻页\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"page\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"页\", \"phrase\": \"turning a page|翻页\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"an apple|苹果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"tastes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝起来\", \"phrase\": \"tastes like|尝起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"tastes like|尝起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"like an apple|像一个苹果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 3}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"an apple|苹果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since this morning|自从今天早上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"caught\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感冒\", \"phrase\": \"caught a cold|感冒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"bad at|不擅长\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"speech\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"演讲\", \"phrase\": \"speech making|演讲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"making\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"speech making|演讲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"found us|找到我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"found us|发现我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eighty percent of all information on computers around the world is in English.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the world|世界各地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom came to the conclusion that no matter what he did, Mary wouldn't like it.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"no matter what|无论如何\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom came to the conclusion that no matter what he did, Mary wouldn't like it.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"wouldn't like|不喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom came to the conclusion that no matter what he did, Mary wouldn't like it.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"wouldn't like it|不喜欢它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They consider it impolite to disagree with someone they don't know very well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"very well|很好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参与\", \"phrase\": \"taking part|参与\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around her waist|在她的腰围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"took ... out|取出...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around her waist|在她的腰围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"took ... out|取出...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"ruins\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"废墟\", \"phrase\": \"in ruins|一片废墟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"according\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"according to|根据\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"according\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"according to|根据\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to your father for not getting home in time for dinner.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"in time|准时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You said Mary was beautiful, but I didn't think she would be this beautiful.\", \"target\": \"beautiful\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美丽的\", \"phrase\": \"this beautiful|这个美丽的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赚\", \"phrase\": \"make money|赚钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of money|很多钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"stock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"股票\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"market\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市场\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The statue of Hachiko, the faithful dog, stands in front of Shibuya Station.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The statue of Hachiko, the faithful dog, stands in front of Shibuya Station.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"Shibuya Station|涩谷站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"strictly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"严格\", \"phrase\": \"strictly prohibited|严格禁止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起作用\", \"phrase\": \"going to work|起作用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"that day|那一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"postponed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推迟\", \"phrase\": \"will be postponed|将被推迟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next fine day|下一个好天气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"fine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晴朗的\", \"phrase\": \"fine day|晴朗的日子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"fine day|晴天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"died\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死了\", \"phrase\": \"all but 9 died|除了9只以外都死了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"sheep\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"羊\", \"phrase\": \"11 sheep|11只羊\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"剩下\", \"phrase\": \"would have left|剩下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last evening|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We apologize for the delay and regret any inconvenience it may have caused.\", \"target\": \"caused\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"have caused|造成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"permitted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被允许\", \"phrase\": \"be permitted to|被允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next weekend|下个周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"permitted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被允许\", \"phrase\": \"be permitted to|被允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next weekend|下个周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave Mary a box of chocolates, and then ate all the chocolates himself.\", \"target\": \"chocolates\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"巧克力\", \"phrase\": \"box of chocolates|巧克力盒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave Mary a box of chocolates, and then ate all the chocolates himself.\", \"target\": \"ate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"ate all|吃光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave Mary a box of chocolates, and then ate all the chocolates himself.\", \"target\": \"chocolates\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"巧克力\", \"phrase\": \"box of chocolates|巧克力盒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"flipped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发狂\", \"phrase\": \"flipped out|发狂\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"flipped out|发火\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The good thing about this electronic dictionary is that it's easy to carry.\", \"target\": \"carry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"携带\", \"phrase\": \"carry it|携带它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"anger\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"激怒\", \"phrase\": \"calculated to anger|计算激怒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"boxes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盒子\", \"phrase\": \"cardboard boxes|纸箱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had been a little more careful, the accident would have been avoided.\", \"target\": \"avoided\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"避免\", \"phrase\": \"would have been avoided|本可以避免\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"provided\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"以...为条件\", \"phrase\": \"provided you|以你为条件\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"还款\", \"phrase\": \"pay it back|还款\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"pay it back|还回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"within\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之内\", \"phrase\": \"within a month|一个月之内\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"前台\", \"phrase\": \"front desk|前台\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good position|好职位\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"take into account|考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"account\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"take into account|考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"planning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"planning a trip|计划一次旅行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his parents|他的父母\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"假期\", \"phrase\": \"summer break|暑假\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"floor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"楼层\", \"phrase\": \"second floor|二楼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"conference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议室\", \"phrase\": \"conference room|会议室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"conference room|会议室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe that Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"in love with|相爱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"willing to help|愿意帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"set\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"set in|开始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You seem to be prejudiced against ideas that come from foreign countries.\", \"target\": \"foreign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"外国的\", \"phrase\": \"foreign countries|外国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"make matters worse|使情况更糟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"annoying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"烦扰\", \"phrase\": \"annoying his neighbors|烦扰他的邻居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his neighbors|他的邻居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"neighbors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邻居\", \"phrase\": \"annoying his neighbors|烦扰他的邻居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visits the dentist on a regular basis, so she seldom gets toothaches.\", \"target\": \"regular\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"规律的\", \"phrase\": \"regular basis|定期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the only one|唯一的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"express\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"快递\", \"phrase\": \"American Express|美国运通\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"found us|找到我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"found us|发现我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶员\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾驶执照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶员\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾驶执照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beer is taxed according to its malt content, so low-malt beer is cheaper.\", \"target\": \"content\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"含量\", \"phrase\": \"malt content|麦芽含量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beer is taxed according to its malt content, so low-malt beer is cheaper.\", \"target\": \"low\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"低\", \"phrase\": \"low-malt|低麦芽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beer is taxed according to its malt content, so low-malt beer is cheaper.\", \"target\": \"beer\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"啤酒\", \"phrase\": \"low-malt beer|低麦芽啤酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"cope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"应对\", \"phrase\": \"cope with|应对\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his job|他的工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't share too much private information on the social networks.\", \"target\": \"networks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"网络\", \"phrase\": \"social networks|社交网络\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"flowers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"give flowers|送花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"wedding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婚礼\", \"phrase\": \"wedding anniversary|结婚周年纪念日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't account for his whereabouts on the day that Mary was murdered.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"the day|当天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"turned out|结果是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"listed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"上市的\", \"phrase\": \"listed on the stock exchange|在证券交易所上市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"stock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"股票\", \"phrase\": \"stock exchange|证券交易所\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"exchange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交易所\", \"phrase\": \"stock exchange|证券交易所\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"years of age|年龄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want to go, then go. If you don't want to, then it's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to go|想要去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want to go, then go. If you don't want to, then it's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"want to go|想去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want to go, then go. If you don't want to, then it's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"don't want to|不想\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want to go, then go. If you don't want to, then it's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"no big deal|没关系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want to go, then go. If you don't want to, then it's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"no big deal|小事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would have made|将会完成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"made it|到达\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"onto\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"到\", \"phrase\": \"made it onto|成功登上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we knew what we were doing, it wouldn't be called research, would it?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would it|会吗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we knew what we were doing, it wouldn't be called research, would it?\", \"target\": \"called\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫做\", \"phrase\": \"be called|被叫做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we knew what we were doing, it wouldn't be called research, would it?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would it|会吗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wanted he|想要他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car when I was eighteen and got a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾驶执照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car and got a driver's license when I was eighteen.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"palms of my hands|手掌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without bending|不弯曲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"said you|你说的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"lost the umbrella|丢失雨伞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"the other day|前几天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As I missed the train, I had to wait for the next one for about an hour.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"wait for|等候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As I missed the train, I had to wait for the next one for about an hour.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next one|下一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As I missed the train, I had to wait for the next one for about an hour.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"next one|下一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Where have you been?\\\" \\\"I have been to the station to see a friend off.\\\"\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"to the station|去车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Where have you been?\\\" \\\"I have been to the station to see a friend off.\\\"\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see off|送别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Where have you been?\\\" \\\"I have been to the station to see a friend off.\\\"\", \"target\": \"friend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"see a friend off|送朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"the light|光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"ran\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"耗尽\", \"phrase\": \"ran short|耗尽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"look for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new place|新地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"place to live|居住地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赚\", \"phrase\": \"make money|赚钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of money|很多钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"stock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"股票\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"market\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市场\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"enough money|足够的钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"快乐的\", \"phrase\": \"Happy Birthday|生日快乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"birthday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生日\", \"phrase\": \"Happy Birthday|生日快乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"entire restaurant|整个餐厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"joined\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"加入\", \"phrase\": \"joined in|一起加入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People show up bright on an infrared camera because of their body heat.\", \"target\": \"body\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"身体\", \"phrase\": \"body heat|体温\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People show up bright on an infrared camera because of their body heat.\", \"target\": \"heat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"热量\", \"phrase\": \"body heat|体温\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father was no less affectionate and tender to me than my mother was.\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不如\", \"phrase\": \"no less...than|不如...比\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father was no less affectionate and tender to me than my mother was.\", \"target\": \"tender\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"温柔的\", \"phrase\": \"affectionate and tender|体贴而温柔的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"can see|能看见\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you enjoy the work you do, you have something worth more than money.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"worth more|更有价值\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参加\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参与\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next meeting|下次会议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary probably won't want to do that anymore.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"won't|不会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary probably won't want to do that anymore.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to do|想要做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary probably won't want to do that anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"won't want to do that anymore|再也不想做那件事了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary knows that she doesn't have to do that.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"Tom knows|汤姆知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does any other country fan the flames of patriotism as much as America?\", \"target\": \"fan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"煽动\", \"phrase\": \"fan the flames|煽动火焰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does any other country fan the flames of patriotism as much as America?\", \"target\": \"flames\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火焰\", \"phrase\": \"fan the flames|煽动火焰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does any other country fan the flames of patriotism as much as America?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"那么\", \"phrase\": \"as much as|和...一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As is evident from the data, smoking is not decreasing among the young.\", \"target\": \"among\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之中\", \"phrase\": \"among the young|在年轻人中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's this song? I've heard it before, but I can't remember the name.\", \"target\": \"heard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听过\", \"phrase\": \"heard it|听过它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's this song? I've heard it before, but I can't remember the name.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"can't remember|记不住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"instead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"代替\", \"phrase\": \"instead of|代替...而不是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"with his children|和他孩子们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"permitted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被允许\", \"phrase\": \"be permitted to|被允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next weekend|下个周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a sprinkling of foreigners among the visitors in the museum.\", \"target\": \"among\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之中\", \"phrase\": \"among the visitors|在参观者之中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She recognized the brooch as the one she had lost a few months before.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the one|那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She recognized the brooch as the one she had lost a few months before.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"had lost|丢失\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She recognized the brooch as the one she had lost a few months before.\", \"target\": \"months\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"几个月\", \"phrase\": \"a few months|几个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"活\", \"phrase\": \"live one day as a tiger|活一天像老虎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Laser printers are generally cheaper to maintain than inkjet printers.\", \"target\": \"printers\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"打印机\", \"phrase\": \"inkjet printers|喷墨打印机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to tell Englishmen from Americans just by the way they look.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"the way|方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to tell Englishmen from Americans just by the way they look.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"look at|看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"would have|将会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 3}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"would have never|将不会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"never consented|从未同意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one|一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"简短的\", \"phrase\": \"short-cut|快捷方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"快捷方式\", \"phrase\": \"short-cut|快捷方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I understood everything Tom said, but I'm not absolutely sure.\", \"target\": \"absolutely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"绝对地\", \"phrase\": \"absolutely sure|绝对确定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Having missed the train, I had to wait about an hour for the next one.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"wait about an hour|等待大约一个小时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Having missed the train, I had to wait about an hour for the next one.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next one|下一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Having missed the train, I had to wait about an hour for the next one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the next one|下一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry! Even if I drink, it doesn't have an effect on my driving.\", \"target\": \"effect\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"影响\", \"phrase\": \"have an effect on|对...产生影响\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you describe to me the difference between black tea and green tea?\", \"target\": \"difference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区别\", \"phrase\": \"the difference|区别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you describe to me the difference between black tea and green tea?\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"green tea|绿茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've received a lot of applications in answer to our advertisements.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"in time|及时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"catch the train|抓住火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wanted to catch|想要抓住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"catch the train|抓住火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is nothing worse than doing something in a half-hearted manner.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"半心的\", \"phrase\": \"half-hearted manner|半心半意的态度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The taller the tree, the more likely it is to be struck by lightning.\", \"target\": \"likely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能地\", \"phrase\": \"more likely|更可能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The taller the tree, the more likely it is to be struck by lightning.\", \"target\": \"struck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被击中\", \"phrase\": \"be struck by|被...击中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took full advantage of her stay in London to improve her English.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"充分的\", \"phrase\": \"full advantage|充分利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took full advantage of her stay in London to improve her English.\", \"target\": \"advantage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"full advantage|充分利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took full advantage of her stay in London to improve her English.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"逗留\", \"phrase\": \"full advantage of her stay|充分利用她的逗留\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a good command of English though she was brought up in Japan.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good command|良好掌握\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a good command of English though she was brought up in Japan.\", \"target\": \"command\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"掌握\", \"phrase\": \"command of English|英语掌握\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a good command of English though she was brought up in Japan.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"though she was|虽然她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a good command of English though she was brought up in Japan.\", \"target\": \"brought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抚养\", \"phrase\": \"brought up|长大\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old building|旧建筑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"torn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"past participle\", \"zh\": \"拆毁\", \"phrase\": \"torn down|拆毁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"in love with|相爱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's clear that there's a rather strong disagreement between the two.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强烈的\", \"phrase\": \"rather strong disagreement|相当强烈的分歧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"fish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鱼\", \"phrase\": \"teach someone how to fish|教人钓鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give someone a fish|给某人一条鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"fish\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鱼\", \"phrase\": \"give someone a fish|给某人一条鱼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a few minutes we'll be landing at New Tokyo International Airport.\", \"target\": \"international\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"国际的\", \"phrase\": \"New Tokyo International Airport|东京国际机场\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"部分的\", \"phrase\": \"part time|兼职\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"part time|兼职\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"days\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"three days a week|一周三天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"three days a week|一周三天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't think of any other way of getting him to accept our proposal.\", \"target\": \"accept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"accept our proposal|接受我们的提议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I agree on an emotional level, but on the pragmatic level I disagree.\", \"target\": \"level\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"层面\", \"phrase\": \"emotional level|情感层面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I agree on an emotional level, but on the pragmatic level I disagree.\", \"target\": \"level\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"层面\", \"phrase\": \"pragmatic level|实用层面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His intelligence and experience enabled him to deal with the trouble.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"处理\", \"phrase\": \"deal with|处理\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I were inseparable friends during our time together in school.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"time together|一起的时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I were inseparable friends during our time together in school.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"together in school|在学校一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"剩余的人\", \"phrase\": \"the rest|剩余的人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Do you know when they will arrive?\\\" \\\"At eleven-thirty this evening.\\\"\", \"target\": \"evening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚上\", \"phrase\": \"this evening|今晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary not to waste her time trying to convince John to help.\", \"target\": \"waste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary not to waste her time trying to convince John to help.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary not to waste her time trying to convince John to help.\", \"target\": \"trying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图\", \"phrase\": \"waste time trying|浪费时间试图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary not to waste her time trying to convince John to help.\", \"target\": \"convince\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说服\", \"phrase\": \"convince John to help|说服约翰帮忙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary not to waste her time trying to convince John to help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help John|帮助约翰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked me to tell you he didn't plan on going to Boston with you.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"plan on going|计划去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The death penalty had been done away with in many states in the USA.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"done away with|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our task has been easy so far, but it will be difficult from now on.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"到目前为止\", \"phrase\": \"so far|到目前为止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"small island|小岛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"small settlements|小定居点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in the habit of reading the newspaper before breakfast.\", \"target\": \"reading\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阅读\", \"phrase\": \"reading the newspaper|阅读报纸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the light of what you told us, I think we should revise our plan.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"in the light of|在...的光芒下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Liszt's \\\"Forgotten Waltz No.3\\\" is a hidden masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"forgotten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"被遗忘的\", \"phrase\": \"Forgotten Waltz|被遗忘的华尔兹\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Liszt's \\\"Forgotten Waltz No.3\\\" is a hidden masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"hidden\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"隐藏的\", \"phrase\": \"hidden masterpiece|隐藏的杰作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom would be a good basketball coach. That's why I hired him.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good basketball coach|好的篮球教练\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father makes sure that all the lights are off before he goes to bed.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"确保\", \"phrase\": \"makes sure|确保\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the guidebook, this is the best restaurant around here.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|这里附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to Dad for not coming home in time for supper.\", \"target\": \"coming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"coming home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This problem is too difficult for primary school children to solve.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"primary school|小学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a secret just between you and me, so don't let it slip out.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let it slip|泄露\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a secret just between you and me, so don't let it slip out.\", \"target\": \"slip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"泄露\", \"phrase\": \"slip out|泄露出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a secret just between you and me, so don't let it slip out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"slip out|泄露\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the painting was estimated at several million dollars.\", \"target\": \"million\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百万\", \"phrase\": \"several million dollars|数百万美元\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher pointed her finger at me and asked me to come with her.\", \"target\": \"pointed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"指着\", \"phrase\": \"pointed her finger at|指着她的手指\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't forget to put a stamp on the letter before mailing it.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put a stamp on|盖邮票在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go outside|外出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"外面\", \"phrase\": \"go outside|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you heard her speak English, you would take her for an American.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"take her for|把她当做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a child, but sometimes you talk to me as if I were a child.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"talk to|和...说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a child, but sometimes you talk to me as if I were a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"as if I were a child|好像我是个孩子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one sort|一种类型\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"sort\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"sort of|种类\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"sort or another|各种各样的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his life|他的一生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his wife|他的妻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"store\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"商店\", \"phrase\": \"department store|百货商店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"sale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"促销\", \"phrase\": \"department store sale|部门商店促销\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone is anxious to know what has become of the former champion.\", \"target\": \"former\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"前任的\", \"phrase\": \"former champion|前任冠军\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of his wealth, he was able to become a member of that club.\", \"target\": \"member\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"成员\", \"phrase\": \"member of that club|俱乐部成员\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A year has passed, but it's as if we saw each other only yesterday.\", \"target\": \"yesterday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"昨天\", \"phrase\": \"only yesterday|昨天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old saying|老话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"may or may not|可能或不可能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We found it very hard going back to our base camp in the blizzard.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"going back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We found it very hard going back to our base camp in the blizzard.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"going back|回去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We found it very hard going back to our base camp in the blizzard.\", \"target\": \"camp\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"营地\", \"phrase\": \"base camp|基地营地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was admiring my new car at the time the truck crashed into it.\", \"target\": \"crashed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撞击\", \"phrase\": \"crashed into|撞入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted Mary's phone number, but she refused to give it to him.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give it|给它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put the large picnic basket on the passenger seat next to him.\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"picnic basket|野餐篮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put the large picnic basket on the passenger seat next to him.\", \"target\": \"seat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"座位\", \"phrase\": \"passenger seat|乘客座位\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put the large picnic basket on the passenger seat next to him.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...旁边\", \"phrase\": \"next to him|在他旁边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"given\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"given rise to|导致...发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"rise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"上升\", \"phrase\": \"given rise to|导致\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of problems|很多问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"given\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"given rise to|导致...发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"rise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"上升\", \"phrase\": \"given rise to|导致\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of problems|很多问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The average height of girls in this class is over 155 centimeters.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"this class|这个班级\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how often I tell her, she keeps making the same mistake.\", \"target\": \"making\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯\", \"phrase\": \"making the same mistake|犯同样的错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife often telephones me when I'm traveling in another country.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another country|另一个国家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always said that heaven helps those who help themselves.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help themselves|自救\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"twenty-year-old|二十岁的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"twenty-year-old|二十岁的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"quite another|完全不同的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"quite another|完全不同的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"carry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"执行\", \"phrase\": \"carry out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"执行\", \"phrase\": \"carry out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"quite another|完全不同的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"quite another|完全不同的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"carry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"执行\", \"phrase\": \"carry out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"执行\", \"phrase\": \"carry out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't have anything nice to say, don't say anything at all.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"say anything|说些什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't have anything nice to say, don't say anything at all.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"say anything|说什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't have anything nice to say, don't say anything at all.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何东西\", \"phrase\": \"anything at all|任何事情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If the lion is the king of beasts, the eagle is the king of birds.\", \"target\": \"king\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国王\", \"phrase\": \"king of birds|鸟类之王\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注意\", \"phrase\": \"watch out|小心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注意\", \"phrase\": \"watch out|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注意\", \"phrase\": \"watch out|小心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注意\", \"phrase\": \"watch out|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was an excellent scientist, and what is more, was a great poet.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"伟大的\", \"phrase\": \"great poet|伟大的诗人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems not to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"conflict\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冲突\", \"phrase\": \"conflict between my father and me|我和我父亲之间的冲突\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"first language|第一语言\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the typhoon, my parents ended their trip one day early.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one day|一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the typhoon, my parents ended their trip one day early.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"one day|一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the typhoon, my parents ended their trip one day early.\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"早\", \"phrase\": \"one day early|提前一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When she was in Los Angeles, she had at least six different jobs.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least|至少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What Tom really wanted was enough money to buy Mary some flowers.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy Mary some flowers|给玛丽买些花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"tickets\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"票\", \"phrase\": \"children's tickets|儿童票\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows where we can get something to eat around here.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get something to eat|吃点东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows where we can get something to eat around here.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"get something to eat|吃东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows where we can get something to eat around here.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|这里附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to tell Mary what time the meeting was going to start.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"what time|什么时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to tell Mary what time the meeting was going to start.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进行\", \"phrase\": \"going to start|即将开始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to tell Mary what time the meeting was going to start.\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"start the meeting|开始会议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This will be a good souvenir of my trip around the United States.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the United States|在美国周围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This will be a good souvenir of my trip around the United States.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was so crowded that I had to keep standing all the way.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep standing|站着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was so crowded that I had to keep standing all the way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"all the way|一路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The leaves of the trees in the garden have turned completely red.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"turned red|变红\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby caught sight of my ballpoint pen and reached out for it.\", \"target\": \"reached\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伸出\", \"phrase\": \"reached out|伸出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby caught sight of my ballpoint pen and reached out for it.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"向外\", \"phrase\": \"reached out|伸出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"gray\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"灰色\", \"phrase\": \"gray building|灰色建筑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"six-story building|六层楼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"story\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"层\", \"phrase\": \"six-story building|六层楼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"spend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"spend it|花钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is out of the question for you to go to New York this weekend.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of the question|不可行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is out of the question for you to go to New York this weekend.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to|去...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case the shipment is delayed, we have special delay insurance.\", \"target\": \"case\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...的情况下\", \"phrase\": \"in case|以防\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case the shipment is delayed, we have special delay insurance.\", \"target\": \"delayed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"延迟的\", \"phrase\": \"shipment is delayed|货物延迟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case the shipment is delayed, we have special delay insurance.\", \"target\": \"special\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"特别的\", \"phrase\": \"special delay insurance|特别延误保险\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case the shipment is delayed, we have special delay insurance.\", \"target\": \"delay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"延迟\", \"phrase\": \"delay insurance|延迟保险\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"get out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Canada, there are many areas where it is illegal to log trees.\", \"target\": \"log\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"砍伐\", \"phrase\": \"log trees|砍伐树木\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下次\", \"phrase\": \"next time|下次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"New York|纽约\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you for ages. Do you remember when I saw you last?\", \"target\": \"ages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很久\", \"phrase\": \"for ages|很久了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you for ages. Do you remember when I saw you last?\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"remember when|记得什么时候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you for ages. Do you remember when I saw you last?\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"saw you|看见你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you for ages. Do you remember when I saw you last?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上次\", \"phrase\": \"saw you last|上次见到你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I crossed the equator for the first time on my trip to Australia.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His name was on the tip of my tongue, but I couldn't remember it.\", \"target\": \"tip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顶端\", \"phrase\": \"tip of my tongue|舌尖上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His name was on the tip of my tongue, but I couldn't remember it.\", \"target\": \"tongue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"舌头\", \"phrase\": \"tip of my tongue|舌尖上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you spare me a few minutes? I'd like to have a word with you.\", \"target\": \"spare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"腾出; 抽出\", \"phrase\": \"spare me a few minutes|腾我几分钟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you spare me a few minutes? I'd like to have a word with you.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"have a word|谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As a matter of fact, I haven't eaten anything since this morning.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since this morning|自从早上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A considerable amount of time and effort have been spent already.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"amount of time|时间量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A considerable amount of time and effort have been spent already.\", \"target\": \"spent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"spent time|时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A considerable amount of time and effort have been spent already.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"spent already|已经花费\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you be at my party tomorrow night?\\\" \\\"I'll try to be there.\\\"\", \"target\": \"party\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"派对\", \"phrase\": \"at my party|在我的派对\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you be at my party tomorrow night?\\\" \\\"I'll try to be there.\\\"\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚上\", \"phrase\": \"tomorrow night|明天晚上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"We haven't seen each other since 2009.\\\" \\\"Has it been that long?\\\"\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since 2009|自2009年以来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"We haven't seen each other since 2009.\\\" \\\"Has it been that long?\\\"\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"that long|这么久\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Dad finds out what you've done, he's going to hit the roof.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发怒\", \"phrase\": \"hit the roof|大发雷霆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Dad finds out what you've done, he's going to hit the roof.\", \"target\": \"roof\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"屋顶\", \"phrase\": \"hit the roof|大发雷霆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were faced with an unusual situation because of the accident.\", \"target\": \"faced\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"面对\", \"phrase\": \"faced with|面对...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"腾出\", \"phrase\": \"make room|腾出空间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"make room|腾出空间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told us this morning that he and Mary were moving to Boston.\", \"target\": \"moving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"搬家\", \"phrase\": \"were moving to|正在搬到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary that she should stop pretending to be intoxicated.\", \"target\": \"pretending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"pretending to be|假装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary that she should quit pretending to be intoxicated.\", \"target\": \"pretending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"pretending to be|假装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he isn't sure if he can do that, but he says he'll try.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"says he'll|他说他将\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he isn't sure if he can do that, but he says he'll try.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will try|将尝试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play tennis|打网球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't want Mary to know that he didn't know how to do that.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"didn't know|不知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the coins depended on the weight of the metal used.\", \"target\": \"weight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"重量\", \"phrase\": \"weight of the metal|金属的重量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the coins depended on the weight of the metal used.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"depended on the weight of the metal used|依赖于使用的金属重量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The accident seemed to have something to do with the heavy snow.\", \"target\": \"heavy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重的\", \"phrase\": \"heavy snow|大雪\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wouldn't let up until I agreed to go to the movies with her.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the movies|去电影院\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She employed a private detective to keep a watch on her husband.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep a watch on|监视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She employed a private detective to keep a watch on her husband.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"监视\", \"phrase\": \"keep a watch on|监视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next time|下次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the post office|去邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"post\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邮局\", \"phrase\": \"post office|邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"post office|邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody noticed that she was absent until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the meeting|会议结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how hard I try, I can't do it any better than she can.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"no better than|不比...好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It hasn't been easy for Tom to deal with Mary's health problems.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"处理\", \"phrase\": \"deal with|处理\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy the car|买车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to buy|想要买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know that Tom talked about me like that behind my back.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"talked about like that|像那样说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know that Tom talked about me like that behind my back.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind my back|背后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know that Tom talked about me like that behind my back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"背后\", \"phrase\": \"behind my back|背后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can still remember the time when we went on a picnic together.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"went on a picnic|去野餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can still remember the time when we went on a picnic together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"went on a picnic together|一起去野餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"陷入\", \"phrase\": \"got into trouble|陷入困境\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his boss|他的老板\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a very romantic boyfriend who brings me flowers each night.\", \"target\": \"brings\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带来\", \"phrase\": \"brings me flowers|给我带来鲜花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a very romantic boyfriend who brings me flowers each night.\", \"target\": \"flowers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"brings me flowers|给我带来花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you ever seen Mt. Fuji? It is beautiful beyond description.\", \"target\": \"beyond\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"超越\", \"phrase\": \"beyond description|难以形容\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, I'm studying French at this language school.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"for the time being|目前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, I'm studying French at this language school.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"language school|语言学校\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the difference between a microscope and a telescope?\", \"target\": \"difference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区别\", \"phrase\": \"the difference|区别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"find out|发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know exactly what it was that Mary wanted him to do.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wanted him to do|想要他做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To have doubts about oneself is the first sign of intelligence.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"first sign|最初迹象\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This year's fashions are completely different from last year's.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"去年的\", \"phrase\": \"last year's|去年的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This year's fashions are completely different from last year's.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"last year|去年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are three empty rooms. However, we can't use any of them.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't use|不能用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The warrior is conscious of both his strength and his weakness.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his strength|他的力量; his weakness|他的弱点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The warrior is conscious of both his strength and his weakness.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his weakness|他的弱点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The third quarter GNP growth was 1% over the preceding quarter.\", \"target\": \"quarter\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"季度\", \"phrase\": \"preceding quarter|上一季度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The senator was censured by the congressional ethics committee.\", \"target\": \"congressional\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"国会的\", \"phrase\": \"congressional ethics committee|国会伦理委员会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"within\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之内\", \"phrase\": \"within five minutes' walk|五分钟步行之内\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"five minutes' walk|五分钟路程\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"步行\", \"phrase\": \"five minutes' walk|五分钟步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police think the burglar entered through a basement window.\", \"target\": \"window\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"窗户\", \"phrase\": \"basement window|地下室窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Six people applied for the job, but none of them were employed.\", \"target\": \"none\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"none of them|他们中的任何一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"cover\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"覆盖\", \"phrase\": \"cover all the expenses|覆盖所有费用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"formed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"形成\", \"phrase\": \"formed a habit|形成习惯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"eyes wide open|睁大眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"wide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"睁大的\", \"phrase\": \"wide open|睁开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睁开\", \"phrase\": \"wide open|睁大\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一半\", \"phrase\": \"half shut|半闭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"shut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关闭\", \"phrase\": \"half shut|半闭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"pay off|还清\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"every month|每个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me ten thousand yen to have my television set repaired.\", \"target\": \"thousand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"千\", \"phrase\": \"ten thousand|一万\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Immediately after it caught fire, the chemical factory blew up.\", \"target\": \"blew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆炸\", \"phrase\": \"blew up|爆炸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If Tom doesn't do what he's supposed to do, please let me know.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"应该的\", \"phrase\": \"supposed to do|应该做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If Tom doesn't do what he's supposed to do, please let me know.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let me know|告诉我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no objection to paying a special fee if it is necessary.\", \"target\": \"special\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"特别的\", \"phrase\": \"special fee|特别费用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that I looked pale and asked me what the matter was.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"asked me what|问我什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"found out|发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"found out|发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He crept out of the room very carefully to avoid waking her up.\", \"target\": \"carefully\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"小心地\", \"phrase\": \"very carefully|非常小心地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He crept out of the room very carefully to avoid waking her up.\", \"target\": \"avoid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"避免\", \"phrase\": \"avoid waking her up|避免唤醒她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He crept out of the room very carefully to avoid waking her up.\", \"target\": \"waking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫醒\", \"phrase\": \"waking her up|叫醒她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"work out|想办法\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"work out|想办法\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"转弯\", \"phrase\": \"turn right|向右转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向右\", \"phrase\": \"turn right|向右转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"third\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal number\", \"zh\": \"第三\", \"phrase\": \"third light|第三个红绿灯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"third light|第三盏灯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, my sister is an assistant in a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"for the time being|目前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is a universal language and is used all over the world.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"is used|被使用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As time went on, rules were added to the game to make it safer.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"make it safer|使它更安全\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she heard the bell ring, she answered the telephone.\", \"target\": \"ring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"响铃\", \"phrase\": \"bell ring|铃响\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You told her that you had finished the work three days before.\", \"target\": \"days\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"three days|三天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't say that kind of thing when children are around.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"around children|在孩子们周围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must get this homework finished by the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"day after tomorrow|后天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may injure yourself if you don't follow safety procedures.\", \"target\": \"follow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遵循\", \"phrase\": \"follow safety procedures|遵循安全规程\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have less than five minutes to evacuate the whole building.\", \"target\": \"whole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"whole building|整个建筑物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"wearing his seat belt|系着安全带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"seat belt|安全带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"seat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"安全带\", \"phrase\": \"seat belt|安全带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"belt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"安全带\", \"phrase\": \"seat belt|安全带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably doesn't know how to do that as well as Mary does.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"as well as|以及\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like it when people cuss in front of his children.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like it when people cuss in front of his children.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his children|他的孩子们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked Mary some questions, but she refused to answer them.\", \"target\": \"answer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回答\", \"phrase\": \"answer them|回答它们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"彼此\", \"phrase\": \"one another|彼此\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"make a success|使成功\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"festival\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节日\", \"phrase\": \"school festival|学校节日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kidnapper told me he'd kill Tom if I didn't show up alone.\", \"target\": \"show\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出现\", \"phrase\": \"show up|露面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kidnapper told me he'd kill Tom if I didn't show up alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"show up alone|独自出现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"围绕\", \"phrase\": \"around the clock|昼夜不停\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"clock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时钟\", \"phrase\": \"around the clock|昼夜不停\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the bluest water in the world is found in Crater Lake.\", \"target\": \"lake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"湖\", \"phrase\": \"Crater Lake|克雷特湖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She doesn't have any friends or relatives to take care of her.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She doesn't have any friends or relatives to take care of her.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother has a driver's license, but she doesn't drive a car.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother has a driver's license, but she doesn't drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive a car|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me stop you right there. We don't want to hear about that.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立刻\", \"phrase\": \"stop you right there|阻止你立刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me stop you right there. We don't want to hear about that.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to hear|想听\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Language is the means by which people communicate with others.\", \"target\": \"communicate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"沟通\", \"phrase\": \"communicate with others|与他人沟通\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is becoming important for us to know how to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use a computer|使用电脑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Islam first reached China about the middle of the 7th century.\", \"target\": \"middle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"中间\", \"phrase\": \"the middle of the 7th century|7世纪中期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll sauté a few sweet potatoes and sprinkle them with sugar.\", \"target\": \"sugar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"糖\", \"phrase\": \"sprinkle with sugar|撒上糖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"movie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电影\", \"phrase\": \"movie theater|电影院\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you need to spend a little more time on your homework.\", \"target\": \"spend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"spend time|花时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I should have tried out this electric shaver before buying it.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"tried out|尝试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I should have tried out this electric shaver before buying it.\", \"target\": \"electric\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"电动的\", \"phrase\": \"electric shaver|电动剃须刀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...外面\", \"phrase\": \"outside the station|在车站外面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I doubt that Tom will ever learn how to speak French properly.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speak French|说法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was disappointed that things didn't turn out as he'd hoped.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"turn out|结果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was disappointed that things didn't turn out as he'd hoped.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"结果\", \"phrase\": \"turn out|结果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the concert schedule of London Symphony Orchestra?\", \"target\": \"schedule\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间表\", \"phrase\": \"concert schedule|音乐会日程\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the age of six, I was taken to a circus for the first time.\", \"target\": \"taken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带去\", \"phrase\": \"was taken|被带去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the age of six, I was taken to a circus for the first time.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"for the first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"护理\", \"phrase\": \"health care|医疗保健\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is take advantage of this rare opportunity.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"take advantage of|利用优势\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is take advantage of this rare opportunity.\", \"target\": \"advantage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"take advantage of|利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is take advantage of this rare opportunity.\", \"target\": \"rare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"稀有的\", \"phrase\": \"rare opportunity|难得的机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is take advantage of this rare opportunity.\", \"target\": \"opportunity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"rare opportunity|难得的机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A trip to America was equivalent to a two-year salary for her.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"two-year salary|两年工资\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A trip to America was equivalent to a two-year salary for her.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"two-year|两年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A couple of flights were delayed on account of the earthquake.\", \"target\": \"account\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"由于\", \"phrase\": \"on account of|由于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How long does it take to get to Vienna on foot?\\\" he inquired.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take to|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How long does it take to get to Vienna on foot?\\\" he inquired.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"get to|到达\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How long does it take to get to Vienna on foot?\\\" he inquired.\", \"target\": \"foot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脚\", \"phrase\": \"on foot|步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must be careful of the traffic when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"cross the street|过马路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With the T.V. on, how can you keep your mind on your studies?\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep your mind on|保持注意力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While we were discussing the problem, I hit upon a good idea.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"偶然发现\", \"phrase\": \"hit upon|偶然发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While we were discussing the problem, I hit upon a good idea.\", \"target\": \"upon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之上\", \"phrase\": \"hit upon|偶然发现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While we were discussing the problem, I hit upon a good idea.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good idea|好主意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think would happen if the earth stopped spinning?\", \"target\": \"stopped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"stopped spinning|停止旋转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the volume up so that the students at the back can hear.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"后方\", \"phrase\": \"at the back|在后方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went into the kitchen and poured himself a cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"poured\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"倒\", \"phrase\": \"poured himself a cup of coffee|给自己倒了一杯咖啡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went into the kitchen and poured himself a cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"cup of coffee|咖啡一杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he thought that Mary used to live in Boston.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"used to|曾经\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is still uncertain about whether to go to college or not.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to college|上大学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This novel is more interesting than the one I read last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This airplane is capable of carrying 40 passengers at a time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"at a time|一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They fine you in Singapore if you throw trash in the streets.\", \"target\": \"throw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扔\", \"phrase\": \"throw trash|扔垃圾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These scissors are suitable for left and right-handed people.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"左边的\", \"phrase\": \"left-handed|左手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These scissors are suitable for left and right-handed people.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"right-handed|左手或右手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These scissors are suitable for left and right-handed people.\", \"target\": \"handed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"手动的\", \"phrase\": \"right-handed|右手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old houses were torn down to make room for a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建造\", \"phrase\": \"make room|腾出空间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old houses were torn down to make room for a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"make room for|为…腾出空间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old church on the hill dates back to the twelfth century.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回溯\", \"phrase\": \"dates back|追溯到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house burned to the ground before the fire truck arrived.\", \"target\": \"ground\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地面\", \"phrase\": \"to the ground|到地面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conference is to be held in Tokyo the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"the day after tomorrow|后天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Small businesses will have to tighten their belts to survive.\", \"target\": \"tighten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"收紧\", \"phrase\": \"tighten their belts|勒紧裤腰带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Small businesses will have to tighten their belts to survive.\", \"target\": \"belts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"腰带\", \"phrase\": \"tighten their belts|勒紧腰带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since I had met him once before, I recognized him right away.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立刻\", \"phrase\": \"right away|立刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since I had met him once before, I recognized him right away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立刻\", \"phrase\": \"right away|立刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"old man|老人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tossed me grapes and I tried to catch them with my mouth.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"catch them|抓住它们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Several dozen young people participated in the demonstration.\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"several dozen|几个一打\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Problems that can be solved with money are not real problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"real problems|真正的问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Plastics have taken the place of many conventional materials.\", \"target\": \"taken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取代\", \"phrase\": \"taken the place of|取代...的位置\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Plastics have taken the place of many conventional materials.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"位置\", \"phrase\": \"take the place of|取代\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My grandfather is fond of taking a walk early in the morning.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"eight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"八个的\", \"phrase\": \"eight-hour working day|八小时工作日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"hour\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"eight-hour working day|八小时工作日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"working\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"工作的\", \"phrase\": \"working day|工作日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"working day|工作日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Judging from the look of the sky, it may rain this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"外观\", \"phrase\": \"look of the sky|天空的外观\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a place where I can charge my cellphone around here?\", \"target\": \"charge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"充电\", \"phrase\": \"charge my cellphone|给我的手机充电\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a place where I can charge my cellphone around here?\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|这附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"India ink produces an interesting pattern when used as a dye.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"used as|作为\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you feed your dog properly, you can increase his lifespan.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his lifespan|他的寿命\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still alive|仍然活着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a headache for three days and I can't get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a headache for three days and I can't get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弄清楚\", \"phrase\": \"figure out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"disable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"禁用\", \"phrase\": \"disable comments|禁用评论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"clock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时钟\", \"phrase\": \"two o'clock|两点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sometimes just don't want to get out of bed in the morning.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"get out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a group of foreigners on my way to school this morning.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way|在我的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just remembered that I was supposed to buy a loaf of bread.\", \"target\": \"bread\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"面包\", \"phrase\": \"loaf of bread|面包\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a phone call from him just as I was about to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to bed|上床睡觉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe that you were the smartest kid in your class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"in your class|在你的班级里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"foot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脚\", \"phrase\": \"on foot|步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"building\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建造\", \"phrase\": \"building a house|建造房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"building\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建造\", \"phrase\": \"building a house|建造房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"Red Cross|红十字会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"十字架; 交叉点; 越过\", \"phrase\": \"Red Cross|红十字会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"bowling\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"保龄球\", \"phrase\": \"gone bowling|去打保龄球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cancer can be cured easily if it is found in its first phase.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"first phase|第一阶段\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An opportunity like this only comes along once in a lifetime.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like this|像这样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An opportunity like this only comes along once in a lifetime.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"comes along|一起出现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a long argument, I finally persuaded her to go camping.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go camping|去露营\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"为了\", \"phrase\": \"in order to|为了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参加\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"take part|参与\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"boat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"船\", \"phrase\": \"boat race|赛舟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"race\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比赛\", \"phrase\": \"boat race|赛艇比赛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"burnt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"烧毁\", \"phrase\": \"burnt down|烧毁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Shall I have him call you when he gets back?\\\" \\\"Yes, please.\\\"\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"have him call|让他打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Shall I have him call you when he gets back?\\\" \\\"Yes, please.\\\"\", \"target\": \"gets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"gets back|回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Shall I have him call you when he gets back?\\\" \\\"Yes, please.\\\"\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"get back|回来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should try to form the habit of using your dictionaries.\", \"target\": \"form\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"形成\", \"phrase\": \"form the habit|养成习惯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should try to form the habit of using your dictionaries.\", \"target\": \"using\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"using your dictionaries|使用你的词典\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't fight a good fight with such a defeatist attitude.\", \"target\": \"fight\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"战斗\", \"phrase\": \"fight a good fight|奋勇拼搏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can lie to everyone else, but you can't lie to yourself.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't lie|不能说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can lie to everyone else, but you can't lie to yourself.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"lie to|对...说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like our neighbors, and they don't like us, either.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"don't like|不喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like our neighbors, and they don't like us, either.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"either...or|或者...或者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We did not expect him to finish the task in so short a time.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"short time|短时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We did not expect him to finish the task in so short a time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"short time|短时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom translated a letter from French to English for his boss.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his boss|他的老板\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took Mary to the hospital on the back of his motorcycle.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...的后部\", \"phrase\": \"on the back of|在...的后部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took Mary to the hospital on the back of his motorcycle.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"back of his motorcycle|他摩托车的后座\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This week the cherry blossoms in the park are in full bloom.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"充分的\", \"phrase\": \"full bloom|盛开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sleep in separate bedrooms even though they're married.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"even though|即使...尽管\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sleep in separate bedrooms even though they're married.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"even though|虽然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The first thing you have to take into consideration is time.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"take into consideration|考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The first thing you have to take into consideration is time.\", \"target\": \"consideration\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"take into consideration|考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pizza is the kind of food that fits into today's life style.\", \"target\": \"style\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风格\", \"phrase\": \"life style|生活方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My younger brother really likes to take photos of mountains.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拍摄\", \"phrase\": \"take photos|拍照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to deceive people, but worse to deceive yourself.\", \"target\": \"deceive\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欺骗\", \"phrase\": \"deceive yourself|欺骗自己\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you stay at a big hotel, you can use their swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big hotel|大酒店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you stay at a big hotel, you can use their swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use their swimming pool|使用他们的游泳池\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you stay at a big hotel, you can use their swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"pool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游泳池\", \"phrase\": \"swimming pool|游泳池\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for civil war, they would be wealthy now.\", \"target\": \"war\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"战争\", \"phrase\": \"civil war|内战\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I were you, I'd want to know what Tom is doing right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热的\", \"phrase\": \"hot weather|炎热的天气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to delete my Facebook account.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弄清楚\", \"phrase\": \"figure out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to delete my Facebook account.\", \"target\": \"delete\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"删除\", \"phrase\": \"delete my Facebook account|删除我的Facebook账户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought he loved you, but as it is, he loved another girl.\", \"target\": \"loved\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"loved another girl|爱另一个女孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought he loved you, but as it is, he loved another girl.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another girl|另一个女孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that our living together has influenced your habits.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"VBG\", \"zh\": \"一起生活\", \"phrase\": \"living together|一起生活\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that our living together has influenced your habits.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"living together|同居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that our living together has influenced your habits.\", \"target\": \"influenced\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"影响\", \"phrase\": \"living together has influenced|共同生活影响\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a hard time trying to persuade him to cancel the trip.\", \"target\": \"persuade\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说服\", \"phrase\": \"persuade him to cancel|说服他取消\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a hard time trying to persuade him to cancel the trip.\", \"target\": \"cancel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取消\", \"phrase\": \"cancel the trip|取消旅行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His bag is right here, so he cannot have gone to school yet.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"就在这里\", \"phrase\": \"right here|就在这里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His bag is right here, so he cannot have gone to school yet.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot have gone|不能去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was aware that I was around, but didn't come to greet me.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come to greet|前来问候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He asked me questions similar to those asked by many others.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"asked me questions|问我问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He asked me questions similar to those asked by many others.\", \"target\": \"similar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"相似的\", \"phrase\": \"similar to|类似于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He asked me questions similar to those asked by many others.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"asked by|被...问\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He asked me questions similar to those asked by many others.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"many others|许多其他人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father would often read detective stories in his spare time.\", \"target\": \"spare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"空闲的\", \"phrase\": \"spare time|空闲时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father would often read detective stories in his spare time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"spare time|空闲时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me, but could you tell me how to get to Central Park?\", \"target\": \"central\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"中央的\", \"phrase\": \"Central Park|中央公园\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Dr. Yukawa played an important part in the scientific study.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"important part|重要部分\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the rain, we weren't able to play tennis outside.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play tennis|打网球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the rain, we weren't able to play tennis outside.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在外面\", \"phrase\": \"outside|在外面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the newspaper, there was a big fire last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Write down the medications you need on this piece of paper.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一张纸\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|纸一张\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Write down the medications you need on this piece of paper.\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|一张纸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Tom woke up, he found Mary reading a book at the desk.\", \"target\": \"desk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书桌\", \"phrase\": \"at the desk|在书桌旁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We will endeavour to finish the job by the end of the week.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the week|周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We will continue the meeting after some light refreshments.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"轻的\", \"phrase\": \"light refreshments|茶点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Use a dictionary to find the meanings of the phrases below.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"find the meanings|找到意思\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Use a dictionary to find the meanings of the phrases below.\", \"target\": \"phrases\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"短语\", \"phrase\": \"phrases below|短语以下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two men are trying to figure out what's wrong with the car.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"figure out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wrote Mary a long letter, but he didn't send it to her.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long letter|长信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wrote Mary a long letter, but he didn't send it to her.\", \"target\": \"send\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发送\", \"phrase\": \"send it|寄送它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would never have let us go if Mary hadn't gone with us.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let us go|让我们走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would never have let us go if Mary hadn't gone with us.\", \"target\": \"gone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去过\", \"phrase\": \"hadn't gone with us|没有和我们一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would never have let us go if Mary hadn't gone with us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"with us|和我们一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he wouldn't be able to do what we asked him to do.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"asked him to do|要求他做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom likes to listen to music while he's doing his homework.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his homework|他的作业\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been to this park with Mary at least a dozen times.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least|至少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been to this park with Mary at least a dozen times.\", \"target\": \"dozen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一打\", \"phrase\": \"a dozen times|一打次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been to this park with Mary at least a dozen times.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"a dozen times|十二次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom died in the evening of the day he and Mary got married.\", \"target\": \"married\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结婚\", \"phrase\": \"got married|结婚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't want Mary to know he didn't know how to do that.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"didn't know|不知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't doubt that there would be a lot of people there.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't doubt that there would be a lot of people there.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of people|很多人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom almost always uses a credit card when he goes shopping.\", \"target\": \"credit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信用卡\", \"phrase\": \"credit card|信用卡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom almost always uses a credit card when he goes shopping.\", \"target\": \"card\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卡\", \"phrase\": \"credit card|信用卡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They wanted a wedding picture in front of the Eiffel Tower.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They wanted a wedding picture in front of the Eiffel Tower.\", \"target\": \"tower\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"塔\", \"phrase\": \"Eiffel Tower|埃菲尔铁塔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They tried very hard to gain an advantage over one another.\", \"target\": \"advantage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"gain an advantage|获得优势\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They tried very hard to gain an advantage over one another.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one another|彼此\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They tried very hard to gain an advantage over one another.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"one another|彼此\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no light without shade, and no shade without light.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without shade|没有阴影\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no light without shade, and no shade without light.\", \"target\": \"shade\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"阴影\", \"phrase\": \"without shade|没有阴影\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no light without shade, and no shade without light.\", \"target\": \"shade\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"阴影\", \"phrase\": \"without shade|没有阴影\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no light without shade, and no shade without light.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without light|没有光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no light without shade, and no shade without light.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"shade without light|没有光就没有阴影\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was some chewing gum stuck to the sole of Tom's shoe.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"粘住\", \"phrase\": \"stuck to|粘在...上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rain stopped us from being able to play tennis outside.\", \"target\": \"stopped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阻止\", \"phrase\": \"stopped us from|阻止我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rain stopped us from being able to play tennis outside.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"外面\", \"phrase\": \"outside|外面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The population of Japan is larger than that of New Zealand.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"proper noun\", \"zh\": \"新西兰\", \"phrase\": \"New Zealand|新西兰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The other day I went fishing for the first time in my life.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The other day I went fishing for the first time in my life.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only useful answers are those that raise new questions.\", \"target\": \"raise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提出\", \"phrase\": \"raise questions|提出问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only useful answers are those that raise new questions.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new questions|新问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most logical place to keep your shoes is near the door.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the door|在门附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She folded up the towels and put them away in the cupboard.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put away|收起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She folded up the towels and put them away in the cupboard.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"put away|收起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how much I think about it, I can't understand it.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"No matter|无论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has been engaged in foreign trade for many years.\", \"target\": \"engaged\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"从事\", \"phrase\": \"engaged in|从事于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has been engaged in foreign trade for many years.\", \"target\": \"trade\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"贸易\", \"phrase\": \"foreign trade|对外贸易\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a crying shame that they weren't insured against fire.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火灾\", \"phrase\": \"against fire|对火灾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there any chance that you'll go to Australia next month?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to Australia|去澳大利亚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there any chance that you'll go to Australia next month?\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个月\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the winter, many older people slip on ice and fall down.\", \"target\": \"slip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"滑倒\", \"phrase\": \"slip on ice|在冰上滑倒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the winter, many older people slip on ice and fall down.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摔倒\", \"phrase\": \"fall down|摔倒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would really like to know why he did something like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like that|像那样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would really like to know why he did something like that.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某事\", \"phrase\": \"something like that|类似的事情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would really like to know why he did something like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like that|像那样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather live by myself than do as he tells me to do.\", \"target\": \"tells\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"tells me to do|告诉我要我做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I waited half an hour for my friend, but he didn't turn up.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"半\", \"phrase\": \"half an hour|半个小时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I waited half an hour for my friend, but he didn't turn up.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出现\", \"phrase\": \"turn up|出现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car I want.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy the car|买车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"buy the car I want|我想买我想要的汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"buy the car that I want|我想买我想要的汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I slept a little during lunch break because I was so tired.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"lunch break|午休\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I let Tom watch a little TV after he finished his homework.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little TV|一点儿电视\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe your parents let you come here by yourself.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let you|让你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How to overcome the high value of the yen is a big problem.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high value|高价值\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How to overcome the high value of the yen is a big problem.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big problem|大问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was about to fall asleep, when he heard his name called.\", \"target\": \"fall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"入睡\", \"phrase\": \"fall asleep|入睡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was about to fall asleep, when he heard his name called.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his name|他的名字\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was about to fall asleep, when he heard his name called.\", \"target\": \"called\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"called his name|叫他的名字\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said that if he knew her address, he would write to her.\", \"target\": \"write\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"write to her|写信给她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He amassed a fortune in stock trading during the last boom.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last boom|最后一次繁荣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He amassed a fortune in stock trading during the last boom.\", \"target\": \"boom\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"繁荣\", \"phrase\": \"stock boom|股市繁荣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the storm, we had no choice but to stay at home.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"stay at home|待在家里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Anything you say may be held against you in a court of law.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"持有\", \"phrase\": \"held against|反对\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Anything you say may be held against you in a court of law.\", \"target\": \"court\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"法庭\", \"phrase\": \"court of law|法庭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Anything you say may be held against you in a court of law.\", \"target\": \"law\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"法律\", \"phrase\": \"court of law|法庭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of a sudden, the enemy bombs came down on us like rain.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like rain|像雨一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of a sudden, the enemy bombs came down on us like rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨\", \"phrase\": \"like rain|像雨一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"When will you come back?\\\" \\\"It all depends on the weather.\\\"\", \"target\": \"depends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"depends on|取决于...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"When will you come back?\\\" \\\"It all depends on the weather.\\\"\", \"target\": \"depends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"depends on|取决于...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You will exist but you will never know what it is to live.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will never|将不会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Yesterday, an explosion occurred at the fireworks factory.\", \"target\": \"fireworks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"烟花\", \"phrase\": \"fireworks factory|烟花工厂\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you mind if I shut the window? I have a slight cold.\", \"target\": \"shut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"shut the window|关窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With the weather getting worse, the departure was put off.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推迟\", \"phrase\": \"put off|推迟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When were you planning on telling Tom about what happened?\", \"target\": \"telling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"planning on telling|计划告诉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What mountain do you think is the second highest in Japan?\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal number\", \"zh\": \"第二\", \"phrase\": \"second highest|第二高的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We should try to avoid imposing our own beliefs on others.\", \"target\": \"imposing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"强加\", \"phrase\": \"imposing our own beliefs|强加我们的信念\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We should try to avoid imposing our own beliefs on others.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own beliefs|自己的信念\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We enjoyed watching the fireworks on a bridge last summer.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"last summer|去年夏天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Was this wall built to keep people out or to keep them in?\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep people out|把人们拒之门外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Was this wall built to keep people out or to keep them in?\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep them in|把他们关在里面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he thought that would probably never happen.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"never happen|永远不会发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom ran and ran, until at last he saw the telephone booth.\", \"target\": \"ran\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"ran and ran|跑和跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom ran and ran, until at last he saw the telephone booth.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最后\", \"phrase\": \"at last|最后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom lived in that small house for a little over ten years.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"small house|小房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom lived in that small house for a little over ten years.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a little over|稍微超过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has no intention of asking Mary to the upcoming dance.\", \"target\": \"upcoming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"即将到来的\", \"phrase\": \"upcoming dance|即将到来的舞会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Three months is too short a time to finish the experiment.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短\", \"phrase\": \"short time|短时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle of Hastings took place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"battle place|战场\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle of Hastings took place.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"took place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle of Hastings took place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"took place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle of Hastings took place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"battle place|战场\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle of Hastings took place.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"took place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle of Hastings took place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"took place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The simplest way is often the best way to solve a problem.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方法\", \"phrase\": \"best way|最佳方法\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The simplest way is often the best way to solve a problem.\", \"target\": \"solve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"solve a problem|解决问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The contract is in the bag, so let's go out and celebrate.\", \"target\": \"bag\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"包\", \"phrase\": \"in the bag|胜券在握\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The contract is in the bag, so let's go out and celebrate.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That was the part that Tom and I were most confused about.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"most confused|最困惑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That pretty girl wearing a bikini is Tom's younger sister.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"wearing a bikini|穿着比基尼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That coat may have cost a lot of money, but it's worth it.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of money|很多钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Step out of the car and place your hands behind your back.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"step out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Step out of the car and place your hands behind your back.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"hands behind your back|双手放在背后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Step out of the car and place your hands behind your back.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind your back|在你的背后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Step out of the car and place your hands behind your back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"背部\", \"phrase\": \"behind your back|在你的身后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people like red wine and some people like white wine.\", \"target\": \"wine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"葡萄酒\", \"phrase\": \"red wine|红酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people like red wine and some people like white wine.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"some people|一些人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people like red wine and some people like white wine.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like white wine|喜欢白葡萄酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people like red wine and some people like white wine.\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"white wine|白葡萄酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people like red wine and some people like white wine.\", \"target\": \"wine\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"葡萄酒\", \"phrase\": \"white wine|白葡萄酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My little brother ran through the living room stark naked.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"起居室\", \"phrase\": \"living room|客厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My little brother ran through the living room stark naked.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"living room|客厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My little brother ran through the living room stark naked.\", \"target\": \"stark\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"赤裸的\", \"phrase\": \"stark naked|赤裸的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My little brother ran through the living room stark naked.\", \"target\": \"naked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"裸体的\", \"phrase\": \"stark naked|赤裸的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many improvements have been made since this century began.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since this century began|自从这个世纪开始\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's impossible to do the sights of Tokyo in a day or two.\", \"target\": \"sights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"景点\", \"phrase\": \"do the sights|观光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was difficult for him to hide his pride in his success.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his success|他的成功\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It says in the Bible, \\\"Man shall not live on bread alone.\\\"\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"单独地\", \"phrase\": \"alone|单独地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is up to you to decide whether we will go there or not.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go there|去那里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is up to you to decide whether we will go there or not.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go there|去那里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the Edo period, moon-viewing parties were very popular.\", \"target\": \"viewing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"观看\", \"phrase\": \"moon-viewing parties|赏月会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never been to New York, and my sister hasn't, either.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"either...or|或者...或者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I wasn't able to see you when you came by today.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"came by|过来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to have this meat dish with your best white wine.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best wine|最好的酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to have this meat dish with your best white wine.\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"white wine|白葡萄酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to have this meat dish with your best white wine.\", \"target\": \"wine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"葡萄酒\", \"phrase\": \"white wine|白葡萄酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd gladly pay more for something if it's of high quality.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high quality|高质量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need you to promise that you'll do what I ask you to do.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will do|将做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to abstain from smoking while I was in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"abstain from smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like being the one who always has to milk the cow.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the one|那一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like being the one who always has to milk the cow.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"always has to|总是不得不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like being the one who always has to milk the cow.\", \"target\": \"milk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"挤奶\", \"phrase\": \"milk the cow|挤奶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"However hard I try, I can't do it any better than she can.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"any better|任何更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to go from here to the Hilton Hotel?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to go from here to the Hilton Hotel?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go from here to the Hilton Hotel|从这里去希尔顿酒店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to go from here to the Hilton Hotel?\", \"target\": \"hotel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"酒店\", \"phrase\": \"Hilton Hotel|希尔顿酒店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He owes his success both to working hard and to good luck.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good luck|好运\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is numbered among the greatest scientists in the world.\", \"target\": \"numbered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被编号\", \"phrase\": \"be numbered among|被列为\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is numbered among the greatest scientists in the world.\", \"target\": \"among\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之中\", \"phrase\": \"numbered among|被列在...之中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a man of few words, but he always keeps his promise.\", \"target\": \"words\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话语\", \"phrase\": \"man of few words|惜字如金\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a man of few words, but he always keeps his promise.\", \"target\": \"keeps\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遵守\", \"phrase\": \"keeps his promise|遵守诺言\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a man of few words, but he always keeps his promise.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his promise|他的承诺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"France is running a welfare state it can no longer afford.\", \"target\": \"afford\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"负担得起\", \"phrase\": \"cannot afford|负担不起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, I must share this room with my friend.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"for the time being|暂时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ebola spreads from person to person through bodily fluids.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"person to person|人与人之间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you really need to ask the question to know the answer?\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"ask the question|问问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you really need to ask the question to know the answer?\", \"target\": \"question\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"ask the question|问问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Both of Tom's parents passed away when he was quite young.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"去世\", \"phrase\": \"passed away|去世\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Between you and me, I'm going to quit my present job soon.\", \"target\": \"quit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"辞职\", \"phrase\": \"quit my job|辞职\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Between you and me, I'm going to quit my present job soon.\", \"target\": \"present\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"现在的\", \"phrase\": \"present job|现在的工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be careful not to drive the wrong way on a one-way street.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"wrong way|错误的方向\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be careful not to drive the wrong way on a one-way street.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"wrong way|错误的方向\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be careful not to drive the wrong way on a one-way street.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"单行\", \"phrase\": \"one-way street|单行道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be careful not to drive the wrong way on a one-way street.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方向\", \"phrase\": \"wrong way|错误的方向\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"bowling\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"保龄球\", \"phrase\": \"gone bowling|去打保龄球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is to write your name and address here.\", \"target\": \"address\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地址\", \"phrase\": \"name and address|姓名和地址\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After running up the hill, I was completely out of breath.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"精疲力尽\", \"phrase\": \"out of breath|气喘吁吁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A true scientist would not approach the question this way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"approach the question this way|以这种方式处理这个问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little walk will give you a good appetite for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give you|给你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little walk will give you a good appetite for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good appetite|好胃口\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What would you like to buy?\\\" \\\"I would like to buy a dog.\\\"\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"would like to buy|想买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What would you like to buy?\\\" \\\"I would like to buy a dog.\\\"\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What would you like to buy?\\\" \\\"I would like to buy a dog.\\\"\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What would you like to buy?\\\" \\\"I would like to buy a dog.\\\"\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"would like to buy|想买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have done it earlier. It cannot be helped now.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot be helped|无法帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have done it earlier. It cannot be helped now.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot be helped|不能帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You never get a second chance to make a first impression.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"first impression|第一印象\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have no right to interfere in other people's affairs.\", \"target\": \"interfere\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"干涉\", \"phrase\": \"interfere in|干涉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have no right to interfere in other people's affairs.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"people's affairs|人事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have changed so much that I can hardly recognize you.\", \"target\": \"hardly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎不\", \"phrase\": \"hardly recognize|几乎认不出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You cannot purchase this medicine without a prescription.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without a prescription|没有处方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would it be ethical to sacrifice one person to save many?\", \"target\": \"save\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拯救\", \"phrase\": \"save many|拯救许多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When he shouted, the veins in his neck stood out clearly.\", \"target\": \"stood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"站立\", \"phrase\": \"stood out|显现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When he shouted, the veins in his neck stood out clearly.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"stood out|显现\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We often hear it said that the Japanese are good workers.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good workers|好工人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We need you to tell us why you were absent all last week.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are here in the name of Jesus Christ and King Charles.\", \"target\": \"king\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国王\", \"phrase\": \"King Charles|查尔斯国王\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are all looking forward to seeing you and your family.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"期待地\", \"phrase\": \"looking forward to|期待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tsunamis swept through rice fields and flooded the towns.\", \"target\": \"swept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"席卷\", \"phrase\": \"swept through|席卷通过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was sitting alone at one of the tables near the door.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one of the tables|桌子中的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was sitting alone at one of the tables near the door.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the door|在门附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom used a fire extinguisher to try and put the fire out.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"fire extinguisher|灭火器\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom used a fire extinguisher to try and put the fire out.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"熄灭\", \"phrase\": \"put out|扑灭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom used a fire extinguisher to try and put the fire out.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"fire extinguisher|灭火器\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom used a fire extinguisher to try and put the fire out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"灭\", \"phrase\": \"put out|扑灭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably doesn't know how to do that as well as Mary.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"as well|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is wearing the same clothes he was wearing yesterday.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"is wearing|穿着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is wearing the same clothes he was wearing yesterday.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"was wearing|穿着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't have any friends who are willing to help him.\", \"target\": \"willing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"乐意的\", \"phrase\": \"willing to help|乐于帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't have any friends who are willing to help him.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"willing to help|愿意帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did a good job predicting who would win the election.\", \"target\": \"win\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢\", \"phrase\": \"win the election|赢得选举\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To tell you the truth, this is a little too spicy for me.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little too spicy|有点儿太辣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To tell you the truth, this is a little too spicy for me.\", \"target\": \"spicy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"辣的\", \"phrase\": \"too spicy|太辣了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They referred to Chaucer as the father of English poetry.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"father of English poetry|英语诗歌之父\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They are leaving in three days, that is to say June 10th.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"to say|说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was so crowded that I had to stand all the way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"all the way|一路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The gate is so narrow that the car can't pass through it.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot pass|不能通过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The gate is so narrow that the car can't pass through it.\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"通过\", \"phrase\": \"pass through|通过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thanks very much for having me to dinner the other night.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚上\", \"phrase\": \"the other night|前夜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tried to lift the box, but found it impossible to do.\", \"target\": \"impossible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不可能的\", \"phrase\": \"impossible to do|做不到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is always poking his nose into my private life.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his nose|他的鼻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is always poking his nose into my private life.\", \"target\": \"nose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鼻子\", \"phrase\": \"poking his nose into|干涉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't really sick. She's only pretending to be sick.\", \"target\": \"pretending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"pretending to be|假装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't really sick. She's only pretending to be sick.\", \"target\": \"sick\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的\", \"phrase\": \"to be sick|生病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't really sick. She's just pretending to be sick.\", \"target\": \"pretending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"pretending to be|假装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't really sick. She's just pretending to be sick.\", \"target\": \"sick\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的\", \"phrase\": \"to be sick|生病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's gravity that makes satellites move around the Earth.\", \"target\": \"move\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"移动\", \"phrase\": \"move around|围绕移动\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's gravity that makes satellites move around the Earth.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"围绕\", \"phrase\": \"move around|移动围绕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is very expensive to keep up with the latest fashions.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep up with|跟上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is very expensive to keep up with the latest fashions.\", \"target\": \"latest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最新的\", \"phrase\": \"latest fashions|最新的时尚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case of fire, break the glass and push the red button.\", \"target\": \"push\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推\", \"phrase\": \"push the red button|按下红色按钮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case of fire, break the glass and push the red button.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"red button|红色按钮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you would move over, there would be room for everyone.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would be|将会是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you would move over, there would be room for everyone.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"room for everyone|为每个人留出空间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you do not have this program, you can download it now.\", \"target\": \"download\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下载\", \"phrase\": \"download it|下载它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If there's anything urgent, you can get in touch with me.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"get in touch with|联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never forget shaking the President's hand last year.\", \"target\": \"shaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握手\", \"phrase\": \"shaking hands|握手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never forget shaking the President's hand last year.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"shaking hands|握手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never forget shaking the President's hand last year.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"last year|去年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would like to have a look at your collection of stamps.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"have a look|看一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to move out of this cramped room as soon as I can.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"move out|搬出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried very hard to put an end to their heated argument.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"put an end to|结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried very hard to put an end to their heated argument.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"put an end to|结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried very hard to put an end to their heated argument.\", \"target\": \"argument\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"争论\", \"phrase\": \"heated argument|激烈的争论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't look at this painting without thinking of my mom.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without thinking of|没有想到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is proud of having been educated in the United States.\", \"target\": \"educated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"受过教育\", \"phrase\": \"been educated|受过教育\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is proud of having been educated in the United States.\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is proud of having been educated in the United States.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody except Tom knew that he didn't need to do that.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except Tom|除了汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't forget to come and pick me up at the train station.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡\", \"phrase\": \"pick me up|接我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't forget to come and pick me up at the train station.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't forget to come and pick me up at the train station.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children should keep away from the river. It's dangerous.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"keep away from|远离...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Almost everyone in our village is related to one another.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one another|彼此\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Almost everyone in our village is related to one another.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"one another|彼此\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is push this button to take a picture.\", \"target\": \"push\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"按下\", \"phrase\": \"push this button|按下这个按钮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is push this button to take a picture.\", \"target\": \"button\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"按钮\", \"phrase\": \"push button|按下按钮\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Action speaks louder than words, but not nearly as often.\", \"target\": \"words\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"speaks louder than words|言行胜于雄辩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Action speaks louder than words, but not nearly as often.\", \"target\": \"nearly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎\", \"phrase\": \"not nearly|几乎不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A girl gave me an orange in exchange for a piece of cake.\", \"target\": \"exchange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"交换\", \"phrase\": \"in exchange for|作为...的交换\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A girl gave me an orange in exchange for a piece of cake.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一块\", \"phrase\": \"piece of cake|一块蛋糕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A girl gave me an orange in exchange for a piece of cake.\", \"target\": \"cake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蛋糕\", \"phrase\": \"piece of cake|一块蛋糕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"When will you be back?\\\" \\\"It all depends on the weather.\\\"\", \"target\": \"depends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"depends on|取决于...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"When will you be back?\\\" \\\"It all depends on the weather.\\\"\", \"target\": \"depends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"depends on|取决于...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better take an umbrella with you in case it rains.\", \"target\": \"case\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"以防\", \"phrase\": \"in case|以防\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should ask your father for his advice and follow it.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his advice|他的建议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should ask your father for his advice and follow it.\", \"target\": \"follow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跟随\", \"phrase\": \"follow it|遵循它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are old enough to know better than to act like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like that|那样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Write down the medicine you need on this piece of paper.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一张纸\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|纸一张\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Write down the medicine you need on this piece of paper.\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|纸片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With just a little more effort, he would have succeeded.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little more|稍微多一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which do you like better, rock music or classical music?\", \"target\": \"music\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"音乐\", \"phrase\": \"classical music|古典音乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to turn in our reports by the end of this month.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提交\", \"phrase\": \"turn in|提交\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to turn in our reports by the end of this month.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the month|月末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We all chipped in to buy our teacher a birthday present.\", \"target\": \"chipped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"凑钱\", \"phrase\": \"chipped in|凑钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tomorrow's weather should be sunny with occasional rain.\", \"target\": \"occasional\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"偶发的\", \"phrase\": \"occasional rain|阵雨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tomorrow's weather should be sunny with occasional rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨\", \"phrase\": \"occasional rain|偶尔下雨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom still works at the same restaurant where Mary works.\", \"target\": \"works\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"works at|在...工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This piece of music is way too difficult for me to play.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"way too|太...了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These cardboard boxes are a hundred per cent recyclable.\", \"target\": \"cent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"百分\", \"phrase\": \"hundred per cent|百分之百\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are too many people here. Let's go somewhere else.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"别的\", \"phrase\": \"somewhere else|其他地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The students were for the most part from the West Coast.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"大多数\", \"phrase\": \"for the most part|大部分\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The students were for the most part from the West Coast.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"for the most part|大部分\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The students were for the most part from the West Coast.\", \"target\": \"west\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西部\", \"phrase\": \"West Coast|西海岸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The population of Shanghai is as large as that of Tokyo.\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"as large as|和...一样大\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The court declared him innocent on the charge of murder.\", \"target\": \"charge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"指控\", \"phrase\": \"charge of murder|谋杀指控\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bathtub was filled with hot water and flower petals.\", \"target\": \"filled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"充满\", \"phrase\": \"filled with|充满...以\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bathtub was filled with hot water and flower petals.\", \"target\": \"flower\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"flower petals|花瓣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The audience was largely made up of very young children.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"组成\", \"phrase\": \"made up of|由...组成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for the wonderful dinner last night.\", \"target\": \"wonderful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"极好的\", \"phrase\": \"wonderful dinner|美好的晚餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for the wonderful dinner last night.\", \"target\": \"dinner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚餐\", \"phrase\": \"wonderful dinner|美妙的晚餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for the wonderful dinner last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sometimes I smoke just to give my hands something to do.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give my hands something to do|让我的手有事做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sometimes I smoke just to give my hands something to do.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"hands something to do|做点什么\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please send me a reply as soon as you receive this mail.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please hide the blueberry jam where Takako can't see it.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't see it|看不到它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People, old and young, all came out to greet the guests.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"came out|出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People, old and young, all came out to greet the guests.\", \"target\": \"greet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"迎接\", \"phrase\": \"greet the guests|迎接客人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one noticed her absence until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the meeting|会议结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My sister is twenty-one years old and a college student.\", \"target\": \"college\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大学\", \"phrase\": \"college student|大学生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My plan is to spend the New Year's holiday in Australia.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"New Year's|新年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My plan is to spend the New Year's holiday in Australia.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"New Year|新年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents have gone to the airport to see my uncle off.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see off|送别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother has a driver's license, but she doesn't drive.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is very much involved in the stock market now.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is very much involved in the stock market now.\", \"target\": \"stock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"股票\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is very much involved in the stock market now.\", \"target\": \"market\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市场\", \"phrase\": \"stock market|股市\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most people think computers will never be able to think.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"思考\", \"phrase\": \"be able to think|能够思考\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mastering a foreign language involves a lot of patience.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life would be so much better if you didn't care so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"so much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life would be so much better if you didn't care so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"so much|如此之多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me remind you again that March 31st is the due date.\", \"target\": \"due\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"到期的\", \"phrase\": \"due date|截止日期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to say what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"be like|像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good thing to read good books when you are young.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good thing|好事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good thing to read good books when you are young.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good books|好书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was before dawn that they got the fire under control.\", \"target\": \"control\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"控制\", \"phrase\": \"under control|控制住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't come, you should let me know ahead of time.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let me know|让我知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't come, you should let me know ahead of time.\", \"target\": \"ahead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"提前\", \"phrase\": \"ahead of time|提前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't come, you should let me know ahead of time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"ahead of time|提前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm considering studying in the United States next year.\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm considering studying in the United States next year.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"明年\", \"phrase\": \"next year|明年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will only buy the car if they repair the brakes first.\", \"target\": \"repair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"repair the brakes|修理刹车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will only buy the car if they repair the brakes first.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"first|首先\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was surprised at his strong resemblance to his father.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强壮的\", \"phrase\": \"strong resemblance|强烈相似\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was surprised at his strong resemblance to his father.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"strong resemblance to his father|他父亲的强烈相似之处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that I told you to stay away from my computer.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"stay away|远离\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that I told you to stay away from my computer.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"stay away|远离\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you were the smartest kid in your class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"in your class|在你的班级里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much time do you estimate it'll take you to do that?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her absence went unnoticed until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the meeting|会议结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He visited his hometown for the first time in ten years.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He hurried to the station so he wouldn't miss the train.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"miss the train|错过火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always plans a thing out carefully before he does it.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仔细地\", \"phrase\": \"plans out|计划\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone except Tom knew that he didn't need to do that.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except Tom|除了汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how far it is from the station to city hall?\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"city hall|市政厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how far it is from the station to city hall?\", \"target\": \"hall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大厅\", \"phrase\": \"city hall|市政厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you keep in contact with your high school classmates?\", \"target\": \"contact\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"keep in contact|保持联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you keep in contact with your high school classmates?\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high school|高中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you keep in contact with your high school classmates?\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"high school|高中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Dad gave me a book, and my little brother gave me a pen.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"little brother|小弟弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Dad gave me a book, and my little brother gave me a pen.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"gave me|给了我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the time Tom got home, we were already eating dinner.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"already eating dinner|已经在吃晚饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the time Tom got home, we were already eating dinner.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating dinner|吃晚餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Apart from on rainy days, I always ride my bike to work.\", \"target\": \"apart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"apart from|除了...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Apart from on rainy days, I always ride my bike to work.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑\", \"phrase\": \"ride my bike|骑我的自行车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A slip of the tongue is sometimes fatal to a politician.\", \"target\": \"tongue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"舌头\", \"phrase\": \"slip of the tongue|口误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A lot of students around the world are studying English.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the world|世界各地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A glass of cold water is very refreshing in hot weather.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold water|冷水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A glass of cold water is very refreshing in hot weather.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"hot weather|炎热的天气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got to set the alarm clock before you go to bed.\", \"target\": \"alarm\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"闹钟\", \"phrase\": \"alarm clock|闹钟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got to set the alarm clock before you go to bed.\", \"target\": \"clock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时钟\", \"phrase\": \"alarm clock|闹钟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You won't be able to see anything without a flashlight.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without a flashlight|没有手电筒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You won't be able to see anything without a flashlight.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without a flashlight|没有手电筒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You had better read a lot of books while you are young.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to know how to prevent getting wrinkles?\", \"target\": \"prevent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"防止\", \"phrase\": \"prevent getting wrinkles|防止皱纹\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Women eat lighter meals when they're eating with a guy.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating with|和...一起吃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you help me give out the programs to those people?\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give out|分发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you help me give out the programs to those people?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分发\", \"phrase\": \"give out|分发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whether you succeed or not depends on your own efforts.\", \"target\": \"depends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"depends on|取决于...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whether you succeed or not depends on your own efforts.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own efforts|自身努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whether you succeed or not depends on your own efforts.\", \"target\": \"efforts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"努力\", \"phrase\": \"own efforts|自身努力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we're children, everything around us looks so big.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"around us|在我们周围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We encountered a lot of difficulties on the expedition.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he'd give me that book if I wanted it.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give me|给我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he'd give me that book if I wanted it.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wanted it|想要它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me not to open the envelope until my birthday.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the envelope|打开信封\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom seems to hardly ever get his homework done on time.\", \"target\": \"hardly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎不\", \"phrase\": \"hardly ever|几乎从不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom seems to hardly ever get his homework done on time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"on time|准时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom needs to study more if he hopes to pass this class.\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"通过\", \"phrase\": \"pass this class|通过这门课\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom needs to study more if he hopes to pass this class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"this class|这个班级\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knew that Mary wanted him to go to Boston with her.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to Boston|去波士顿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got the job on the strength of your recommendation.\", \"target\": \"strength\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"力量\", \"phrase\": \"on the strength of|凭借\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got the job on the strength of your recommendation.\", \"target\": \"recommendation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"推荐信\", \"phrase\": \"on the strength of your recommendation|凭借你的推荐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked Mary if she knew John's new telephone number.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new telephone number|新的电话号码\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked Mary if she knew John's new telephone number.\", \"target\": \"telephone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"telephone number|电话号码\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Time passes quickly when we're doing something we like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"doing something we like|做我们喜欢的事情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They had their houses destroyed by a strong earthquake.\", \"target\": \"destroyed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摧毁\", \"phrase\": \"had their houses destroyed|他们的房子被摧毁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They had their houses destroyed by a strong earthquake.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强\", \"phrase\": \"strong earthquake|强烈地震\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a good chance that gasoline prices will go up.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"上涨\", \"phrase\": \"go up|上涨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sun comes up in the east and goes down in the west.\", \"target\": \"goes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"落下\", \"phrase\": \"goes down|落下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sun comes up in the east and goes down in the west.\", \"target\": \"west\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西\", \"phrase\": \"in the west|在西边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The show was very interesting. You should have seen it.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看到\", \"phrase\": \"have seen|已经看过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent coffee shortage brought about many problems.\", \"target\": \"brought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带来\", \"phrase\": \"brought about|导致\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent coffee shortage brought about many problems.\", \"target\": \"brought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带来\", \"phrase\": \"brought about|导致\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The radio is too loud. Can't you turn it down a little?\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关小\", \"phrase\": \"turn down|调小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The radio is too loud. Can't you turn it down a little?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The opening ceremony of the Olympics has already begun.\", \"target\": \"opening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开幕的\", \"phrase\": \"opening ceremony|开幕式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people who go abroad has been increasing.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go abroad|出国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The mother missed her daughter who was away at college.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"away at college|在大学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Japanese military forces seemed too strong to stop.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强\", \"phrase\": \"too strong|太强\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Japanese military forces seemed too strong to stop.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"to stop|停止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sorry, but can you show me the way to the next village?\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"the way|道路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sorry, but can you show me the way to the next village?\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next village|下一个村庄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She needed some money to buy something to feed her dog.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy something|买东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She needed some money to buy something to feed her dog.\", \"target\": \"feed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喂养\", \"phrase\": \"feed her dog|喂养她的狗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Prince William is second in line to the English throne.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"排队\", \"phrase\": \"in line|排队\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One hundred and fifty people entered the marathon race.\", \"target\": \"race\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比赛\", \"phrase\": \"marathon race|马拉松比赛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife's part-time job brings in a little extra money.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little extra money|一点额外的钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother happened to be there when the fire broke out.\", \"target\": \"broke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"broke out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother happened to be there when the fire broke out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"broke out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My brother is very important. At least he thinks he is.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least|至少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My brother is very important. At least he thinks he is.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least|至少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Meet me at the lobby of the Imperial Hotel at 6:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"hotel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"酒店\", \"phrase\": \"Imperial Hotel|帝国酒店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many people are suffering from hunger around the world.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the world|世界各地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go out and eat dinner together from time to time.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go out and eat dinner together from time to time.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eat dinner|吃晚餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go out and eat dinner together from time to time.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"from time to time together|偶尔一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go out and eat dinner together from time to time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"from time to time|偶尔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go out and eat dinner together from time to time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"from time to time|偶尔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lake Baikal in Russia is the deepest lake in the world.\", \"target\": \"lake\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"湖\", \"phrase\": \"Lake Baikal|贝加尔湖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lake Baikal in Russia is the deepest lake in the world.\", \"target\": \"lake\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"湖\", \"phrase\": \"Lake Baikal|贝加尔湖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Kissing a person who smokes is like licking an ashtray.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like licking an ashtray|像舔一个烟灰缸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Just as he was going out, there was a great earthquake.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"巨大的\", \"phrase\": \"great earthquake|大地震\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's easy to make friends, but hard to get rid of them.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's easy to make friends, but hard to get rid of them.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It takes 165 years for Neptune to orbit around the sun.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"围绕\", \"phrase\": \"orbit around|围绕...轨道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that money cannot buy happiness.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"goes without saying|不言而喻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that money cannot buy happiness.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot buy|不能买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that money cannot buy happiness.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"购买\", \"phrase\": \"buy happiness|购买幸福\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Iron the inside of collars first, and then the outside.\", \"target\": \"iron\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"熨烫\", \"phrase\": \"iron the inside|熨烫内部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Iron the inside of collars first, and then the outside.\", \"target\": \"inside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"内部\", \"phrase\": \"inside of collars|领子的内部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Iron the inside of collars first, and then the outside.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"first, and|首先，和\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Iron the inside of collars first, and then the outside.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"外部\", \"phrase\": \"outside|外部\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you are not going to the concert, then neither am I.\", \"target\": \"neither\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"也不\", \"phrase\": \"neither am I|我也不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm certain that Tom is the only one who won't do that.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the only one|唯一的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid I can't help you. You must ask someone else.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"ask someone else|问别人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid I can't help you. You must ask someone else.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"否则\", \"phrase\": \"ask someone else|问别人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was quite thirsty and wanted to drink something cool.\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"drink something|喝点东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was quite thirsty and wanted to drink something cool.\", \"target\": \"cool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"凉爽的\", \"phrase\": \"something cool|凉爽的东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I studied English for four years with a native speaker.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"native speaker|母语者\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really look forward to your visit in the near future.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"期待\", \"phrase\": \"look forward to|期待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really look forward to your visit in the near future.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"附近的\", \"phrase\": \"near future|不久的将来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lost my job and I have no money. I'm at my wit's end.\", \"target\": \"wit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"才智\", \"phrase\": \"at my wit's end|到绝境\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lost my job and I have no money. I'm at my wit's end.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尽头\", \"phrase\": \"at my wit's end|走投无路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a friend waiting for me in front of the library.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to study hard to keep up with the other students.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep up with|跟上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found a good place to buy fruit a couple of days ago.\", \"target\": \"couple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"a couple of days|几天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I felt so sleepy that I could hardly keep my eyes open.\", \"target\": \"hardly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎不\", \"phrase\": \"hardly keep|几乎不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I felt so sleepy that I could hardly keep my eyes open.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep my eyes open|睁开眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I felt so sleepy that I could hardly keep my eyes open.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"keep my eyes open|保持睁开眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I felt so sleepy that I could hardly keep my eyes open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"keep my eyes open|睁开眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to go there. He doesn't want to go either.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to go|想要去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to go there. He doesn't want to go either.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go there|去那里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to go there. He doesn't want to go either.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"either|也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't survive without air conditioning in the summer.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without air conditioning|没有空调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't survive without air conditioning in the summer.\", \"target\": \"air\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"空气\", \"phrase\": \"air conditioning|空调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't survive without air conditioning in the summer.\", \"target\": \"conditioning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"空调\", \"phrase\": \"air conditioning|空调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always have a look at the newspaper before breakfast.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"have a look|看一看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His record is a new world record in the 100-meter dash.\", \"target\": \"record\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"记录\", \"phrase\": \"world record|世界纪录\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His record is a new world record in the 100-meter dash.\", \"target\": \"meter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"米\", \"phrase\": \"100-meter dash|100米短跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He went on reading the book as if nothing had happened.\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"什么也没有\", \"phrase\": \"nothing had happened|什么也没有发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't know the difference between right and wrong.\", \"target\": \"difference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区别\", \"phrase\": \"the difference between...|...之间的区别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Finishing the report by tomorrow is next to impossible.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎\", \"phrase\": \"next to impossible|几乎不可能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Finishing the report by tomorrow is next to impossible.\", \"target\": \"impossible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不可能的\", \"phrase\": \"next to impossible|几乎不可能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't be afraid to make mistakes when speaking English.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯\", \"phrase\": \"make mistakes|犯错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't be afraid to make mistakes when speaking English.\", \"target\": \"speaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speaking English|说英语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't be afraid to make mistakes when speaking English.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯\", \"phrase\": \"make mistakes|犯错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't be afraid to make mistakes when speaking English.\", \"target\": \"speaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speaking English|说英语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to get married first or have a child first?\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"get married first|先结婚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to get married first or have a child first?\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"get married first|先结婚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Books are for people who wish they were somewhere else.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"其他地方\", \"phrase\": \"somewhere else|在其他地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be sure to drop us a line as soon as you get to London.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"落下; 投递\", \"phrase\": \"drop us a line|给…写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be sure to drop us a line as soon as you get to London.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"drop us a line|给…写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are there any direct flights between Boston and Sydney?\", \"target\": \"direct\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"直接的\", \"phrase\": \"direct flights|直飞航班\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All horses are animals, but not all animals are horses.\", \"target\": \"animals\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"动物\", \"phrase\": \"not all animals|并非所有动物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All horses are animals, but not all animals are horses.\", \"target\": \"horses\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"not all animals are horses|并非所有动物都是马\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to TV news, there was a plane crash in India.\", \"target\": \"crash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"坠毁\", \"phrase\": \"plane crash|飞机失事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How did you get my phone number?\\\" \\\"Tom gave it to me.\\\"\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"gave it|给了它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"He'd like to have a coffee after work.\\\" \\\"I would too.\\\"\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"would too|也一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"He'd like to have a coffee after work.\\\" \\\"I would too.\\\"\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"after work|下班后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"He'd like to have a coffee after work.\\\" \\\"I would too.\\\"\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"would too|也一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're the one who suggested that we do that together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"do that together|一起做那件事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should've done it earlier. It can't be helped now.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't|不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You need to attach your photo to the application form.\", \"target\": \"attach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"附加\", \"phrase\": \"attach your photo|附加你的照片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You continue making the same mistakes time after time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"time after time|一次又一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You continue making the same mistakes time after time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"time after time|一次又一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Women are not permitted to drive cars in Saudi Arabia.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drive cars|驾驶汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With your approval, I would like to offer him the job.\", \"target\": \"offer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提供\", \"phrase\": \"offer him the job|给他提供工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who is in charge of the office while the boss is away?\", \"target\": \"charge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"负责\", \"phrase\": \"in charge of|负责...的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Were you able to do everything you wanted to get done?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"get done|完成\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We will have learned English for five years next year.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"five years|五年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We will have learned English for five years next year.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"明年\", \"phrase\": \"next year|明年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We should approach this problem from different angles.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"different angles|不同的角度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We should approach this problem from different angles.\", \"target\": \"angles\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"角度\", \"phrase\": \"different angles|不同角度\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was able to go to college thanks to a scholarship.\", \"target\": \"thanks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"由于\", \"phrase\": \"thanks to|由于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary he couldn't do what she asked him to do.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"asked him to do|要求他做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary was probably still studying French.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still studying|仍然学习\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom poured cold water over himself to wake himself up.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold water|冷水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom poured cold water over himself to wake himself up.\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"水\", \"phrase\": \"cold water|冷水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom dragged himself out of bed and put on his clothes.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从\", \"phrase\": \"dragged himself out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom dragged himself out of bed and put on his clothes.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿\", \"phrase\": \"put on|穿上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom dragged himself out of bed and put on his clothes.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his clothes|他的衣服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like people who smoke in no smoking areas.\", \"target\": \"smoke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吸烟\", \"phrase\": \"smoke in|在...吸烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like people who smoke in no smoking areas.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"gerund\", \"zh\": \"吸烟\", \"phrase\": \"smoking areas|禁烟区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like people who smoke in no smoking areas.\", \"target\": \"areas\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区域\", \"phrase\": \"smoking areas|禁烟区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't get to sleep till after three last night.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"till after three|直到凌晨三点之后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't get to sleep till after three last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could have dealt with the problem in a better way.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better way|更好的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could have dealt with the problem in a better way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"in a better way|以更好的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I have decided to go to Australia next summer.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to Australia|去澳大利亚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This laboratory is equipped with the latest computers.\", \"target\": \"equipped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"配备\", \"phrase\": \"equipped with|配备有\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is considered to be a matter of great importance.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"伟大的\", \"phrase\": \"great importance|重要性\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a sudden drop in the temperature last night.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"下降\", \"phrase\": \"drop in|下降在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a sudden drop in the temperature last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There used to be a big pine tree in front of my house.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a bookstore in front of the department store.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a bookstore in front of the department store.\", \"target\": \"store\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"商店\", \"phrase\": \"department store|百货商店\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Their contract is to run out at the end of this month.\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"run out|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Their contract is to run out at the end of this month.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"run out|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Their contract is to run out at the end of this month.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the month|月末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The young man saved the girl from a bunch of hoodlums.\", \"target\": \"bunch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一群\", \"phrase\": \"bunch of hoodlums|一群歹徒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The policeman told me that the last bus leaves at ten.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last bus|末班车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The movie is worth seeing at least two or three times.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least|至少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The movie is worth seeing at least two or three times.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"two or three times|两次或三次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bus is full. You'll have to wait for the next one.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next one|下一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bus is full. You'll have to wait for the next one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"next one|下一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave birth to her first child at twenty years old.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"first child|第一个孩子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She covered the mouthpiece of the phone with her hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"with her hand|用她的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Seen from the sky, the river looked like a huge snake.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looked like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Seen from the sky, the river looked like a huge snake.\", \"target\": \"huge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"巨大的\", \"phrase\": \"huge snake|巨大的蛇\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please bring us two cups of tea and one cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"cups\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"two cups of tea|两杯茶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please bring us two cups of tea and one cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"one cup|一杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please bring us two cups of tea and one cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯\", \"phrase\": \"cups of tea|茶杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once in a while, we should take a step back and think.\", \"target\": \"step\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"步骤\", \"phrase\": \"take a step back|退一步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once in a while, we should take a step back and think.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向后\", \"phrase\": \"step back|退后一步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My husband reads the newspaper while eating breakfast.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating breakfast|吃早餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My husband reads the newspaper while eating breakfast.\", \"target\": \"breakfast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早餐\", \"phrase\": \"eating breakfast|吃早餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father took out his wallet and gave me ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿出了\", \"phrase\": \"took out|拿出了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father took out his wallet and gave me ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿出\", \"phrase\": \"took out|拿出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father took out his wallet and gave me ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"gave me ten dollars|给了我十美元\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary said that she loved me, but I didn't believe her.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"didn't believe|不相信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Make sure to turn off all the lights before going out.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Make sure to turn off all the lights before going out.\", \"target\": \"lights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灯\", \"phrase\": \"turn off the lights|关灯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would be better if you stayed here a little longer.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a little longer|稍微长一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that money can't buy happiness.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"goes without saying|不言而喻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that money can't buy happiness.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't buy|不能买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that money can't buy happiness.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"购买\", \"phrase\": \"can't buy happiness|不能买到幸福\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there anything you want to add to what I just said?\", \"target\": \"add\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"添加\", \"phrase\": \"add to|添加到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there any chance you'll go to Australia next month?\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个月\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In recent years, science has made remarkable progress.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取得进展\", \"phrase\": \"made progress|取得进展\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case I can't come, I'll give you a call beforehand.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give you a call|给你打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case I can't come, I'll give you a call beforehand.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"give you a call|给你打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he is innocent, it follows that his wife is guilty.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his wife|他的妻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason I'm late, please don't wait for me.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等\", \"phrase\": \"wait for me|等我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I lost my key, I wouldn't be able to lock the door.\", \"target\": \"lock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"锁\", \"phrase\": \"lock the door|锁门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can't do that.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"the only one|唯一的一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can't do that.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't do|不能做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to run a couple of errands. Wanna tag along?\", \"target\": \"couple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"a couple of|一对\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to run a couple of errands. Wanna tag along?\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"tag along|一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to run a couple of errands. Wanna tag along?\", \"target\": \"tag\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"一起去\", \"phrase\": \"tag along|一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to run a couple of errands. Wanna tag along?\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"tag along|一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wouldn't be too surprised if this song became a hit.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"热门歌曲\", \"phrase\": \"became a hit|成为热门歌曲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was caught in a shower and got drenched to the skin.\", \"target\": \"skin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"皮肤\", \"phrase\": \"to the skin|到皮肤\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took him to the most expensive restaurant on campus.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"most expensive|最贵的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took him to the most expensive restaurant on campus.\", \"target\": \"expensive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"昂贵的\", \"phrase\": \"most expensive|最贵的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I now have enough money to buy the car I want.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy the car|买车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I now have enough money to buy the car I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"buy the car I want|我想买我想要的汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I suggest we drink as little as possible to be polite.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽可能少\", \"phrase\": \"as little as possible|尽可能少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't understand why Tom doesn't want to go with us.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to go|想去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't understand why Tom doesn't want to go with us.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go with|和...一起去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am convinced that things will change for the better.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"for the better|为了更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I admit that this may not be the best way of doing it.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best way|最佳方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I admit that this may not be the best way of doing it.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"way of doing it|做事的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"foot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脚\", \"phrase\": \"on foot|步行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took care of the business after his father's death.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"took care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He quickly made friends with the new boy on the block.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new boy|新男孩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He quickly made friends with the new boy on the block.\", \"target\": \"block\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"街区\", \"phrase\": \"on the block|在街区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He quickly accustomed himself to his new surroundings.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new surroundings|新环境\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made use of the opportunity to improve his English.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"made use of|利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made use of the opportunity to improve his English.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"made use of|利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made use of the opportunity to improve his English.\", \"target\": \"opportunity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"make use of the opportunity|利用机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is doing very well considering he lacks experience.\", \"target\": \"considering\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"考虑到\", \"phrase\": \"considering he lacks experience|考虑到他缺乏经验\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had his sister help him paint the wall of his room.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his room|他的房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give me the book back once you've finished reading it.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"give back|还回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't throw away this magazine. I haven't read it yet.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"扔掉\", \"phrase\": \"throw away|扔掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have an extra English dictionary by any chance?\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"by any chance|偶然，或许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you please pull the weeds and water the flowers?\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浇水\", \"phrase\": \"water the flowers|浇花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Blow out all the candles on the birthday cake at once.\", \"target\": \"blow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吹灭\", \"phrase\": \"blow out|吹灭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Blow out all the candles on the birthday cake at once.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吹灭\", \"phrase\": \"blow out|吹灭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As we went around the corner, the lake came into view.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"went around|在...周围走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Apparently, there is nothing that cannot happen today.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot happen|不能发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An argument may be logically sound without being true.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without being|没有是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a couple of drinks, the guy was feeling no pain.\", \"target\": \"couple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"couple of drinks|几杯酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're the one who suggested that we travel together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"travel together|一起旅行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should look after the children from time to time.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看望\", \"phrase\": \"look after|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should look after the children from time to time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"from time to time|不时地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should look after the children from time to time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"from time to time|时不时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to go for a drink or something to eat?\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"something to eat|吃东西\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is learned in the cradle is carried to the tomb.\", \"target\": \"carried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"携带\", \"phrase\": \"carried to the tomb|带到坟墓\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is learned in the cradle is carried to the tomb.\", \"target\": \"carried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"携带\", \"phrase\": \"carried to the tomb|带到坟墓\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We just have to make sure Tom is planning to be here.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"确保\", \"phrase\": \"make sure|确保\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to look into the disappearance of the doctor.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"look into|调查\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have three spare rooms, none of which can be used.\", \"target\": \"none\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"none of which|其中任何一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are looking forward to seeing you and your family.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"期待地\", \"phrase\": \"looking forward to|期待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he has no intention of marrying you.\", \"target\": \"marrying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结婚\", \"phrase\": \"intention of marrying|结婚的意图\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he had been cleaning the house all day.\", \"target\": \"cleaning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打扫\", \"phrase\": \"been cleaning|一直在打扫\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he thought that would probably never happen.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"never happen|永远不会发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom ran out of matches so he couldn't light the fire.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"ran out of|用完\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom ran out of matches so he couldn't light the fire.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"点燃\", \"phrase\": \"light the fire|点燃火\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't like the idea of Mary going out with John.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't like the idea of Mary going out with John.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom cut down the tree that was in front of his house.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought a camera at a store not too far from here.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远\", \"phrase\": \"not too far|不太远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary even always wear the same color clothes.\", \"target\": \"color\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"颜色\", \"phrase\": \"same color|相同颜色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is where I want to live for the rest of my life.\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"剩余\", \"phrase\": \"rest of my life|我余生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They say she and her husband can't agree on anything.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't agree|不同意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher lined the children up in order of height.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顺序\", \"phrase\": \"in order|按顺序\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police will put you behind bars for twenty years.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind bars|监禁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police will put you behind bars for twenty years.\", \"target\": \"bars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"监狱\", \"phrase\": \"behind bars|身陷囹圄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The hallway needs to be wide enough for a wheelchair.\", \"target\": \"wide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"宽的\", \"phrase\": \"wide enough|足够宽的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bus stopped suddenly in the middle of the street.\", \"target\": \"middle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"中间\", \"phrase\": \"middle of the street|街道中间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some chewing gum was stuck to the sole of Tom's shoe.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"粘住\", \"phrase\": \"stuck to|粘在...上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's practicing English so she can get a better job.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better job|更好的工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She will return home next Sunday, that is, the tenth.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next Sunday|下个星期天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was a tall, thin girl with long, soft brown hair.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long hair|长发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was a tall, thin girl with long, soft brown hair.\", \"target\": \"soft\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"柔软的\", \"phrase\": \"soft hair|柔软的头发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She speaks English better than any of her classmates.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"speaks better|说得更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She ran very fast to catch up with the other members.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"追上\", \"phrase\": \"catch up with|追赶上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She lost her way and on top of that it began to rain.\", \"target\": \"top\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之上\", \"phrase\": \"on top of|在...之上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one is working. Everyone's watching the World Cup.\", \"target\": \"watching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"观看\", \"phrase\": \"watching the World Cup|观看世界杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one is working. Everyone's watching the World Cup.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"World Cup|世界杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one is working. Everyone's watching the World Cup.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"World Cup|世界杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My uncle's company launched a new product last month.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个月\", \"phrase\": \"last month|上个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has been in good shape since his operation.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good shape|身体好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has been in good shape since his operation.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since his operation|自从他的手术以来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary is not poor. On the contrary, she is quite rich.\", \"target\": \"contrary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相反地\", \"phrase\": \"on the contrary|与此相反\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary is not poor. On the contrary, she is quite rich.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"quite rich|相当富有\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me read the paper when you have finished with it.\", \"target\": \"finished\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"finished with|与...结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long time since I've had a real vacation.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since I've|自从我以来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's absolutely impossible for me to go on like this.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"go on|继续\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's absolutely impossible for me to go on like this.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"go on like this|像这样继续下去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was so still that you would have heard a pin drop.\", \"target\": \"pin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"别针\", \"phrase\": \"pin drop|落针可闻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was so still that you would have heard a pin drop.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"落下\", \"phrase\": \"pin drop|落针可闻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like Tom will do what we've asked him to do.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"asked him to do|要求他做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is said that his father died in a foreign country.\", \"target\": \"foreign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"外国的\", \"phrase\": \"foreign country|外国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a crisis, you must get in touch with your teacher.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"get in touch with|与...联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you pass this test, you could graduate next month.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个月\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you need my advice, I'd be glad to give it to you.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give it|给它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you have a question, please raise your right hand.\", \"target\": \"raise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"举起\", \"phrase\": \"raise your hand|举手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you have a question, please raise your right hand.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"right hand|右手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you have a question, please raise your right hand.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"right hand|右手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll arrange for someone to pick you up at your home.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接\", \"phrase\": \"pick you up|接你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to try this on. Where are the fitting rooms?\", \"target\": \"fitting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"试穿的\", \"phrase\": \"fitting rooms|试衣间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to try this on. Where are the fitting rooms?\", \"target\": \"rooms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"fitting rooms|试衣间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I worked in a post office during the summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"post\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邮局\", \"phrase\": \"post office|邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I worked in a post office during the summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"post office|邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was the second to last person to hear the bad news.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"second to last|倒数第二个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I shouldn't have eaten the whole bag of potato chips.\", \"target\": \"whole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"whole bag|整袋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I shouldn't have eaten the whole bag of potato chips.\", \"target\": \"bag\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"袋子\", \"phrase\": \"bag of potato chips|一袋薯片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I shouldn't have eaten the whole bag of potato chips.\", \"target\": \"potato\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"土豆\", \"phrase\": \"potato chips|薯片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I shouldn't have eaten the whole bag of potato chips.\", \"target\": \"chips\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"薯片\", \"phrase\": \"potato chips|薯片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must think over the matter before giving my answer.\", \"target\": \"giving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"giving my answer|给出我的答案\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hear you passed the entrance exam. Congratulations!\", \"target\": \"entrance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"入口\", \"phrase\": \"entrance exam|入学考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long did it take you to finish reading that book?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He does nothing but complain from morning till night.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"morning till night|从早到晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He does nothing but complain from morning till night.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"from morning till night|从早到晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning we take the dog for a walk in the park.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take the dog for a walk|带狗去散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning we take the dog for a walk in the park.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"take a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is spoken in many countries around the world.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the world|世界各地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't throw out this magazine. I haven't read it yet.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扔掉\", \"phrase\": \"throw out|扔掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know why spring rolls are called spring rolls?\", \"target\": \"spring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"春天\", \"phrase\": \"spring rolls|春卷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know why spring rolls are called spring rolls?\", \"target\": \"rolls\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卷\", \"phrase\": \"spring rolls|春卷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know why spring rolls are called spring rolls?\", \"target\": \"called\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫做\", \"phrase\": \"are called|被叫做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know why spring rolls are called spring rolls?\", \"target\": \"spring\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"春天\", \"phrase\": \"spring rolls|春卷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know why spring rolls are called spring rolls?\", \"target\": \"rolls\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卷\", \"phrase\": \"spring rolls|春卷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you feel like you can't connect with other people?\", \"target\": \"connect\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"连接\", \"phrase\": \"connect with|与...建立联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cutting a cake into equal pieces is rather difficult.\", \"target\": \"pieces\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"块\", \"phrase\": \"equal pieces|等份\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you wake me up at seven o'clock tomorrow morning?\", \"target\": \"clock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时钟\", \"phrase\": \"o'clock|点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Artificial leather can't compare with the real thing.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't compare|不能比较\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"American kitchens are much bigger than Japanese ones.\", \"target\": \"ones\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"那些\", \"phrase\": \"much bigger than Japanese ones|比日本的厨房大得多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After walking for an hour, we stopped to take a rest.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take a rest|休息一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After she had read the letter, she tore it to pieces.\", \"target\": \"tore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撕碎\", \"phrase\": \"tore it to pieces|撕成碎片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After she had read the letter, she tore it to pieces.\", \"target\": \"pieces\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"碎片\", \"phrase\": \"to pieces|成碎片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stay of execution was ordered at the eleventh hour.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"停留; 暂停\", \"phrase\": \"stay of execution|暂缓执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stay of execution was ordered at the eleventh hour.\", \"target\": \"ordered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"命令\", \"phrase\": \"stay of execution was ordered|执行令被发布\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A stay of execution was ordered at the eleventh hour.\", \"target\": \"hour\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"eleventh hour|最后一刻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A foreign language can't be mastered in a year or so.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't be mastered|不能被掌握\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A few years ago, our room had little furniture in it.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"少量的\", \"phrase\": \"little furniture|少量家具\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should not have lent the money to such a person.\", \"target\": \"lent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借出\", \"phrase\": \"lent the money|借钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to lend him money.\", \"target\": \"lend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借\", \"phrase\": \"lend him money|借钱给他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why is everyone being so nice to me all of a sudden?\", \"target\": \"sudden\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"突然\", \"phrase\": \"all of a sudden|突然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I hear this song, I think of you, and miss you.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"miss you|想你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think I should wear on my date tomorrow?\", \"target\": \"date\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"约会\", \"phrase\": \"on my date|在我的约会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the fact that he is young.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"take into account|考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the fact that he is young.\", \"target\": \"account\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"take into account|考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Unfortunately, I have to get up early every morning.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"every morning|每天早上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sits in front of his computer eight hours a day.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he didn't have it all figured out yet.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"弄清楚\", \"phrase\": \"figured out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has contributed a lot of money to this hospital.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom donates half his salary to his favorite charity.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his salary|他的工资\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could've dealt with the problem in a better way.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better way|更好的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could've dealt with the problem in a better way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"in a better way|以更好的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary admired the scenery as they held hands.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"握住\", \"phrase\": \"held hands|牵手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary admired the scenery as they held hands.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"held hands|牵手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's a lot of trash on the far bank of the river.\", \"target\": \"bank\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"岸\", \"phrase\": \"far bank|远岸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The students are talking about language and culture.\", \"target\": \"talking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"谈论\", \"phrase\": \"talking about|关于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The situation is getting worse and worse day by day.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变得\", \"phrase\": \"getting worse|越来越糟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The situation is getting worse and worse day by day.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更糟\", \"phrase\": \"getting worse|越来越糟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The situation is getting worse and worse day by day.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更糟\", \"phrase\": \"getting worse and worse|越来越糟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The situation is getting worse and worse day by day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"day by day|日复一日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The situation is getting worse and worse day by day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"day by day|日复一日\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ship made slow progress against the strong wind.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强壮的\", \"phrase\": \"strong wind|强风\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ship made slow progress against the strong wind.\", \"target\": \"wind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风\", \"phrase\": \"strong wind|强风\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The party will be held outdoors, weather permitting.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"举行\", \"phrase\": \"be held|举行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The party will be held outdoors, weather permitting.\", \"target\": \"permitting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"weather permitting|如果天气允许\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ice on the lake is too thin to bear your weight.\", \"target\": \"bear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"承受\", \"phrase\": \"bear weight|承受重量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The doctor advised my father to cut down on smoking.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"减少\", \"phrase\": \"cut down on|减少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The camel can go a long time without water and food.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The camel can go a long time without water and food.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without water and food|没有水和食物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bill was passed after a hard fight in the House.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"艰难的\", \"phrase\": \"hard fight|艰苦的战斗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bill was passed after a hard fight in the House.\", \"target\": \"fight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"战斗\", \"phrase\": \"hard fight|艰苦的斗争\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bill was passed after a hard fight in the House.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"House|众议院\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Internet is an invaluable source of information.\", \"target\": \"source\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"来源\", \"phrase\": \"source of information|信息来源\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take your hat off when you enter a house of worship.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take your hat off when you enter a house of worship.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"house of worship|礼拜场所\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since my mother was sick, I stayed home from school.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在家\", \"phrase\": \"stayed home|待在家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She waved her hand until the train was out of sight.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of sight|视线之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She studied abroad in order to brush up her English.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"为了\", \"phrase\": \"in order to|为了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She studied abroad in order to brush up her English.\", \"target\": \"brush\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提高\", \"phrase\": \"brush up|提高\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She drew a circle on a piece of paper with a pencil.\", \"target\": \"piece\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一块\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|纸的一块\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She drew a circle on a piece of paper with a pencil.\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"piece of paper|纸张\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Quite by chance, I met my old friend at the airport.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old friend|老朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People should be the masters of their own destinies.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own destinies|自己的命运\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Parents teach their children that it's wrong to lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"to lie|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My hands were shaking too much to thread the needle.\", \"target\": \"thread\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿线\", \"phrase\": \"thread the needle|穿针引线\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has already given up smoking and drinking.\", \"target\": \"given\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给予\", \"phrase\": \"given up|放弃\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has already given up smoking and drinking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"戒烟\", \"phrase\": \"given up smoking|戒烟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father has already given up smoking and drinking.\", \"target\": \"drinking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝酒\", \"phrase\": \"given up smoking and drinking|放弃吸烟和饮酒\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Maybe I'll just give up soon and take a nap instead.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"take a nap|打个盹\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Maybe I'll just give up soon and take a nap instead.\", \"target\": \"instead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"代替\", \"phrase\": \"take a nap instead|打个盹代替\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't really sick. She's only pretending to be.\", \"target\": \"pretending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"pretending to be|假装\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"London, where I live, used to be famous for its fog.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"used to be|曾经是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last night, I went to bed without brushing my teeth.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without brushing my teeth|不刷牙\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last night, I went to bed without brushing my teeth.\", \"target\": \"brushing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"VBG\", \"zh\": \"刷\", \"phrase\": \"brushing my teeth|刷我的牙齿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes closed until I tell you to open them.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"eyes closed|闭上眼睛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes closed until I tell you to open them.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open them|睁开它们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is a leader in the world's high-tech industry.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高\", \"phrase\": \"high-tech|高科技\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is a leader in the world's high-tech industry.\", \"target\": \"tech\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"技术\", \"phrase\": \"high-tech|高科技\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's the middle of the night. Why aren't you asleep?\", \"target\": \"middle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"中间\", \"phrase\": \"middle of the night|午夜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to chill white wine before you serve it.\", \"target\": \"serve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"上菜\", \"phrase\": \"serve it|上菜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's already eleven. It's high time you were in bed.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high time|高时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a two-hour drive from here to my uncle's house.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开车\", \"phrase\": \"two-hour drive|两小时的车程\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is not easy to catch a hare with your bare hands.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"catch a hare|抓住兔子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is not easy to catch a hare with your bare hands.\", \"target\": \"bare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"裸的\", \"phrase\": \"bare hands|赤手空拳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is not easy to catch a hare with your bare hands.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"bare hands|赤手空拳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case of an emergency, get in touch with my agent.\", \"target\": \"touch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"get in touch with|联系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you need a dictionary, I can lend you my old one.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old one|旧的那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you need a dictionary, I can lend you my old one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"old one|旧的那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it is worth doing at all, it is worth doing well.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"worth doing|值得做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it is worth doing at all, it is worth doing well.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"worth doing|值得做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it is worth doing at all, it is worth doing well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好地\", \"phrase\": \"doing well|做得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If by any chance I'm late, please don't wait for me.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等\", \"phrase\": \"wait for|等候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been wanting to see that movie for a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm really sorry. I seem to have lost your umbrella.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"have lost|丢失\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to do shopping on Fifth Avenue in New York.\", \"target\": \"fifth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第五的\", \"phrase\": \"Fifth Avenue|第五大道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wrote a letter asking him to return a bit earlier.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a bit earlier|稍微早一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought you'd be full after eating that big steak.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big steak|大牛排\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you should do that before you go home today.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think we should be able to go wherever we want to.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go wherever|无论去哪里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think we should be able to go wherever we want to.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think the time is right to introduce this product.\", \"target\": \"introduce\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"介绍\", \"phrase\": \"introduce this product|介绍这个产品\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I suspect that they water down the beer in that pub.\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"稀释\", \"phrase\": \"water down|冲淡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I plan to spend the New Year's holiday in Australia.\", \"target\": \"spend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"度过\", \"phrase\": \"spend the holiday|度过假期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I plan to spend the New Year's holiday in Australia.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"New Year's|新年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I plan to spend the New Year's holiday in Australia.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"New Year|新年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't take the place of her as an English teacher.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"代替\", \"phrase\": \"take the place of|代替...的位置\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't take the place of her as an English teacher.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"位置\", \"phrase\": \"take the place of|代替...的位置\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long did you think the picnic was going to last?\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"going to last|将要持续\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long did you think the picnic was going to last?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"持续\", \"phrase\": \"going to last|将持续\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did Tom talk Mary into babysitting his children?\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说服\", \"phrase\": \"talk into|说服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did Tom talk Mary into babysitting his children?\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his children|他的孩子们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did Tom talk Mary into babysitting his children?\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"his children|他的孩子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was found lying unconscious on the kitchen floor.\", \"target\": \"floor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地板\", \"phrase\": \"kitchen floor|厨房地板\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He must have said so without giving it much thought.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without giving it much thought|没有仔细考虑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He must have said so without giving it much thought.\", \"target\": \"giving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"giving it much thought|考虑周全\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He must have said so without giving it much thought.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"much thought|考虑很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left the house without so much as saying goodbye.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without so much as|没有...就\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left the house without so much as saying goodbye.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"那么\", \"phrase\": \"so much as|如此之多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left the house without so much as saying goodbye.\", \"target\": \"saying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"saying goodbye|告别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a wife and two young children to provide for.\", \"target\": \"young\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年轻的\", \"phrase\": \"young children|孩子们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a wife and two young children to provide for.\", \"target\": \"provide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提供\", \"phrase\": \"provide for|供养\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody except Tom knew he didn't need to do that.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except Tom|除了汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't translate English into Japanese word for word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词\", \"phrase\": \"word for word|逐字逐句\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't translate English into Japanese word for word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词\", \"phrase\": \"word for word|逐字逐句\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know which deity this temple is dedicated to?\", \"target\": \"dedicated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"奉献\", \"phrase\": \"dedicated to|献给\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you lend me your bicycle for a couple of days?\", \"target\": \"couple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"couple of days|几天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Better be the head of a cat than the tail of a lion.\", \"target\": \"tail\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尾巴\", \"phrase\": \"tail of a lion|狮子的尾巴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be sure to fill out the registration form in person.\", \"target\": \"fill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"填写\", \"phrase\": \"fill out|填写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be sure to fill out the registration form in person.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"填写\", \"phrase\": \"fill out|填写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be sure to fill out the registration form in person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"in person|亲自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At last, she gave in to him and told him the secret.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让步\", \"phrase\": \"gave in|让步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of a sudden, three dogs appeared in front of us.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out at the inn where they were staying.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"broke out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A caged cricket eats just as much as a free cricket.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"那么\", \"phrase\": \"as much as|和...一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A beautiful woman was seated one row in front of me.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"one row|一行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A beautiful woman was seated one row in front of me.\", \"target\": \"row\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"行\", \"phrase\": \"one row|一行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A beautiful woman was seated one row in front of me.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're the one who suggested that we sing together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"sing together|一起唱歌\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must look over the contract before you sign it.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"look over|检查\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to study hard to catch up with your class.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赶上\", \"phrase\": \"catch up|赶上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to study hard to catch up with your class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"catch up with your class|赶上你的班级\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't buy this medicine without a prescription.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without a prescription|没有处方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are working too hard. Take it easy for a while.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are working too hard. Take it easy for a while.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易的\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With her help, my French improved little by little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点点\", \"phrase\": \"little by little|一点一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With her help, my French improved little by little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点点\", \"phrase\": \"little by little|一点一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whether the medicine will work or not is uncertain.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起作用\", \"phrase\": \"work or not|起作用或不起作用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When was the last time that you watered the garden?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last time|最后一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When was the last time that you watered the garden?\", \"target\": \"watered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浇水\", \"phrase\": \"watered the garden|浇灌花园\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I entered the room, she was playing the piano.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在弹奏\", \"phrase\": \"playing the piano|弹钢琴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We should've taken the schedule into consideration.\", \"target\": \"consideration\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"考虑\", \"phrase\": \"into consideration|考虑在内\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We all wondered why she had dumped such a nice man.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"nice man|好人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Water is liquid. When it freezes, it becomes solid.\", \"target\": \"becomes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"becomes solid|变成固体\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visiting all the tourist sights really wore me out.\", \"target\": \"wore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使疲惫\", \"phrase\": \"wore me out|使我疲惫\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visiting all the tourist sights really wore me out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"精疲力尽\", \"phrase\": \"wore me out|累坏了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that I shouldn't go out alone at night.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that I shouldn't go out alone at night.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that I shouldn't go out alone at night.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"go out alone|独自外出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he didn't want to waste time arguing.\", \"target\": \"waste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he didn't want to waste time arguing.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he didn't want to waste time arguing.\", \"target\": \"arguing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"争论\", \"phrase\": \"waste time arguing|浪费时间争论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows someone who can teach us French.\", \"target\": \"teach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"教\", \"phrase\": \"teach us French|教我们法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows that I want to leave as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows that I want to leave as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is from Australia and Mary is from New Zealand.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"New Zealand|新西兰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom carefully wiped his fingerprints off the knife.\", \"target\": \"wiped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"擦\", \"phrase\": \"wiped off|擦掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I have a lot more in common than I thought.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I have a lot more in common than I thought.\", \"target\": \"common\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"共同的\", \"phrase\": \"in common|共同点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This company is listed on the Paris stock exchange.\", \"target\": \"stock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"股票\", \"phrase\": \"stock exchange|证券交易所\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This company is listed on the Paris stock exchange.\", \"target\": \"exchange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交易所\", \"phrase\": \"stock exchange|股票交易所\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They set fire to their neighbor's house in revenge.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放火\", \"phrase\": \"set fire to|纵火\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They didn't even know how to write their own names.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own names|自己的名字\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no need for you to prepare a formal speech.\", \"target\": \"formal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"正式的\", \"phrase\": \"formal speech|正式演讲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There used to be a big cherry tree behind my house.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind my house|在我房子后面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a castle in the background of the picture.\", \"target\": \"background\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"背景\", \"phrase\": \"in the background|在背景中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There has been no rain here for the past two weeks.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"过去的\", \"phrase\": \"past two weeks|过去两周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The truth is that nothing is totally true or false.\", \"target\": \"totally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全地\", \"phrase\": \"totally true|完全真实\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The tip of the spear was dipped in a deadly poison.\", \"target\": \"deadly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"致命的\", \"phrase\": \"deadly poison|致命的毒药\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher granted me permission to go home early.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police assembled a lot of evidence against him.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The physician prescribed his patient some medicine.\", \"target\": \"prescribed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开了药\", \"phrase\": \"prescribed his patient some medicine|开了他的病人一些药\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The opposite sides of a parallelogram are parallel.\", \"target\": \"parallel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"平行的\", \"phrase\": \"parallel sides|平行边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old man loaded his mule with bags full of sand.\", \"target\": \"bags\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"袋子\", \"phrase\": \"bags full of sand|装满沙子的袋子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old man loaded his mule with bags full of sand.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"满的\", \"phrase\": \"full of sand|装满沙子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Cold War ended when the Soviet Union collapsed.\", \"target\": \"union\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"联盟\", \"phrase\": \"Soviet Union|苏联\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Amazon is fed by a large number of tributaries.\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"large number|大量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That child may have been kidnapped on his way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"way home|回家路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That child may have been kidnapped on his way home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"way home|回家路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop getting yourself worked up over little things.\", \"target\": \"worked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"激动\", \"phrase\": \"worked up|激动\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop getting yourself worked up over little things.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"little things|小事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop getting yourself worked up over little things.\", \"target\": \"worked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"激动\", \"phrase\": \"worked up|激动\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop getting yourself worked up over little things.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"little things|小事\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Staying up late at night is very bad for your skin.\", \"target\": \"staying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"熬夜\", \"phrase\": \"staying up late|熬夜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wrote him a long letter, but he didn't read it.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long letter|长信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was at a loss for words to express her feeling.\", \"target\": \"loss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"损失\", \"phrase\": \"at a loss|不知所措\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She twisted her ankle while she was doing exercise.\", \"target\": \"twisted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扭伤\", \"phrase\": \"twisted her ankle|扭伤了脚踝\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She can sing better than anybody else in her class.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"别的\", \"phrase\": \"better than else|比...更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She can sing better than anybody else in her class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"in her class|在她的班级里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Quite a lot of friends and acquaintances have come.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"President Lincoln was what we call a self-made man.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"称呼\", \"phrase\": \"call a self-made man|称某人为自力更生的人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"President Lincoln was what we call a self-made man.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"past participle\", \"zh\": \"创造的\", \"phrase\": \"self-made|自给自足\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Possibly the factory will be closed down next week.\", \"target\": \"closed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"VBN\", \"zh\": \"关闭\", \"phrase\": \"closed down|关闭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Possibly the factory will be closed down next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next week|下周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please wait for me at the entrance of the building.\", \"target\": \"entrance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"入口\", \"phrase\": \"entrance of the building|建筑物入口\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mercury is the smallest planet in our solar system.\", \"target\": \"solar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"太阳系的\", \"phrase\": \"solar system|太阳系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mercury is the smallest planet in our solar system.\", \"target\": \"system\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"系统\", \"phrase\": \"solar system|太阳系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let go of my arm! I can't stand people touching me.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放开\", \"phrase\": \"let go of|放开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let go of my arm! I can't stand people touching me.\", \"target\": \"touching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"触摸\", \"phrase\": \"touching me|触摸我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long time since we last saw each other.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since we last saw each other|自从我们上次见面以来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long time since we last saw each other.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上次\", \"phrase\": \"last saw|上次看见\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It will be snowing when we arrive at Shiga Heights.\", \"target\": \"heights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"高度\", \"phrase\": \"Shiga Heights|志贺高原\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took a long time to take in what she was saying.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"take in|理解\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't anything like as cold as it was yesterday.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like as|像...一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is impossible to master English in a short time.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"short time|短时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is this the first time that you've seen this movie?\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次的\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it true that Tom wants to paint his house green?\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his house|他的房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll only buy the car if they fix the brakes first.\", \"target\": \"fix\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"fix the brakes|修理刹车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll only buy the car if they fix the brakes first.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"first|首先\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to try out this new model before I buy it.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"try out|尝试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to ask Tom how long he had lived in India.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"how long|多久\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a boat that will take me far away from here.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take me|带我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a boat that will take me far away from here.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"far away|遥远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought I told you to stay away from my computer.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"stay away|远离\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought I told you to stay away from my computer.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"stay away|远离\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like rugby, but not as much as I like basketball.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like basketball|喜欢篮球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a video cassette recorder cheap at that shop.\", \"target\": \"cheap\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"便宜的\", \"phrase\": \"cheap at that shop|在那个商店便宜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I go to the office by bicycle except on rainy days.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except on rainy days|除了在下雨天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I find it much easier to speak French than English.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speak French|说法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't use taxis unless it's absolutely necessary.\", \"target\": \"absolutely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"绝对地\", \"phrase\": \"absolutely necessary|绝对必要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that Tom has any teaching experience.\", \"target\": \"teaching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教学\", \"phrase\": \"teaching experience|教学经验\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't prevent Tom from eating all the cookies.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating all the cookies|吃光所有的饼干\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long has it been since you saw your girlfriend?\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since you|自从你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's getting along well with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相处\", \"phrase\": \"getting along|相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's getting along well with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"along\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"和...相处\", \"phrase\": \"getting along well|相处得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's getting along well with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"getting along well|相处得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said he did not enter the room, which was a lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"a lie|谎言\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He postponed leaving for Hokkaido until next month.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows German and French, not to mention English.\", \"target\": \"mention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提及\", \"phrase\": \"not to mention|不必说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has no right to interfere in our family affairs.\", \"target\": \"interfere\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"干涉\", \"phrase\": \"interfere in|干涉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has no right to interfere in our family affairs.\", \"target\": \"family\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家庭\", \"phrase\": \"family affairs|家庭事务\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He divided one million dollars among his five sons.\", \"target\": \"among\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之中\", \"phrase\": \"among his five sons|在他五个儿子之中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone ought to be the master of his own destiny.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his own destiny|他自己的命运\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone ought to be the master of his own destiny.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own destiny|命运\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone except Tom knew he didn't need to do that.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except Tom|除了汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Driving on a slippery road can lead to a car wreck.\", \"target\": \"lead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"lead to|导致\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't speak unless you have something worth saying.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有价值的\", \"phrase\": \"worth saying|值得说的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't speak unless you have something worth saying.\", \"target\": \"saying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"something worth saying|有价值的话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because his salary is low, he can't buy that house.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't buy|不能买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as he sat down, he picked up the telephone.\", \"target\": \"picked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿起\", \"phrase\": \"picked up|拿起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of us would like to get rid of nuclear weapons.\", \"target\": \"rid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摆脱\", \"phrase\": \"get rid of|摆脱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Have you seen my cell phone?\\\" \\\"It's on the table.\\\"\", \"target\": \"cell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手机\", \"phrase\": \"cell phone|手机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Have you seen my cell phone?\\\" \\\"It's on the table.\\\"\", \"target\": \"table\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"桌子\", \"phrase\": \"on the table|在桌子上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're working too hard. Take it easy for a while.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息一下\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're working too hard. Take it easy for a while.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易的\", \"phrase\": \"take it easy|放松点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better go to see your family doctor at once.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see your family doctor|看你的家庭医生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't talk back to your parents like that.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"顶撞\", \"phrase\": \"talk back|顶嘴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't talk back to your parents like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"talk like that|那样说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should read a lot of books while you're young.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should read a lot of books while you're young.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You look the way your father did thirty years ago.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"thirty years ago|三十年前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You don't seem to be as afraid as Tom seems to be.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"seems to be|似乎是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What would you do if you had ten thousand dollars?\", \"target\": \"thousand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"千\", \"phrase\": \"ten thousand|一万\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We woke up very early in order to see the sunrise.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"为了\", \"phrase\": \"in order to|为了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We didn't know how to do it, so we asked for help.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"asked for|请求\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are sorry we are unable to accept your request.\", \"target\": \"accept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"accept your request|接受你的请求\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wouldn't dare show his face around here again.\", \"target\": \"face\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸\", \"phrase\": \"show face|露面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wouldn't dare show his face around here again.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|这里周围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the first to arrive and the last to leave.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"the last to leave|最后离开的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the first to arrive and the last to leave.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"to leave|离开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants a computer small enough to easily carry.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"small enough|足够小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants a computer small enough to easily carry.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"small enough|足够小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants a computer small enough to easily carry.\", \"target\": \"easily\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"容易地\", \"phrase\": \"easily carry|容易携带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants a computer small enough to easily carry.\", \"target\": \"carry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"携带\", \"phrase\": \"easily carry|容易携带\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he won't come to school tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come to school|来上学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me he'd give me that book if I wanted it.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give me|给我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me he'd give me that book if I wanted it.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wanted it|想要它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sat on that park bench for nearly three hours.\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公园\", \"phrase\": \"park bench|公园长椅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had a hunch that Mary was seeing someone else.\", \"target\": \"seeing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"seeing someone|和某人在一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had a hunch that Mary was seeing someone else.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"别的\", \"phrase\": \"seeing someone else|和别人在一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't go out because he has a lot of homework.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary are studying together in the library.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"together in the library|在图书馆一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is covered with snow all year round.\", \"target\": \"covered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"覆盖\", \"phrase\": \"covered with snow|被雪覆盖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is covered with snow all year round.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一年四季\", \"phrase\": \"all year round|一年四季\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They nominated Calvin Coolidge for vice president.\", \"target\": \"vice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"副总统\", \"phrase\": \"vice president|副总统\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was no one in the room besides Tom and Mary.\", \"target\": \"besides\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"besides Tom and Mary|除了汤姆和玛丽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The plane was three hours late due to bad weather.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"bad weather|坏天气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy who lives next door often comes home late.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy who lives next door often comes home late.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy who lives next door often comes home late.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The boy who lives next door often comes home late.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"next door|隔壁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby was in a deep sleep in his mother's arms.\", \"target\": \"arms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"胳膊\", \"phrase\": \"mother's arms|母亲的怀抱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She waved at me before she got on board the plane.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"上\", \"phrase\": \"got on board|登机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She waved at me before she got on board the plane.\", \"target\": \"board\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"登上\", \"phrase\": \"on board|登船\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wants to move out and find a place of her own.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"place of her own|自己的地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wants to move out and find a place of her own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"of her own|属于她自己的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She speaks clearly enough to be easily understood.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"clearly enough|清楚地足够\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She speaks clearly enough to be easily understood.\", \"target\": \"easily\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"容易地\", \"phrase\": \"easily understood|容易理解\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She had scarcely finished speaking when he cut in.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打断\", \"phrase\": \"cut in|打断\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She always lets her children do what they want to.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Scientists are working hard to put an end to AIDS.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"put an end to|结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Scientists are working hard to put an end to AIDS.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"put an end to|结束\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People are more educated now than they used to be.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"used to|习惯于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife buys vegetables from a supermarket nearby.\", \"target\": \"nearby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"附近\", \"phrase\": \"nearby|附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My sister has made remarkable progress in English.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"made progress|取得进展\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My business has at last gotten on the right track.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确的\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|在正轨上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My business has at last gotten on the right track.\", \"target\": \"track\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轨道\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|走上正轨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My business has at last gotten on the right track.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确的\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|在正轨上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My business has at last gotten on the right track.\", \"target\": \"track\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"轨道\", \"phrase\": \"on the right track|走上正轨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary placed her baby in a car seat for the flight.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"car seat|汽车座椅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary placed her baby in a car seat for the flight.\", \"target\": \"seat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"座位\", \"phrase\": \"car seat|汽车座椅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Jupiter is the largest planet in the Solar System.\", \"target\": \"solar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"太阳系的\", \"phrase\": \"Solar System|太阳系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Jupiter is the largest planet in the Solar System.\", \"target\": \"system\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"系统\", \"phrase\": \"Solar System|太阳系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me a thousand yen to get my bicycle fixed.\", \"target\": \"fixed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"get fixed|修理好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it all right to take pictures in this building?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿, 拍摄\", \"phrase\": \"take pictures|拍照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you're not listening to the radio, turn it off.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关掉\", \"phrase\": \"turn it off|关掉它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you really want to know, why don't you ask Tom?\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"ask Tom|问汤姆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you do it this way, you can save several hours.\", \"target\": \"save\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"节省\", \"phrase\": \"save hours|节省时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you do it this way, you can save several hours.\", \"target\": \"several\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"几个\", \"phrase\": \"several hours|几个小时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't make it, call us as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"make it|做到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't make it, call us as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call us|给我们打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't make it, call us as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you can't make it, call us as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been coming to work one train earlier lately.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"train earlier|更早的火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not talking to you. I'm talking to the monkey.\", \"target\": \"talking\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"talking to the monkey|和猴子说话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm fixing the radio which I found on my way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that he would pass the exam.\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"通过\", \"phrase\": \"pass the exam|通过考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that he would keep his word.\", \"target\": \"granted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为…理所当然\", \"phrase\": \"took it for granted|认为…理所当然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that he would keep his word.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遵守\", \"phrase\": \"keep his word|信守承诺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that he would keep his word.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"keep his word|信守承诺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that he would keep his word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"keep his word|信守承诺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told her not to let go of the rope, but she did.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let go|放开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told her not to let go of the rope, but she did.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放开\", \"phrase\": \"let go of|放开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told Tom that I thought that it was a good idea.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good idea|好主意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I shot the horse because it had trouble breathing.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"trouble breathing|呼吸困难\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope he'll be able to come! I'd like to see him.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"would like|想\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope he'll be able to come! I'd like to see him.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see him|看他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to take the book back to the library today.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"take back|拿回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to take the book back to the library today.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"take back|取回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to get to sleep! I've got classes tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"got to|不得不\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a friend whose father is a famous novelist.\", \"target\": \"famous\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"著名的\", \"phrase\": \"famous novelist|著名的作家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hate when other people make me wait a long time.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"make me wait|让我等待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hate when other people make me wait a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hate when other people make me wait a long time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"a long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had no idea it would put you to so much trouble.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"put you to trouble|给你添麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had no idea it would put you to so much trouble.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"那么\", \"phrase\": \"so much trouble|如此多的麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had no idea it would put you to so much trouble.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"so much trouble|如此多的麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I enjoyed talking with you this evening very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"very much|非常多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't trust Tom and he didn't trust me, either.\", \"target\": \"trust\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"信任\", \"phrase\": \"didn't trust|不信任\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't trust Tom and he didn't trust me, either.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"didn't trust...either|不信任...也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I cannot help thinking that my son is still alive.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still alive|仍然活着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am grateful to you for inviting me to the party.\", \"target\": \"inviting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"邀请\", \"phrase\": \"inviting me to the party|邀请我参加聚会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does the airport bus take to the airport?\", \"target\": \"airport\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机场\", \"phrase\": \"airport bus|机场巴士\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does the airport bus take to the airport?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take to|花费到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does the airport bus take to the airport?\", \"target\": \"airport\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机场\", \"phrase\": \"airport bus|机场巴士\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get to the train station?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get to the train station?\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wore a mask so that no one could recognize him.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"no one|没有人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He went to see his grandfather off at the station.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"送别\", \"phrase\": \"see off|送别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He studies English, but he's also studying German.\", \"target\": \"also\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"also studying|也在学习\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He placed emphasis on the importance of education.\", \"target\": \"emphasis\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"强调\", \"phrase\": \"placed emphasis on|强调...的重要性\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is busy preparing for the entrance examination.\", \"target\": \"entrance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"入口\", \"phrase\": \"entrance examination|入学考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He failed in his attempt to swim across the river.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"swim across|游泳穿过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He drove the car, listening to music on the radio.\", \"target\": \"listening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听着\", \"phrase\": \"listening to music|听音乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though he has a lot of money, he's not happy.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the lights on when you leave the room.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave the room|离开房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the lights on when you leave the room.\", \"target\": \"lights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灯\", \"phrase\": \"lights on|灯开着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the lights on when you leave the room.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave the room|离开房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Compared with her sister, she isn't very punctual.\", \"target\": \"compared\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"与...相比\", \"phrase\": \"compared with|与...相比\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you give me a ride to the office on Wednesday?\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"搭车\", \"phrase\": \"give me a ride|给我搭车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As long as we love each other, we'll be all right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"对的\", \"phrase\": \"all right|一切都好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Anything you say can be used against you in court.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被利用\", \"phrase\": \"be used against|被用来反对\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although he was exhausted, he had to keep working.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep working|继续工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although I was tired, I did what I was able to do.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够的\", \"phrase\": \"able to do|能够做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Air quality has deteriorated these past few years.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"过去\", \"phrase\": \"past few years|过去几年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new branch will be opened in Chicago next month.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个月\", \"phrase\": \"next month|下个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A green carpet will not go with this blue curtain.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"搭配\", \"phrase\": \"go with|与...搭配\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A boy of seventeen is often as tall as his father.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his father|他父亲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bird in the hand is better than two in the bush.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"in the hand|在手中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bird in the hand is better than two in the bush.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better than|比...更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bird in the hand is better than two in the bush.\", \"target\": \"bush\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灌木丛\", \"phrase\": \"in the bush|在灌木丛中\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're still too young to get a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶员\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾驶执照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're still too young to get a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶员\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾驶执照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should practice playing the violin every day.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"演奏\", \"phrase\": \"playing the violin|演奏小提琴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may take either the big box or the small one.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"或者\", \"phrase\": \"either...or...|或者...或者...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may take either the big box or the small one.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big box|大盒子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may take either the big box or the small one.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"small one|小盒子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may take either the big box or the small one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"small one|小一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to do as you please with your money.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"as you please|请随意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are allowed to use the hotel's swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use the hotel's swimming pool|使用酒店的游泳池\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are allowed to use the hotel's swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"swimming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"swimming pool|游泳池\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are allowed to use the hotel's swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"pool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游泳池\", \"phrase\": \"swimming pool|游泳池\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why on earth did you sell your newly-built house?\", \"target\": \"newly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"新近\", \"phrase\": \"newly-built|新建造的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why on earth did you sell your newly-built house?\", \"target\": \"built\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新建的\", \"phrase\": \"newly-built|新建的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are bound to each other by a close friendship.\", \"target\": \"bound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"束缚\", \"phrase\": \"be bound to|注定\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are bound to each other by a close friendship.\", \"target\": \"close\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"亲密的\", \"phrase\": \"close friendship|亲密的朋友关系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to catch up with Mary, but he couldn't.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"追上\", \"phrase\": \"catch up with|追赶上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thinks that Mary may have an eating disorder.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating disorder|饮食失调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said it was cold in Boston this time of year.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"time of year|一年中的时候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been under a great deal of strain lately.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"巨大的\", \"phrase\": \"great deal|很大的数量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been under a great deal of strain lately.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大量的; 许多\", \"phrase\": \"a great deal|大量的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been under a great deal of strain lately.\", \"target\": \"strain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"压力\", \"phrase\": \"a great deal of strain|巨大的压力\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom encouraged Mary to learn how to speak French.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"speak French|说法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't pay much attention to how he dresses.\", \"target\": \"attention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"注意力\", \"phrase\": \"pay attention|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary went to the best restaurant in town.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best restaurant|最好的餐厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This piano has probably not been tuned for years.\", \"target\": \"tuned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"调音\", \"phrase\": \"been tuned|已调音\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the room where the author killed himself.\", \"target\": \"killed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"killed himself|自杀\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This flower is the most beautiful of all flowers.\", \"target\": \"flower\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"flower|花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This flower is the most beautiful of all flowers.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"most beautiful|最美丽的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This flower is the most beautiful of all flowers.\", \"target\": \"beautiful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美丽的\", \"phrase\": \"most beautiful|最美丽的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This flower is the most beautiful of all flowers.\", \"target\": \"flowers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"flowers|花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This conference is very important. Don't miss it.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"miss it|错过它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They will tear down the old building in two days.\", \"target\": \"tear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拆除\", \"phrase\": \"tear down|拆除\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They will tear down the old building in two days.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old building|旧建筑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They came up with a plan after a long discussion.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"long discussion|长时间的讨论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They came up with a plan after a long discussion.\", \"target\": \"discussion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"讨论\", \"phrase\": \"long discussion|长时间的讨论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The whole neighborhood was surprised at the news.\", \"target\": \"whole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"whole neighborhood|整个街区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The weather was so cold that the lake froze over.\", \"target\": \"froze\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"冻结\", \"phrase\": \"froze over|冻结\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house stood out because of its unusual shape.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"突出\", \"phrase\": \"stood out|突出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The explosion may have been caused by a gas leak.\", \"target\": \"gas\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"气体\", \"phrase\": \"gas leak|气体泄漏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The explosion may have been caused by a gas leak.\", \"target\": \"leak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"泄漏\", \"phrase\": \"gas leak|气体泄漏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's the computer he used to write the article.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"used to|习惯于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's the computer he used to write the article.\", \"target\": \"write\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"write the article|写文章\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Strawberries sell for a high price in the winter.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high price|高价\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wears high heels to make herself look taller.\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high heels|高跟鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wears high heels to make herself look taller.\", \"target\": \"heels\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"高跟鞋\", \"phrase\": \"high heels|高跟鞋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wears high heels to make herself look taller.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"make herself look|使自己看起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wears high heels to make herself look taller.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"look taller|显得更高\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was in trouble because she lost her passport.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"lost her passport|丢失了护照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"paint\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"油漆\", \"phrase\": \"paint the house|粉刷房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gives me a nasty look every time she sees me.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"看了一眼\", \"phrase\": \"nasty look|难看的表情\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gives me a nasty look every time she sees me.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每次\", \"phrase\": \"every time|每次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gives me a nasty look every time she sees me.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"every time|每次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She followed him home to find out where he lived.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"到家\", \"phrase\": \"followed him home|跟随他回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She followed him home to find out where he lived.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"find out|查明\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She asked him if he was a student at this school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"at school|在学校\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the light before you go to sleep.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please let me pick up your sister at the station.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"pick up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Perseverance, as you know, is the key to success.\", \"target\": \"key\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钥匙\", \"phrase\": \"key to success|成功的关键\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once upon a time, there was a beautiful princess.\", \"target\": \"upon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之上\", \"phrase\": \"once upon a time|很久以前\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter what happens, I'm not changing my mind.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"No matter|无论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My train left at 7 and arrived in New York at 10.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"proper noun\", \"zh\": \"纽约\", \"phrase\": \"New York|纽约\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father will come home at the end of this week.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"come home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father will come home at the end of this week.\", \"target\": \"end\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"end of the week|周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Man is the only animal that can make use of fire.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"make use of|利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would've been better if you'd stayed with Tom.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would've been|将会是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me half an hour to work out this problem.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"work out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me half an hour to work out this problem.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"work out|解决\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you buy me an ice cream, I'll give you a kiss.\", \"target\": \"cream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奶油\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If possible, I'd like to travel around the world.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around the world|环游世界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I'm late. I couldn't find the bus stop.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"bus stop|公交车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm grateful to you for inviting me to the party.\", \"target\": \"inviting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"邀请\", \"phrase\": \"inviting me to the party|邀请我参加聚会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm fixing the radio that I found on my way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way home|回家的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will never forget the day when I first met him.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first met|初次见面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a boat that'll take me far away from here.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take me|带我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a boat that'll take me far away from here.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"far away|遥远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told Tom I'd be willing to loan him some money.\", \"target\": \"loan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借贷\", \"phrase\": \"loan him money|借钱给他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we were going to do this together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"together|一起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I talked to him on the telephone yesterday night.\", \"target\": \"telephone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"on the telephone|在电话里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I received a letter written in English yesterday.\", \"target\": \"written\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"past participle\", \"zh\": \"写成的\", \"phrase\": \"written in English|用英语写的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really like him, but not his circle of friends.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his circle of friends|他的朋友圈\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really like him, but not his circle of friends.\", \"target\": \"circle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"圈子\", \"phrase\": \"circle of friends|朋友圈\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really like him, but not his circle of friends.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"circle of friends|朋友圈\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran as fast as I could, but I missed the train.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快地\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as|尽可能快地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran as fast as I could, but I missed the train.\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"missed the train|错过火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you. I need to see you. Could I come over?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能\", \"phrase\": \"could come|能来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you. I need to see you. Could I come over?\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"come over|过来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just felt like hearing the sound of your voice.\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"声音\", \"phrase\": \"sound of your voice|你的声音\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope to retire from work when I'm 60 years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"years old|岁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to write a letter. Do you have some paper?\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"some paper|一些纸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to write a letter. Do you have some paper?\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"some paper|一些纸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found the secret compartment quite by accident.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"意外\", \"phrase\": \"by accident|偶然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think this rain will let up anytime soon.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"let up|停止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think Tom will go to Boston next weekend.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next weekend|下个周末\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I admit this may not be the best way of doing it.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"best way|最佳方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much money do you have hidden under your bed?\", \"target\": \"hidden\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"隐藏的\", \"phrase\": \"hidden under|在...下面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His parents are saving for his college education.\", \"target\": \"college\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大学\", \"phrase\": \"college education|高等教育\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said he did not know the man, which was a lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"a lie|谎言\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He returned home for the first time in ten years.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He once knew her, but they are no longer friends.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不再\", \"phrase\": \"no longer|不再\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is regarded as the best doctor in the village.\", \"target\": \"regarded\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被认为是\", \"phrase\": \"be regarded as|被认为是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is constantly finding fault with other people.\", \"target\": \"finding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"finding fault|挑毛病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is constantly finding fault with other people.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"缺点\", \"phrase\": \"finding fault with|挑剔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He graduated from Harvard University with honors.\", \"target\": \"honors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"荣誉\", \"phrase\": \"with honors|以优异的成绩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He failed the exam, but he doesn't care too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't know how to write a letter in English.\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"write a letter|写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He could not come because of his serious illness.\", \"target\": \"serious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"严重的\", \"phrase\": \"serious illness|严重的疾病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He cannot afford to buy a car, much less a house.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"afford to buy|负担得起买\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He cannot afford to buy a car, much less a house.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更不用说\", \"phrase\": \"much less|更不用说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He cannot afford to buy a car, much less a house.\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更不用说\", \"phrase\": \"much less|更不用说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He cannot afford to buy a car, much less a house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"much less a house|更不用说房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father ran short of money and had to borrow some.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短缺\", \"phrase\": \"ran short of|资金短缺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father ran short of money and had to borrow some.\", \"target\": \"borrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借\", \"phrase\": \"borrow some|借一些\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone inside the building felt the earthquake.\", \"target\": \"inside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...里面\", \"phrase\": \"inside the building|在建筑物里面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even when I was a child, I was able to swim well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"swim well|游得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't pay any attention to what your father says.\", \"target\": \"attention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"注意力\", \"phrase\": \"pay attention|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have something that you want to say to me?\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to say|想要说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you check all the items on the shopping list?\", \"target\": \"shopping\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"购物\", \"phrase\": \"shopping list|购物清单\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you check all the items on the shopping list?\", \"target\": \"list\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"清单\", \"phrase\": \"shopping list|购物清单\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because our kids got married, we are now in-laws.\", \"target\": \"laws\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"法律\", \"phrase\": \"in-laws|姻亲\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"place like home|家是最好的归宿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like home|像家一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she wakes up, we'll turn on the music.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"turn on|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as I get to London, I'll drop you a line.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"落下; 放弃; 减少\", \"phrase\": \"drop a line|发短信; 写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as I get to London, I'll drop you a line.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"drop you a line|给…写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As far as I know, your letter is under that book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"under that book|在那个书下面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Aren't you coming to pick me up tomorrow morning?\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接\", \"phrase\": \"pick me up|接我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After you have read it, give the book back to me.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"give back|还回\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After you have read it, give the book back to me.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"give back|归还\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great number of books are published every year.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every year|每年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A friend of mine asked me to send her a postcard.\", \"target\": \"send\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发送\", \"phrase\": \"send her a postcard|寄给她一张明信片\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A barber is a man who shaves and cuts men's hair.\", \"target\": \"cuts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"剪\", \"phrase\": \"cuts hair|剪头发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A barber is a man who shaves and cuts men's hair.\", \"target\": \"men\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男人\", \"phrase\": \"men's hair|男士头发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"I'll do it tomorrow.\\\" \\\"You said that yesterday!\\\"\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"said that|说了那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Did he write a letter yesterday?\\\" \\\"Yes, he did.\\\"\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"write a letter|写信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're not old enough to get a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶员\", \"phrase\": \"driver's license|驾驶执照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll soon get accustomed to this cold weather.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"寒冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold weather|寒冷的天气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd do that if Tom asked you to, wouldn't you?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"would you|你会吗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You will soon get accustomed to your new school.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new school|新学校\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should set a good example for your children.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good example|好榜样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should set a good example for your children.\", \"target\": \"example\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"例子\", \"phrase\": \"good example|好榜样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You look like you've just lost your best friend.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best friend|最好的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who will take care of the dog while we are away?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who will take care of the dog while we are away?\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where do you suppose you'll spend your vacation?\", \"target\": \"spend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"度过\", \"phrase\": \"spend your vacation|度过你的假期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When he retired, his son took over the business.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接管\", \"phrase\": \"took over|接管\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When he retired, his son took over his business.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接管\", \"phrase\": \"took over|接管\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When he retired, his son took over his business.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his business|他的生意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Were I to die, who would look after my children?\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"look after|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We want to be on the first bus tomorrow morning.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"first bus|第一辆公共汽车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two months have passed since he left for France.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since he left|自从他离开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom still drinks, but not as much as he used to.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"那么\", \"phrase\": \"as much as|和...一样多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom still drinks, but not as much as he used to.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"used to|习惯于\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom speaks Japanese better than the Japanese do.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"speaks better|说得更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom seems to be a fairly successful businessman.\", \"target\": \"successful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"成功的\", \"phrase\": \"successful businessman|成功的商人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he wasn't ready, but Mary said she was.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"said she was|她说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom puts a lot of sugar and cream in his coffee.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom puts a lot of sugar and cream in his coffee.\", \"target\": \"cream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奶油\", \"phrase\": \"sugar and cream|糖和奶油\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom opened the blinds and looked out the window.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"向外\", \"phrase\": \"looked out|向外看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't the only one here who's a good singer.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good singer|好歌手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is very good at doing things with his hands.\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"with his hands|用他的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is single and has a three-year-old daughter.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"three-year-old|三岁的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is single and has a three-year-old daughter.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"three-year-old|三岁的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is looking for someone to take Mary's place.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"代替\", \"phrase\": \"take place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is looking for someone to take Mary's place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"位置\", \"phrase\": \"take place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been on the wanted list for three years.\", \"target\": \"list\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名单\", \"phrase\": \"wanted list|通缉名单\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had no idea why Mary didn't want to do that.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to do|想要做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like women who wear too much makeup.\", \"target\": \"wear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿,戴\", \"phrase\": \"wear makeup|化妆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like women who wear too much makeup.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't have any idea why his wife left him.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his wife|他的妻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't have any idea why his wife left him.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"left him|离开了他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't come home last night. I hope he's OK.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"昨晚的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary argue with each other all the time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"all the time|一直\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I have known each other for a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This towel is so soft and fluffy. It feels good!\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"feels good|感觉好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This river is dangerous for children to swim in.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"swim in|在...里游泳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is covered in snow all year round.\", \"target\": \"covered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"覆盖\", \"phrase\": \"covered in snow|被雪覆盖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is covered in snow all year round.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一年四季\", \"phrase\": \"all year round|一年四季\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a man at the door who wants to see you.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wants to see|想要看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are at least thirty students in our class.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least|至少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are at least thirty students in our class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"our class|我们班\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are a lot of dictionaries in the bookcase.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|许多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The weatherman says there is a storm on the way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on the way|在路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The weather was not only cold, it was also damp.\", \"target\": \"also\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"not only...also|不仅仅...也\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was delayed because of heavy snowfall.\", \"target\": \"heavy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重的\", \"phrase\": \"heavy snowfall|大雪\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The problem is that solar energy costs too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"costs too much|花费太高\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The money you give them will be put to good use.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"put to good use|善用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The money you give them will be put to good use.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good use|善用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The money you give them will be put to good use.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"用途\", \"phrase\": \"good use|好用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The majority of his income goes to pay his rent.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"pay his rent|支付房租\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The majority of his income goes to pay his rent.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his rent|他的租金\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The king will appear in person tomorrow evening.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"in person|亲自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The court acquitted him of the charge of murder.\", \"target\": \"charge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"指控\", \"phrase\": \"charge of murder|谋杀指控\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The coral reef is the region's prime attraction.\", \"target\": \"prime\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"主要的\", \"phrase\": \"prime attraction|主要景点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The circumstances did not allow me to go abroad.\", \"target\": \"allow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"allow me to|允许我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The circumstances did not allow me to go abroad.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go abroad|出国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car broke down after half an hour's driving.\", \"target\": \"half\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一半的\", \"phrase\": \"half an hour|半个小时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The bill passed by a small majority of 10 votes.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"small majority|小多数\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people like summer, and others like winter.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like winter|喜欢冬天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sir, that CD is available only by special order.\", \"target\": \"special\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"特殊的\", \"phrase\": \"special order|特别订购\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sir, that CD is available only by special order.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"订单\", \"phrase\": \"special order|特别订单\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She will be glad if you go to see her in person.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"see her|看她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She will be glad if you go to see her in person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"in person|亲自\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She suggested to me that I call off the meeting.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取消\", \"phrase\": \"call off|取消\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She suggested to me that I call off the meeting.\", \"target\": \"meeting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"call off the meeting|取消会议\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She furnished the room with beautiful furniture.\", \"target\": \"beautiful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美丽的\", \"phrase\": \"beautiful furniture|漂亮的家具\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Seen from the moon, the earth looks like a ball.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like a ball|看起来像一个球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Seen from the moon, the earth looks like a ball.\", \"target\": \"ball\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"球\", \"phrase\": \"like a ball|像一个球\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Perhaps Tom is too old to do this kind of thing.\", \"target\": \"kind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"kind of|种类的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Patience is sometimes the most effective weapon.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"most effective|最有效\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our situation should improve in the near future.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"附近的\", \"phrase\": \"near future|近期\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"New York City policemen wear dark blue uniforms.\", \"target\": \"dark\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"深色的\", \"phrase\": \"dark blue|深蓝色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"New York City policemen wear dark blue uniforms.\", \"target\": \"blue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"蓝色\", \"phrase\": \"dark blue|深蓝色\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father insisted on our waiting for the train.\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"waiting for|等待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Monopoly is a popular game for families to play.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play game|玩游戏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mastering a foreign language calls for patience.\", \"target\": \"calls\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"calls for|要求\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would be ridiculous to spend all their money.\", \"target\": \"spend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"spend money|花钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't easy to write a love letter in English.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"love letter|情书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is said that treasure is buried in this area.\", \"target\": \"buried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"埋藏\", \"phrase\": \"is buried|被埋藏\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is an advantage to be able to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"use a computer|使用电脑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It goes without saying that health is important.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"goes without saying|不言而喻\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been looking for a new job for a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been looking for a new job for a long time.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"long time|很长时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm cold. Would you mind turning the heating on?\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"介意\", \"phrase\": \"would you mind|你介意吗\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm cold. Would you mind turning the heating on?\", \"target\": \"turning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"turning on|打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm cold. Would you mind turning the heating on?\", \"target\": \"heating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"暖气\", \"phrase\": \"turning the heating on|打开暖气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll wait for you in front of the radio station.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll wait for you in front of the radio station.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"radio station|广播电台\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder why I feel so lonely when it gets cold.\", \"target\": \"gets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变得\", \"phrase\": \"gets cold|变冷\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder where Tom is planning to go to college.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to college|上大学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to get a haircut before I go on the trip.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go on the trip|去旅行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that it's unlikely Tom will get elected.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will get|将会得到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I passed the city hall on my way to the station.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on my way|在我的路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I often use SSH to access my computers remotely.\", \"target\": \"access\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"访问\", \"phrase\": \"access my computers|访问我的电脑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live near the sea, so I often go to the beach.\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near the sea|在海边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live near the sea, so I often go to the beach.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to the beach|去海滩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom is in his room changing clothes.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his room|他的房间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom is in his room changing clothes.\", \"target\": \"changing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"换衣服\", \"phrase\": \"changing clothes|换衣服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom is in his room changing clothes.\", \"target\": \"clothes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"衣服\", \"phrase\": \"changing clothes|换衣服\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope everything will turn out well in the end.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结果\", \"phrase\": \"turn out|结果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope everything will turn out well in the end.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最终\", \"phrase\": \"turn out well|结果良好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope everything will turn out well in the end.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"turn out well|结果很好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a friend whose father is a famous writer.\", \"target\": \"famous\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"著名的\", \"phrase\": \"famous writer|著名作家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I find it hard to get up early on cold mornings.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold mornings|寒冷的早晨\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't believe you. You're always telling lies.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"always telling lies|总是说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't believe you. You're always telling lies.\", \"target\": \"telling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"telling lies|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't believe you. You're always telling lies.\", \"target\": \"lies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"telling lies|说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't pay attention to what they were saying.\", \"target\": \"attention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"注意力\", \"phrase\": \"pay attention to|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't expect to see you at a place like this.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like this|像这样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I could swear there's something inside this box.\", \"target\": \"inside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...里面\", \"phrase\": \"inside this box|盒子里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I cannot help wondering if he will come on time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"on time|准时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How many flights to New York do you offer a day?\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"proper noun\", \"zh\": \"纽约\", \"phrase\": \"New York|纽约\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How many flights to New York do you offer a day?\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"a day|一天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long would it take to swim across the river?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long would it take to swim across the river?\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"swim across|游泳穿过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long did it take you to translate this book?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His mother sat up all night waiting for her son.\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"sat up all night waiting for|整夜等待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a regular at the bars and pubs around here.\", \"target\": \"pubs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"酒吧\", \"phrase\": \"bars and pubs|酒吧和酒馆\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a regular at the bars and pubs around here.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...周围\", \"phrase\": \"around here|这里附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He stressed the convenient aspects of city life.\", \"target\": \"aspects\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方面\", \"phrase\": \"convenient aspects|便利的方面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He stressed the convenient aspects of city life.\", \"target\": \"aspects\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方面\", \"phrase\": \"convenient aspects|便利的方面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said he was tired, so he would go home early.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said he was tired, so he would go home early.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"go home|回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He said he was tired, so he would go home early.\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"早\", \"phrase\": \"go home early|早点回家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He makes it a rule to take a walk every morning.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"采取\", \"phrase\": \"take a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He makes it a rule to take a walk every morning.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"take a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is very influential in the world of medicine.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"world of medicine|医学界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is on goods terms with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"goods\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"on goods terms|关系良好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is on goods terms with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"terms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"条款\", \"phrase\": \"good terms|良好关系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is on goods terms with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"goods\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"on goods terms|关系良好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is on goods terms with all of his classmates.\", \"target\": \"terms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"条款\", \"phrase\": \"good terms|良好关系\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He hasn't come yet. He must have missed the bus.\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"missed the bus|错过公交车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came to my house on the pretext of seeing me.\", \"target\": \"seeing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"on the pretext of seeing|以看望为借口\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always leaves the window open when he sleeps.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"打开的\", \"phrase\": \"leaves the window open|留下窗户打开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give a thief enough rope and he'll hang himself.\", \"target\": \"rope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绳子\", \"phrase\": \"enough rope|足够的绳子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Give a thief enough rope and he'll hang himself.\", \"target\": \"hang\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"绞死\", \"phrase\": \"hang himself|自缢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"From time to time, he goes to Tokyo on business.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"From time to time|时常\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Fish such as carp and trout live in fresh water.\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"水\", \"phrase\": \"fresh water|淡水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody knew that Tom could speak French well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"speak well|说得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you think you could make a little less noise?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a little less|稍微少一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you think you could make a little less noise?\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"少\", \"phrase\": \"a little less|稍微少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the difference between good and bad?\", \"target\": \"difference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区别\", \"phrase\": \"the difference|区别\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know if my father is still in the office?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still in|仍然在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know if my father is still in the office?\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"in the office|在办公室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you have any difficulty in finding my house?\", \"target\": \"finding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"finding my house|找到我的房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you please speak a little bit more slowly?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you please speak a little bit more slowly?\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little bit|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you please speak a little bit more slowly?\", \"target\": \"slowly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"慢慢地\", \"phrase\": \"speak slowly|慢慢地说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you tell me how to get to the train station?\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you tell me how to get to the train station?\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you tell me how to get to the train station?\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you tell me how to get to the train station?\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"train station|火车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At that time, I was still taking French lessons.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still taking|仍然在学\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At that time, I was still taking French lessons.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在学\", \"phrase\": \"taking lessons|上课\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Apart from some fruit, he hasn't eaten anything.\", \"target\": \"apart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"apart from|除了...之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After the accident, Tom decided to stop skating.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"stop skating|停止滑冰\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"About how long will it take to get there by bus?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A detective arrived upon the scene of the crime.\", \"target\": \"upon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之上\", \"phrase\": \"arrived upon the scene|到达现场\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll have to play it by ear at the interview.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"演奏\", \"phrase\": \"play it by ear|即兴发挥\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll have to play it by ear at the interview.\", \"target\": \"ear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"耳朵\", \"phrase\": \"play it by ear|听其自然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should set a good example to your children.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good example|好榜样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should set a good example to your children.\", \"target\": \"example\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"例子\", \"phrase\": \"good example|好榜样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should keep your valuables in a safe place.\", \"target\": \"safe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"安全的\", \"phrase\": \"safe place|安全的地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should keep your valuables in a safe place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"safe place|安全的地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You don't need to be afraid of making mistakes.\", \"target\": \"making\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯错误\", \"phrase\": \"making mistakes|犯错误\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to go to the zoo this afternoon?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to|去...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to go to the zoo this afternoon?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to|去...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to go to the zoo this afternoon?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to|去...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to go to the zoo this afternoon?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go to|去...\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's your favorite game to play with friends?\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"play with|和...一起玩\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What time was it when you entered the building?\", \"target\": \"entered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进入\", \"phrase\": \"entered the building|进入大楼\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll have lived here for two years next April.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个月\", \"phrase\": \"next April|明年四月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We promised to stand by him in case of trouble.\", \"target\": \"stand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支持\", \"phrase\": \"stand by|支持\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We promised to stand by him in case of trouble.\", \"target\": \"case\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...情况下\", \"phrase\": \"in case of|以防\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We often watch TV while we're eating breakfast.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating breakfast|吃早餐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We need to talk about that as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We made good time until we ran into a blizzard.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good time|好时光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We are having a serious talk about your future.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谈话\", \"phrase\": \"serious talk|严肃的谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom worked very hard and earned a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of money|很多钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom will be the first person to enter the cave.\", \"target\": \"enter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进入\", \"phrase\": \"enter the cave|进入洞穴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was arrested for driving without a license.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without a license|没有驾照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to know if you have time to help him.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help him|帮助他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to know where he could buy turmeric.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy turmeric|购买姜黄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to follow in his father's footsteps.\", \"target\": \"follow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跟随\", \"phrase\": \"follow in|追随\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to follow in his father's footsteps.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"father's footsteps|父亲的脚步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to follow in his father's footsteps.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"father's footsteps|父亲的脚步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom turned right when he should've turned left.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"转弯\", \"phrase\": \"turned right|向右转\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows you better than he knows anyone else.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"knows you better|知道你更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows you better than he knows anyone else.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"knows anyone else|知道任何人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't doing what he's supposed to be doing.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"应该的\", \"phrase\": \"supposed to be|应该\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is trying to figure out how to do that now.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"figure out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom hasn't yet told us what he wants us to buy.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"told us|告诉我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has no friends who are willing to help him.\", \"target\": \"willing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"愿意的\", \"phrase\": \"willing to help|乐于帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has no friends who are willing to help him.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help him|帮助他\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom folded the paper before handing it to Mary.\", \"target\": \"handing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"递给\", \"phrase\": \"handing it to|递给它给\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did better this time than he did last time.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last time|上次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did better this time than he did last time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"last time|上次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could've figured that out without any help.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"figured out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could've figured that out without any help.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without any help|没有帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom could've figured that out without any help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"any help|任何帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom begged his father to buy him a new bicycle.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy him a new bicycle|给他买一辆新自行车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom begged his father to buy him a new bicycle.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new bicycle|新自行车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked for Mary's permission to leave early.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave early|早点离开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This ship is too big to pass through the canal.\", \"target\": \"pass\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"通过\", \"phrase\": \"pass through|通过\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This river is three times longer than that one.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"倍\", \"phrase\": \"three times|三倍\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This carpet is superior to that one in quality.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"that one|那个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They attempted to break through the enemy line.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打破\", \"phrase\": \"break through|突破\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They attempted to break through the enemy line.\", \"target\": \"line\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"enemy line|敌线\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The sun rises in the east and sets in the west.\", \"target\": \"west\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西\", \"phrase\": \"in the west|在西边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The policeman arrested him for drunken driving.\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"drunken driving|酒后驾驶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The man is loading the moving truck on his own.\", \"target\": \"loading\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"装载\", \"phrase\": \"loading truck|装载卡车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The man is loading the moving truck on his own.\", \"target\": \"moving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"移动的\", \"phrase\": \"moving truck|搬运卡车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The man is loading the moving truck on his own.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his own|他自己的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The man is loading the moving truck on his own.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"on his own|独自地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house I bought is pretty far from downtown.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远离\", \"phrase\": \"far from|远离...从\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The girl was afraid to jump down from the roof.\", \"target\": \"jump\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跳\", \"phrase\": \"jump down|跳下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby was sound asleep in her mother's arms.\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"安静的\", \"phrase\": \"sound asleep|安然入睡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby was sound asleep in her mother's arms.\", \"target\": \"arms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"胳膊\", \"phrase\": \"mother's arms|母亲的怀抱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The armed forces occupied the entire territory.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"entire territory|整个领土\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's not a full-time employee of this company.\", \"target\": \"full\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"全职的\", \"phrase\": \"full-time|全职\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's not a full-time employee of this company.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"full-time|全职\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She succeeded in getting him to tell the truth.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"tell the truth|说实话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She spent a good deal of money on her vacation.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"good deal|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She spent a good deal of money on her vacation.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大量的钱\", \"phrase\": \"a good deal|大量的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is always finding fault with her neighbors.\", \"target\": \"finding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"finding fault|挑剔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is always finding fault with her neighbors.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"缺点\", \"phrase\": \"finding fault with|挑剔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is always finding fault with her neighbors.\", \"target\": \"neighbors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邻居\", \"phrase\": \"with her neighbors|和她的邻居\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please turn off the light before you go to bed.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter what happens, I won't change my mind.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"no matter|无论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My sister can play the piano better than I can.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弹奏\", \"phrase\": \"play the piano|弹钢琴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My sister can play the piano better than I can.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better than|比...更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I be the first to offer my congratulations.\", \"target\": \"offer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提供\", \"phrase\": \"offer congratulations|祝贺\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Losing one's health is worse than losing money.\", \"target\": \"losing\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"失去\", \"phrase\": \"losing one's health|失去健康\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not easy writing a love letter in English.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"love letter|情书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's dangerous to fool around with electricity.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"fool around|四处玩乐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is a pity that you cannot come to the party.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot come|不能来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost him 50 dollars to rent a car in Hawaii.\", \"target\": \"rent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"租借\", \"phrase\": \"rent a car|租车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is this ladder strong enough to bear my weight?\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强壮的\", \"phrase\": \"strong enough|足够强壮的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is this ladder strong enough to bear my weight?\", \"target\": \"bear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"承受\", \"phrase\": \"bear weight|承受重量\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't hurry, you'll miss the last train.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"miss the train|错过火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't hurry, you'll miss the last train.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last train|末班车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he knew her phone number, he could call her.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话号码\", \"phrase\": \"phone number|电话号码\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he knew her phone number, he could call her.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"call her|给她打电话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure Tom won't have any trouble finding us.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"have trouble|有麻烦\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry that I have kept you waiting so long.\", \"target\": \"kept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让...等待\", \"phrase\": \"kept you waiting|让您等待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry that I have kept you waiting so long.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很长时间\", \"phrase\": \"so long|这么久\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad that I didn't buy something like this.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like this|像这样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would like to sit in the non-smoking section.\", \"target\": \"non\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"无烟的\", \"phrase\": \"non-smoking section|无烟区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would like to sit in the non-smoking section.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"无烟的\", \"phrase\": \"non-smoking section|无烟区\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took my shoes off and put them under the bed.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"put them under|把它们放在下面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that you were on my side.\", \"target\": \"granted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为...理所当然\", \"phrase\": \"took it for granted|认为...理所当然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took it for granted that you were on my side.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一边\", \"phrase\": \"on my side|在我一边\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I suspect they water down the beer in that pub.\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"稀释\", \"phrase\": \"water down|冲淡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I stayed home all day instead of going to work.\", \"target\": \"instead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"代替\", \"phrase\": \"instead of|代替...而不是\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I stayed home all day instead of going to work.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"going to work|去上班\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran as fast as possible to catch up with him.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"as fast as possible|尽可能快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ran as fast as possible to catch up with him.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"追上\", \"phrase\": \"catch up with|追上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like swimming, but I don't like to swim here.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"don't like|不喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that I know it, but I can't remember it.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"know it|知道它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that I know it, but I can't remember it.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't remember|不能记得\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that I know it, but I can't remember it.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"can't remember|记不住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got up early enough to catch the first train.\", \"target\": \"catch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"catch the train|抓住火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got up early enough to catch the first train.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"first train|第一班火车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found a taxi, but there was no driver inside.\", \"target\": \"inside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"里面\", \"phrase\": \"inside|里面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I felt cold and uncomfortable the entire night.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"entire night|整夜\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think Tom is going to be too much help.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know that you didn't know how to swim.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"didn't know|不知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't have done it without you. Thank you.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without you|没有你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am not used to drinking coffee without sugar.\", \"target\": \"drinking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"drinking coffee|喝咖啡\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am not used to drinking coffee without sugar.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without sugar|没有糖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am not used to drinking coffee without sugar.\", \"target\": \"sugar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"糖\", \"phrase\": \"without sugar|没有糖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How many books do you think you've read so far?\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"到目前为止\", \"phrase\": \"so far|到目前为止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long can it be kept going with 100 dollars?\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"kept going|继续进行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about eating out this evening for a change?\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"eating out|外出吃饭\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How about eating out this evening for a change?\", \"target\": \"change\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"改变\", \"phrase\": \"for a change|为了换换口味\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's very influential in the world of medicine.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"world of medicine|医学界\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He went to the United States to study medicine.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"美国\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He rescued the dog at the risk of his own life.\", \"target\": \"risk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风险\", \"phrase\": \"at the risk of|在…的风险下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He rescued the dog at the risk of his own life.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his own life|他自己的生命\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He rescued the dog at the risk of his own life.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own life|生命\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is always a little irritable in the morning.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little irritable|有点儿烦躁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He got into this school in September last year.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"last year|去年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He brought me coffee, when I had asked for tea.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"asked for|要求\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He amazed everyone by passing his driving test.\", \"target\": \"passing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"通过\", \"phrase\": \"passing his driving test|通过驾驶考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He amazed everyone by passing his driving test.\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"driving test|驾驶考试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you still not finished paying for my bike?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"still not|仍然没有\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Friends are like flowers in the garden of life.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like flowers|像花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Friends are like flowers in the garden of life.\", \"target\": \"flowers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"flowers in the garden|花园里的花\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Friends are like flowers in the garden of life.\", \"target\": \"garden\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花园\", \"phrase\": \"garden of life|生命的花园\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone knew that Tom could speak French well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"speak well|说得好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you think the weather will be fine tomorrow?\", \"target\": \"fine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"be fine|一切都好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know if Tom has spoken to Mary recently?\", \"target\": \"spoken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"spoken to|和...说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you ever dream about flying through the sky?\", \"target\": \"flying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"飞行\", \"phrase\": \"dream about flying|梦想着飞行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cities are exciting places, but also stressful.\", \"target\": \"also\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"also stressful|也紧张\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At what age did you have your first girlfriend?\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"first girlfriend|第一个女朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An angle of 90 degrees is called a right angle.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"直角的\", \"phrase\": \"right angle|直角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An angle of 90 degrees is called a right angle.\", \"target\": \"angle\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"角度\", \"phrase\": \"right angle|直角\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is to take care of yourself.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"采取\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is to take care of yourself.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"take care of|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All the guests were touched by her hospitality.\", \"target\": \"touched\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感动\", \"phrase\": \"touched by|被...感动\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A tsunami is coming, so please be on the alert.\", \"target\": \"alert\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警惕\", \"phrase\": \"on alert|保持警惕\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A truck was standing in the middle of the road.\", \"target\": \"middle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"中间\", \"phrase\": \"in the middle of|在...中间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A strange sound was heard from behind the door.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind the door|在门后\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A permanent job is better than a temporary one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"a temporary one|一个临时的职位\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A good cook doesn't throw out yesterday's soup.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扔掉\", \"phrase\": \"throw out|扔掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out in my neighborhood last night.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"broke out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A cafeteria is a self-service style restaurant.\", \"target\": \"self\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自助的\", \"phrase\": \"self-service|自助服务\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A cafeteria is a self-service style restaurant.\", \"target\": \"service\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"服务\", \"phrase\": \"self-service|自助服务\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A cafeteria is a self-service style restaurant.\", \"target\": \"style\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"风格\", \"phrase\": \"self-service style|自助餐风格\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Thank you for helping me.\\\" \\\"Don't mention it.\\\"\", \"target\": \"mention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提及\", \"phrase\": \"don't mention it|不必客气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"A rolling stone gathers no moss\\\" is a proverb.\", \"target\": \"rolling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"滚动的\", \"phrase\": \"rolling stone|滚石\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"A rolling stone gathers no moss\\\" is a proverb.\", \"target\": \"stone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"石头\", \"phrase\": \"rolling stone|滚石\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"A rolling stone gathers no moss\\\" is a proverb.\", \"target\": \"gathers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"聚集\", \"phrase\": \"gathers no moss|不生苔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're too old to be doing this kind of thing.\", \"target\": \"kind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"kind of|种类的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're just running away from life's problems.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"逃避\", \"phrase\": \"running away|逃跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should pay more attention to what you say.\", \"target\": \"attention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"注意力\", \"phrase\": \"pay attention|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should pay more attention to his warnings.\", \"target\": \"attention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"注意力\", \"phrase\": \"pay attention|注意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You need to have friends who can help you out.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help you out|帮助你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You need to have friends who can help you out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"help out|帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you put down that paper and listen to me?\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放下\", \"phrase\": \"put down|放下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you put down that paper and listen to me?\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"put down paper|放下纸\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will you pick me up at seven tomorrow morning?\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡\", \"phrase\": \"pick me up|接我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where is the United Airlines check-in counter?\", \"target\": \"check\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"检查\", \"phrase\": \"check-in|办理登机手续\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where is the United Airlines check-in counter?\", \"target\": \"counter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"柜台\", \"phrase\": \"check-in counter|值机柜台\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where did you get the money to buy that dress?\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"buy that dress|买那件裙子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When was the last time you watered the garden?\", \"target\": \"watered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浇水\", \"phrase\": \"watered the garden|浇灌花园\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When she was thirteen, she ran away from home.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"逃跑\", \"phrase\": \"ran away|逃跑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When she was thirteen, she ran away from home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"away from home|离家出走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What makes you think I won't be able to do it?\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"be able to|能够\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Unfortunately, the telephone was out of order.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不工作\", \"phrase\": \"out of order|失修\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Unfortunately, the telephone was out of order.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"顺序;秩序\", \"phrase\": \"out of order|失修;故障\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wrung out the towel and hung it up to dry.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拧出\", \"phrase\": \"wrung out|拧出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wrung out the towel and hung it up to dry.\", \"target\": \"hung\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"悬挂\", \"phrase\": \"hung it up|把它挂起来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom waited for Mary in front of the warehouse.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thinks I'm missing this great opportunity.\", \"target\": \"missing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"missing this opportunity|错过这个机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thinks I'm missing this great opportunity.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"伟大的\", \"phrase\": \"great opportunity|绝佳的机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thinks I'm missing this great opportunity.\", \"target\": \"opportunity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"great opportunity|绝佳的机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom studied hard so he could get into college.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get into|进入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that he didn't like air conditioning.\", \"target\": \"conditioning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"空调\", \"phrase\": \"air conditioning|空调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he didn't want to waste time arguing.\", \"target\": \"waste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浪费\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he didn't want to waste time arguing.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"waste time|浪费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he didn't want to waste time arguing.\", \"target\": \"arguing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"争论\", \"phrase\": \"waste time arguing|浪费时间争论\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows I want to leave as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows I want to leave as soon as possible.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as possible|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is waiting for you in the conference room.\", \"target\": \"conference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"conference room|会议室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is waiting for you in the conference room.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"conference room|会议室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the one that told us about the problem.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"told us|告诉我们\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has already been told to leave Mary alone.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"leave Mary alone|独自离开玛丽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has already been told to leave Mary alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"leave alone|独自离开\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom had no intention of giving Mary any money.\", \"target\": \"giving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"giving money|给钱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't have any friends who like camping.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"like camping|喜欢露营\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't think of a good place to hide it.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good place|好地方\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought this camera for a reasonable price.\", \"target\": \"reasonable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"合理的\", \"phrase\": \"reasonable price|合理的价格\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bought this camera for a reasonable price.\", \"target\": \"price\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"价格\", \"phrase\": \"reasonable price|合理的价格\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bent down and picked up a handful of sand.\", \"target\": \"picked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"picked up|捡起\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom bent down and picked up a handful of sand.\", \"target\": \"handful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一把\", \"phrase\": \"handful of sand|沙一把\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To my surprise, he easily came up with a plan.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想出\", \"phrase\": \"came up with|想出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This plan will be very expensive to carry out.\", \"target\": \"carry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"执行\", \"phrase\": \"carry out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This plan will be very expensive to carry out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"执行\", \"phrase\": \"carry out|执行\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is snow-covered the entire year.\", \"target\": \"snow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雪\", \"phrase\": \"snow-covered|覆盖着雪的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is snow-covered the entire year.\", \"target\": \"covered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"覆盖\", \"phrase\": \"snow-covered|雪覆盖的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This mountain is snow-covered the entire year.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"entire year|整年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle took place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"took place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the place where the battle took place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"took place|发生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This dictionary isn't the most recent version.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"most recent|最新\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This dictionary isn't the most recent version.\", \"target\": \"recent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最近的\", \"phrase\": \"most recent version|最新版本\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would capture as many people as possible.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"as many people as possible|尽可能多的人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would capture as many people as possible.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"as possible|尽可能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They arrived in Osaka at the beginning of May.\", \"target\": \"beginning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"beginning of May|五月初\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There has been a good apple harvest this year.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"good apple harvest|苹果大丰收\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There has been a good apple harvest this year.\", \"target\": \"harvest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"收获\", \"phrase\": \"apple harvest|苹果收获\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Their traditional life style no longer exists.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不再\", \"phrase\": \"no longer|不再\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The young man put out his hand and I shook it.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伸出\", \"phrase\": \"put out|伸出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The young man put out his hand and I shook it.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伸出\", \"phrase\": \"put out|伸出\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The young man put out his hand and I shook it.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his hand|他的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The young man put out his hand and I shook it.\", \"target\": \"hand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"put out his hand|伸出手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The young man put out his hand and I shook it.\", \"target\": \"shook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摇动\", \"phrase\": \"shook it|摇动它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The revolution has brought about many changes.\", \"target\": \"brought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带来\", \"phrase\": \"brought about|带来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The participants were for the most part women.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"大多数\", \"phrase\": \"for the most part|大部分\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The participants were for the most part women.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"for the most part|大部分\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The living room furniture was modern in style.\", \"target\": \"style\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风格\", \"phrase\": \"in style|风格地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dog followed its master, wagging its tail.\", \"target\": \"tail\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尾巴\", \"phrase\": \"wagging its tail|摇着尾巴\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby was fast asleep in her mother's arms.\", \"target\": \"arms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"胳膊\", \"phrase\": \"mother's arms|母亲的怀抱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The air is bad here. Will you open the window?\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"open the window|打开窗户\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thanks to a cold summer, beer has sold poorly.\", \"target\": \"sold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卖\", \"phrase\": \"sold poorly|销售不佳\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some say that China was like a Russian colony.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"like a|像一个\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some say that China was like a Russian colony.\", \"target\": \"colony\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"殖民地\", \"phrase\": \"Russian colony|俄罗斯殖民地\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wrote to her parents at least once a week.\", \"target\": \"least\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"至少\", \"phrase\": \"at least once a week|至少一次一周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She will give her picture to whoever wants it.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"wants it|想要它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She spends a lot of time practicing the piano.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of time|很多时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made elaborate preparations for the party.\", \"target\": \"preparations\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"准备工作\", \"phrase\": \"elaborate preparations|精心的准备\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She loved me in the same way that I loved her.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"in the same way|以同样的方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She loved me in the same way that I loved her.\", \"target\": \"loved\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"loved her|爱她\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is busy at present and can't speak to you.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot speak|不能说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is busy at present and can't speak to you.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot speak|不能说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is busy at present and can't speak to you.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"cannot speak|不能说\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Remember to mail this letter tomorrow morning.\", \"target\": \"mail\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"邮寄\", \"phrase\": \"mail this letter|寄这封信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our restaurant is better than that restaurant.\", \"target\": \"restaurant\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐厅\", \"phrase\": \"that restaurant|那家餐厅\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother made us cheese sandwiches for lunch.\", \"target\": \"sandwiches\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"三明治\", \"phrase\": \"cheese sandwiches|奶酪三明治\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most people only want to hear their own truth.\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"自己的\", \"phrase\": \"own truth|自己的真相\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary hardly ever talks to her husband anymore.\", \"target\": \"anymore\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"再也不\", \"phrase\": \"hardly ever talks to her husband anymore|几乎不再和她的丈夫说话了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many Asians have English as a common language.\", \"target\": \"common\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"共同的\", \"phrase\": \"common language|通用语言\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Just pull the door shut. It'll lock by itself.\", \"target\": \"shut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关上\", \"phrase\": \"pull the door shut|拉门关上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Just pull the door shut. It'll lock by itself.\", \"target\": \"lock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"锁\", \"phrase\": \"lock by itself|自动锁住\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Jazz fusion is a combination of rock and jazz.\", \"target\": \"combination\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"组合\", \"phrase\": \"combination of rock and jazz|摇滚和爵士乐的组合\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Jazz fusion is a combination of rock and jazz.\", \"target\": \"jazz\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爵士乐\", \"phrase\": \"jazz fusion|爵士融合\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time you went to bed. Turn off the radio.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's next to impossible to finish it in a day.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎\", \"phrase\": \"next to impossible|几乎不可能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been ten years since I came to this town.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since I came|自从我来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was not long before we met again by chance.\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"by chance|偶然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is like looking for a needle in a haystack.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"looking for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is like looking for a needle in a haystack.\", \"target\": \"needle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"针\", \"phrase\": \"needle in a haystack|海底捞针\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it true Tom wants to paint his house green?\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his house|他的房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If anything should happen, please let me know.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"please let me know|请告诉我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If anything should happen, please let me know.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"let me know|让我知道\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm really looking forward to summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"期待\", \"phrase\": \"looking forward to|期待着\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not used to drinking coffee without sugar.\", \"target\": \"without\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"without sugar|没有糖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not used to drinking coffee without sugar.\", \"target\": \"sugar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"糖\", \"phrase\": \"without sugar|没有糖\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm considering studying in America next year.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"明年\", \"phrase\": \"next year|明年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish that we could spend more time together.\", \"target\": \"spend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"spend time|花时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish that we could spend more time together.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"spend time together|一起度过时光\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to help us find out who killed Tom.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弄清楚\", \"phrase\": \"find out|查明\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I missed the opening ceremony of the Olympics.\", \"target\": \"opening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"开幕的\", \"phrase\": \"opening ceremony|开幕式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him just as he was coming out of school.\", \"target\": \"coming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"coming out|出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him just as he was coming out of school.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从...出来\", \"phrase\": \"coming out of|从...出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met him by chance on the train this morning.\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"by chance|偶然\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like cracking sunflower seeds with my teeth.\", \"target\": \"cracking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"嗑\", \"phrase\": \"cracking sunflower seeds|嗑瓜子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like cracking sunflower seeds with my teeth.\", \"target\": \"seeds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"种子\", \"phrase\": \"sunflower seeds|葵花籽\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like cracking sunflower seeds with my teeth.\", \"target\": \"teeth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"牙齿\", \"phrase\": \"teeth|牙齿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I go to the library two or three times a week.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"two or three times a week|一周两三次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feed my cat every morning and every evening.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"every morning|每天早上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I fear this work will take up most of my time.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take up|花费\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I fear this work will take up most of my time.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"most of my time|我大部分时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think Tom has any teaching experience.\", \"target\": \"teaching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教学\", \"phrase\": \"teaching experience|教学经验\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't know what I should be doing right now.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"right now|现在\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't believe the child came to Tokyo alone.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"独自地\", \"phrase\": \"came alone|独自地来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't expect to hear back from Tom so soon.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"hear back|回复\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I did that as soon as Tom told me I needed to.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"as soon as|尽快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I certainly wouldn't want to be seen with Tom.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看到\", \"phrase\": \"be seen with|和...一起被看到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't let you give me your last ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"let you give|让你给\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't let you give me your last ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last ten dollars|最后十美元\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't let you give me your last ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"ten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"十\", \"phrase\": \"ten dollars|十美元\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't let you give me your last ten dollars.\", \"target\": \"dollars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"美元\", \"phrase\": \"ten dollars|十美元\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can talk about anything with my best friend.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"best friend|最好的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向前\", \"phrase\": \"looking forward|期待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向前\", \"phrase\": \"looking forward|期待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always thought that Tom was a bit different.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"a bit|稍微\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always drink a cup of coffee in the morning.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯\", \"phrase\": \"cup of coffee|咖啡杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I advise you never to live beyond your income.\", \"target\": \"beyond\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"超过\", \"phrase\": \"beyond your income|超过你的收入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long did it take you to write this report?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How late did you stay at the party last night?\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last night|昨晚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His absence gave birth to all sorts of rumors.\", \"target\": \"birth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"诞生\", \"phrase\": \"gave birth to|产生\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His absence gave birth to all sorts of rumors.\", \"target\": \"sorts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"sorts of|各种\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her suggestion seems to have been turned down.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拒绝\", \"phrase\": \"turned down|被拒绝\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was kind enough to take me to the hospital.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take me to|带我去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is the manager of the marketing department.\", \"target\": \"marketing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市场营销\", \"phrase\": \"marketing department|市场营销部门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He couldn't wait to try out his new surfboard.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"particle\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"try out|尝试\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He couldn't wait to try out his new surfboard.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"new surfboard|新冲浪板\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Going out in this rain is out of the question.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在外面\", \"phrase\": \"out of the question|毫无疑问\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Going out in this rain is out of the question.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...之外\", \"phrase\": \"out of the question|毫无疑问\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Going out in this rain is out of the question.\", \"target\": \"question\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"out of the question|问题\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me, I have to get off at the next stop.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下车\", \"phrase\": \"get off|下车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me, I have to get off at the next stop.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下一个\", \"phrase\": \"next stop|下一站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me, I have to get off at the next stop.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"站\", \"phrase\": \"get off at the stop|在站下车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody showed sympathy toward the prisoner.\", \"target\": \"toward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"对\", \"phrase\": \"toward the prisoner|对囚犯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't get an upset stomach by eating too much.\", \"target\": \"upset\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"难受的\", \"phrase\": \"upset stomach|胃痛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't get an upset stomach by eating too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Doctors refused to perform a second operation.\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal\", \"zh\": \"第二个\", \"phrase\": \"second operation|第二次手术\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the reason why the sky looks blue?\", \"target\": \"blue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"蓝色\", \"phrase\": \"looks blue|看起来是蓝色的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the reason why he cut class today?\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"逃课\", \"phrase\": \"cut class|逃课\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the reason why he cut class today?\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"课\", \"phrase\": \"cut class|逃课\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you tell me where the nearest bus stop is?\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"bus stop|公交车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you tell me where the nearest bus stop is?\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"站\", \"phrase\": \"bus stop|公交车站\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Asia is roughly four times the size of Europe.\", \"target\": \"size\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大小\", \"phrase\": \"the size of|大小\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she opened the door, a cat ran out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"ran out|跑出来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you have to do is ask him to pay the debt.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"pay the debt|偿还债务\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A true gentleman would not betray his friends.\", \"target\": \"betray\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"背叛\", \"phrase\": \"betray his friends|背叛他的朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A lot of houses were washed away by the flood.\", \"target\": \"washed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"冲走\", \"phrase\": \"washed away|冲走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A lot of houses were washed away by the flood.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"被冲走\", \"phrase\": \"washed away|被冲走\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Where were you?\\\" \\\"I was at a friend's house.\\\"\", \"target\": \"friend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"friend's house|朋友的家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Where were you?\\\" \\\"I was at a friend's house.\\\"\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"friend's house|朋友的家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better take an umbrella with you today.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"take an umbrella|带伞\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better keep your money for a rainy day.\", \"target\": \"rainy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"多雨的\", \"phrase\": \"rainy day|雨天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better keep your money for a rainy day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"rainy day|雨天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You will soon get used to speaking in public.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"习惯的\", \"phrase\": \"get used to|习惯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You walk too fast for me to keep up with you.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"walk too fast|走得太快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You walk too fast for me to keep up with you.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跟上\", \"phrase\": \"keep up with|跟上...的步伐\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should put safety before everything else.\", \"target\": \"everything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一切\", \"phrase\": \"everything else|其他一切\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should make good use of this opportunity.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"make use of|利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should make good use of this opportunity.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"make good use of|好好利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should make good use of this opportunity.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"make good use of|好好利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should make good use of this opportunity.\", \"target\": \"opportunity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"good use of opportunity|善用机会\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should make better use of your free time.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"make better use of|更好地利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should make better use of your free time.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"make use of|利用\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may have been the last person to see Tom.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last person|最后一个人\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You know as well as I do that Tom hates Mary.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"as well as|以及\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Yesterday I played tennis for the first time.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Yesterday I played tennis for the first time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"for the first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you please have a look at these papers?\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"have a look|看一下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like to have a drink before dinner?\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"have a drink|喝一杯\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When you hurt others, you also hurt yourself.\", \"target\": \"hurt\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伤害\", \"phrase\": \"hurt yourself|伤害自己\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you say to taking a walk in the park?\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you say to taking a walk in the park?\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公园\", \"phrase\": \"in the park|在公园里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must learn to live in harmony with nature.\", \"target\": \"harmony\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"和谐\", \"phrase\": \"in harmony with|与...和谐相处\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to put off the game till next Sunday.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推迟\", \"phrase\": \"put off|推迟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to put off the game till next Sunday.\", \"target\": \"game\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比赛\", \"phrase\": \"put off the game|推迟比赛\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to put off the game till next Sunday.\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"put off till|推迟到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have to put off the game till next Sunday.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"next Sunday|下个星期天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a heart-to-heart talk with each other.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心\", \"phrase\": \"heart-to-heart talk|真心话谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a heart-to-heart talk with each other.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心\", \"phrase\": \"heart-to-heart talk|倾心交谈\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We had a heart-to-heart talk with each other.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谈话\", \"phrase\": \"heart-to-heart talk|深入的谈话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Watch out for cars when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"particle\", \"zh\": \"小心\", \"phrase\": \"watch out|小心\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Watch out for cars when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"cross\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"cross the street|过马路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two hundred people died of cholera last year.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"last year|去年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn off the television. I can't concentrate.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关掉\", \"phrase\": \"turn off|关掉\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's Japanese is improving little by little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点点\", \"phrase\": \"little by little|一点一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's Japanese is improving little by little.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点点\", \"phrase\": \"little by little|一点一点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom worked hard to get the work done on time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"on time|按时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom will never willingly go there by himself.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go there|去那里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom visits Mary every time he goes to Boston.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每次\", \"phrase\": \"every time|每次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tricked Mary into doing his work for him.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his work|他的工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom seems to speak French better than before.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"better than|比...更好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says that he doesn't feel like going out.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"feel like|感觉像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says that he doesn't feel like going out.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says that he doesn't feel like going out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"going out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he can't figure out what Mary wants.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't figure out|弄不清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he can't figure out what Mary wants.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弄清楚\", \"phrase\": \"figure out|弄清楚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom remained standing as the others sat down.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐下\", \"phrase\": \"sat down|坐下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom refused to even listen to my suggestions.\", \"target\": \"listen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"listen to|听取\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom likes asparagus, but his brother doesn't.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his brother|他的兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has spent the past three years in prison.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"过去的\", \"phrase\": \"past three years|过去三年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has been struck by lightning three times.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"three times|三次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't need to stay if he didn't want to.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"want to|想要\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I see each other every day at school.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This English composition is far from perfect.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很远\", \"phrase\": \"far from|离...很远\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They have English lessons three times a week.\", \"target\": \"times\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"次\", \"phrase\": \"three times a week|每周三次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These kinds of mistakes are easy to overlook.\", \"target\": \"overlook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忽略\", \"phrase\": \"overlook|忽略\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no space in the room for another bed.\", \"target\": \"space\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"空间\", \"phrase\": \"no space|没有空间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's no space in the room for another bed.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"another bed|另一个床\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were no hats in that store that fit me.\", \"target\": \"fit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"适合\", \"phrase\": \"fit me|适合我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a cold wind blowing from the north.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷的\", \"phrase\": \"cold wind|冷风\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a cold wind blowing from the north.\", \"target\": \"wind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风\", \"phrase\": \"cold wind|寒风\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a cold wind blowing from the north.\", \"target\": \"blowing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吹\", \"phrase\": \"wind blowing|风吹\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There used to be a lot of frogs in this pond.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of|很多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There isn't a grain of truth in what he says.\", \"target\": \"grain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"颗粒\", \"phrase\": \"grain of truth|真相\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There isn't a grain of truth in what he says.\", \"target\": \"grain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"颗粒\", \"phrase\": \"grain of truth|真相\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is insufficient light to take pictures.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拍摄\", \"phrase\": \"take pictures|拍照\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is an urgent need for medical supplies.\", \"target\": \"urgent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"紧急的\", \"phrase\": \"urgent need|紧急需求\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is a small garden in front of my house.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher gathered his students around him.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"around him|在他周围\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The scenery was beautiful beyond description.\", \"target\": \"beyond\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"超过\", \"phrase\": \"beyond description|难以形容\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The plane took off and was soon out of sight.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"out of sight|视线之外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old man walked across the road carefully.\", \"target\": \"across\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"walked across the road|走过马路\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The man turned out to be a private detective.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结果\", \"phrase\": \"turned out|结果\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The information you gave me is of little use.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"少\", \"phrase\": \"little use|用处不大\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The information you gave me is of little use.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"用途\", \"phrase\": \"little use|用处不大\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flowers in the garden need to be watered.\", \"target\": \"watered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"浇水\", \"phrase\": \"be watered|被浇水\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The fire broke out after the staff went home.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"broke out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The cook prepares different dishes every day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every day|每天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The charge for a front row seat is 5 dollars.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"前排的\", \"phrase\": \"front row seat|前排座位\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The charge for a front row seat is 5 dollars.\", \"target\": \"row\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"排\", \"phrase\": \"front row|前排\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take off your hat when you enter a classroom.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Take off your hat when you enter a classroom.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"take off|脱下\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sir, you have left your lighter on the table.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"留下\", \"phrase\": \"left your lighter|留下你的打火机\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has to take a remedial course in English.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"take a course|上课\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please translate this sentence into Japanese.\", \"target\": \"translate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻译\", \"phrase\": \"translate this sentence|翻译这句话\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please remind me to mail the report tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"mail\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"邮寄\", \"phrase\": \"mail the report|邮寄报告\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who will lie for you, will lie to you.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"lie for you|为你说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who will lie for you, will lie to you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will lie|将会说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who will lie for you, will lie to you.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"lie to|对...说谎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our friend finished the race in second place.\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal number\", \"zh\": \"第二\", \"phrase\": \"second place|第二名\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One good friend is better than ten relatives.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good friend|好朋友\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One good friend is better than ten relatives.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"good friend is better than ten relatives|好朋友胜过十个亲戚\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother bought two bottles of orange juice.\", \"target\": \"bottles\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"瓶子\", \"phrase\": \"bottles of orange juice|橙汁瓶\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother bought two bottles of orange juice.\", \"target\": \"orange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"橙色的\", \"phrase\": \"orange juice|橙汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother bought two bottles of orange juice.\", \"target\": \"juice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"果汁\", \"phrase\": \"orange juice|橙汁\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always speaks in a very loud voice.\", \"target\": \"loud\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"响亮的\", \"phrase\": \"loud voice|大声\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't really sick. She's just faking it.\", \"target\": \"faking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"faking it|装病\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary isn't like the other girls in the class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"in the class|在班级里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me give you a lift as far as the station.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"到...为止\", \"phrase\": \"as far as|到...为止\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep an eye on the child for me for a moment.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看守\", \"phrase\": \"keep an eye on|看守\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep an eye on the child for me for a moment.\", \"target\": \"eye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"keep an eye on|留心照看\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep an eye on the child for me for a moment.\", \"target\": \"moment\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时刻\", \"phrase\": \"for a moment|一会儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's rude to make fun of your boss in public.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"嘲笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|取笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's rude to make fun of your boss in public.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取笑\", \"phrase\": \"make fun of|嘲笑\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's high time you left for school, isn't it?\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"high time|高时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It wouldn't be wise to ignore Tom completely.\", \"target\": \"completely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全地\", \"phrase\": \"ignore completely|完全忽略\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me 50 dollars to have my watch fixed.\", \"target\": \"fixed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"have my watch fixed|修理我的手表\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is the water in the Black Sea actually black?\", \"target\": \"black\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑色\", \"phrase\": \"Black Sea|黑海\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is the water in the Black Sea actually black?\", \"target\": \"black\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑色\", \"phrase\": \"Black Sea|黑海\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In front of the train station there's a bank.\", \"target\": \"front\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"前面\", \"phrase\": \"in front of|在...前面\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you see a mistake, then please correct it.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"please correct|请改正\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you see a mistake, then please correct it.\", \"target\": \"correct\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"纠正\", \"phrase\": \"correct it|纠正它\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains tonight, I'm not going to go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got to stop eating such sweet ice cream.\", \"target\": \"sweet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"甜的\", \"phrase\": \"sweet ice cream|甜冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got to stop eating such sweet ice cream.\", \"target\": \"ice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冰\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got to stop eating such sweet ice cream.\", \"target\": \"cream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奶油\", \"phrase\": \"ice cream|冰淇淋\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry that I've kept you waiting so long.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很长时间\", \"phrase\": \"so long|这么久\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll stop by the post office on the way home.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"post office|邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll stop by the post office on the way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on the way|在路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll drop by the post office on the way home.\", \"target\": \"drop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"顺便去\", \"phrase\": \"drop by|顺便去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll drop by the post office on the way home.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"post office|邮局\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll drop by the post office on the way home.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"on the way|在路上\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll always love you, no matter what happens.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"no matter what|无论如何\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder if you have something to write with.\", \"target\": \"write\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"write with|用笔写\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder if a third world war will break out.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"break out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder if a third world war will break out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"break out|爆发\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will make it clear that I won't come again.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"will make|将要...做\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to emphasize this point in particular.\", \"target\": \"particular\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"特别的\", \"phrase\": \"in particular|尤其\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told Tom that I thought it was a good idea.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good idea|好主意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told Tom I thought that it was a good idea.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"good idea|好主意\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you've mistaken me for somebody else.\", \"target\": \"mistaken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认错\", \"phrase\": \"mistaken for|认错\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think we've found what we were looking for.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"looking for|寻找\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's better for us to adopt his plan.\", \"target\": \"adopt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"采纳\", \"phrase\": \"adopt his plan|采纳他的计划\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I take a walk every day except when it rains.\", \"target\": \"except\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"除了\", \"phrase\": \"except when|除了...的时候\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I remember returning the book to the library.\", \"target\": \"returning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"归还\", \"phrase\": \"returning the book|归还书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I played tennis yesterday for the first time.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I played tennis yesterday for the first time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I played tennis for the first time yesterday.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一次\", \"phrase\": \"first time|第一次\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to give back the book before Saturday.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"give back|归还\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to give back the book before Saturday.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"give back|归还\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had intended to go shopping this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go shopping|购物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get a kick out of her cheerful personality.\", \"target\": \"kick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐趣\", \"phrase\": \"get a kick out of|从...中获得乐趣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get a kick out of her cheerful personality.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"从\", \"phrase\": \"get out of|从...中得到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that she looks like her mother.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"looks like|看起来像\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like his affected manner of speaking.\", \"target\": \"manner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"举止\", \"phrase\": \"manner of speaking|说话方式\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't know your reasons for not liking Tom.\", \"target\": \"liking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"not liking|不喜欢\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't feel like taking a walk this morning.\", \"target\": \"walk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"散步\", \"phrase\": \"taking a walk|散步\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not know whether to accept or to refuse.\", \"target\": \"refuse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拒绝\", \"phrase\": \"to refuse|拒绝\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't put up with her arrogant behavior.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忍受\", \"phrase\": \"put up with|忍受\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't enter because the door was closed.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"the door|门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't enter because the door was closed.\", \"target\": \"closed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"关闭的\", \"phrase\": \"was closed|门是关闭的\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I could hear birds singing outside my window.\", \"target\": \"singing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"唱歌\", \"phrase\": \"birds singing|鸟儿歌唱\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I could hear birds singing outside my window.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...外面\", \"phrase\": \"outside my window|在我的窗外\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am staying at the hotel for the time being.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"for the time being|暂时\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am going to stay here for a couple of days.\", \"target\": \"couple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"couple of days|几天\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hurry up, otherwise you'll be late for lunch.\", \"target\": \"otherwise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"否则\", \"phrase\": \"otherwise you'll be late|否则你会迟到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to walk to the station?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"take time|花费时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hemingway enjoyed big game hunting in Africa.\", \"target\": \"game\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游戏\", \"phrase\": \"game hunting|狩猎\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's the manager of the marketing department.\", \"target\": \"marketing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市场营销\", \"phrase\": \"marketing department|市场营销部门\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wrote a book about the American Civil War.\", \"target\": \"civil\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"内战的\", \"phrase\": \"Civil War|内战\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wrote a book about the American Civil War.\", \"target\": \"war\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"战争\", \"phrase\": \"Civil War|内战\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He studied hard in order to get into college.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"为了\", \"phrase\": \"in order to|为了\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He studied hard in order to get into college.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"get into|进入\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lost his balance and fell off his bicycle.\", \"target\": \"fell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摔倒\", \"phrase\": \"fell off|从...掉下来\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lost his balance and fell off his bicycle.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his bicycle|他的自行车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looked for every possible means of escape.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"possible means|可能的手段\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looked for every possible means of escape.\", \"target\": \"means\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方法\", \"phrase\": \"possible means|可能的方法\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He looked for every possible means of escape.\", \"target\": \"escape\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"逃跑\", \"phrase\": \"means of escape|逃脱的手段\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is as smart as any other boy in the class.\", \"target\": \"class\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"班级\", \"phrase\": \"in the class|在班级里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has not written to us since last February.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"since last February|自从上个月\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has not written to us since last February.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"last February|二月份\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He broke his word, which made his wife angry.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his wife|他的妻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He broke his word, which made his wife angry.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"broke his word|失信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He broke his word, which made his wife angry.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"made his wife angry|使他的妻子生气\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He broke his word, which made his wife angry.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his wife|他的妻子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me for opening your letter by mistake.\", \"target\": \"opening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"opening your letter|打开你的信\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eating habits differ from country to country.\", \"target\": \"country\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"country to country|国家与国家\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you take part in any community activities?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参加\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you take part in any community activities?\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参与\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参与\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know of any good restaurant near here?\", \"target\": \"near\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...附近\", \"phrase\": \"near here|在这里附近\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have your student identification card?\", \"target\": \"identification\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"身份证明\", \"phrase\": \"student identification card|学生证\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you help me translate this into French?\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"help me|帮助我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could you help me translate this into French?\", \"target\": \"translate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻译\", \"phrase\": \"translate into French|翻译成法语\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As long as you keep quiet, you can stay here.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"只要\", \"phrase\": \"as long as|只要...就\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As long as you keep quiet, you can stay here.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"keep quiet|保持安静; stay here|留在这里\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As everyone knows, air is a mixture of gases.\", \"target\": \"mixture\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"混合物\", \"phrase\": \"mixture of gases|气体混合物\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you planning to take part in the meeting?\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参加\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you planning to take part in the meeting?\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"take part in|参加\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Alcohol consumption is increasing every year.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"every year|每年\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After she had lunch, she got ready to go out.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"got ready|准备好\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After she had lunch, she got ready to go out.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After she had lunch, she got ready to go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"go out|出去\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A wise leader knows when to listen to others.\", \"target\": \"listen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"listen to others|听取别人的意见\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Did you watch TV last week?\\\" \\\"No, I didn't.\\\"\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"上个\", \"phrase\": \"last week|上周\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You smoke far too much. You should cut back.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"far too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You smoke far too much. You should cut back.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"far too much|太多\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You smoke far too much. You should cut back.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"减少\", \"phrase\": \"cut back|减少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You smoke far too much. You should cut back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"cut back|减少\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may not remember me, but I remember you.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"remember you|记得你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may not remember me, but I remember you.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"remember you|记得你\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You haven't washed your hands yet, have you?\", \"target\": \"washed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗过\", \"phrase\": \"washed your hands|洗你的手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You haven't washed your hands yet, have you?\", \"target\": \"hands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手\", \"phrase\": \"washed hands|洗手\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't understand this sentence, can you?\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"can't|不能\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Yesterday's board meeting was a big success.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big success|巨大的成功\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Yesterday's board meeting was a big success.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"big success|巨大的成功\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you please write with a ballpoint pen?\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笔\", \"phrase\": \"ballpoint pen|圆珠笔\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you please tell me a little about Tom?\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"would you please|请您\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you please tell me a little about Tom?\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"a little|一点儿\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you please look after my dog tomorrow?\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看顾\", \"phrase\": \"look after|照顾\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will the fine weather keep up till tomorrow?\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"keep up|保持\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will the fine weather keep up till tomorrow?\", \"target\": \"till\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"直到\", \"phrase\": \"keep up till|保持到\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which is better, red thread or white thread?\", \"target\": \"thread\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"red thread|红线\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which is better, red thread or white thread?\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"white thread|白色线\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which is better, red thread or white thread?\", \"target\": \"thread\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"线\", \"phrase\": \"red thread|红线\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's your impression of the United States?\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's your impression of the United States?\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What are you lingering for? Hurry up and go.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"快点\", \"phrase\": \"hurry up|快点\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't have class on Wednesday afternoons.\", \"target\": \"afternoons\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"下午\", \"phrase\": \"Wednesday afternoons|星期三下午\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wrote his name in the sand with a stick.\", \"target\": \"stick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"棍子\", \"phrase\": \"with a stick|用棍子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was embarrassed to have to ask for help.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"请求\", \"phrase\": \"ask for|请求\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was embarrassed to have to ask for help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"ask for help|寻求帮助\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that his father had passed away.\", \"target\": \"passed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去世\", \"phrase\": \"passed away|去世\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that his father had passed away.\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"去世\", \"phrase\": \"passed away|去世\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thinks Mary may have an eating disorder.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"eating disorder|饮食失调\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sells T-shirts at a 30 percent discount.\", \"target\": \"percent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"百分比\", \"phrase\": \"30 percent|30百分比\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom sells T-shirts at a 30 percent discount.\", \"target\": \"discount\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"折扣\", \"phrase\": \"30 percent discount|30%的折扣\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary looked very disappointed.\", \"target\": \"looked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"looked very disappointed|看起来很失望\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he wanted to try riding a unicycle.\", \"target\": \"riding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑行\", \"phrase\": \"riding a unicycle|骑单轮车\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has spent a lot of time studying French.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"a lot of time|很多时间\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom eats asparagus, but his brother doesn't.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"his brother|他的兄弟\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like being treated like a child.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"treated like a child|像个孩子一样对待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like being treated like a child.\", \"target\": \"treated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"对待\", \"phrase\": \"treated like|像...一样\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like being treated like a child.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"treated like a child|像个孩子一样对待\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like being treated like a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"like a child|像个孩子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can swim faster than anyone else I know.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"否则\", \"phrase\": \"faster than anyone else|比任何人都快\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked me to pick Mary up at the airport.\", \"target\": \"pick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捡起\", \"phrase\": \"pick up|接\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary always work together as a team.\", \"target\": \"together\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一起\", \"phrase\": \"work together|一起工作\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and Mary always work together as a team.\", \"target\": \"team\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"团队\", \"phrase\": \"as a team|作为一个团队\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They say there are ghosts in this old house.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"old house|老房子\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These are my books, and those are his books.\", \"target\": \"books\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"his books|他的书\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a cottage on the side of the hill.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"侧面\", \"phrase\": \"side of the hill|山坡的一侧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a cottage on the side of the hill.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"侧面\", \"phrase\": \"side of the hill|山坡的一侧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a cottage on the side of the hill.\", \"target\": \"side\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"侧面\", \"phrase\": \"side of the hill|山坡的一侧\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are no hats in that store that fit me.\", \"target\": \"fit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"适合\", \"phrase\": \"fit me|适合我\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are five patients in the waiting room.\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"waiting room|候诊室\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are fifty states in the United States.\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"United States|美国\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are fifty states in the United States.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"fifty states|五十个州\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The weather was not only cold, but also wet.\", \"target\": \"also\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"not only...but also|不仅仅...而且\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The prisoner was behind bars for two months.\", \"target\": \"behind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...后面\", \"phrase\": \"behind bars|身陷囹圄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The prisoner was behind bars for two months.\", \"target\": \"bars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"栅栏\", \"phrase\": \"behind bars|身陷囹圄\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm Tom's dad.\", \"target\": \"dad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爸爸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm Tom's dad.\", \"target\": \"dad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爸爸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on a diet.\", \"target\": \"diet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节食\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on my way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a big boy.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a big boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a shy boy.\", \"target\": \"shy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"害羞的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a shy boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't get it.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need it ASAP.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need it ASAP.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need it ASAP.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"尽快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to go.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to go.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see to it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see to it.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see to it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see to it.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a free man.\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自由的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a free man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a good guy.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a good guy.\", \"target\": \"guy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a nice guy.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a nice guy.\", \"target\": \"guy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good lad.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good lad.\", \"target\": \"lad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小伙子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a tall boy.\", \"target\": \"tall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a tall boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's not a hero.\", \"target\": \"hero\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"英雄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a good boy.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a good boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like it.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want it.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get up at six.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I get up at six.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lent him a CD.\", \"target\": \"lent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lent him a CD.\", \"target\": \"cd\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光盘\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's OK.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's OK.\", \"target\": \"ok\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you'd go.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you'd go.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you'd go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't be long.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't be long.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go by taxi.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go by taxi.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go by taxi.\", \"target\": \"taxi\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出租车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a good cook.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a good cook.\", \"target\": \"cook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a night owl.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"夜间的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm out of here.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm out of time.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm out of time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm so worn out.\", \"target\": \"worn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疲惫的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm so worn out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"精疲力尽的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a bike.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a bike.\", \"target\": \"bike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"自行车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a boat.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a boat.\", \"target\": \"boat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"船\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a bath.\", \"target\": \"bath\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洗澡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a nice day.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a nice day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's okay to go.\", \"target\": \"okay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's okay to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to go.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to go.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go by bus.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go by bus.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go by bus.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go by bus.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I try it on?\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I try it on?\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No, I didn't go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's on a diet.\", \"target\": \"diet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节食\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's on a diet.\", \"target\": \"diet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节食\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've got to go.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've got to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Am I in your way?\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I rest a bit?\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a TV?\", \"target\": \"tv\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电视\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you own a gun?\", \"target\": \"own\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拥有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you own a gun?\", \"target\": \"gun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"枪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't yell at me.\", \"target\": \"yell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喊\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ate all of it.\", \"target\": \"ate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a tall boy.\", \"target\": \"tall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a tall boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He isn't at home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told us a lie.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told us a lie.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told us a lie.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's new in town.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's new in town.\", \"target\": \"town\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城镇\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do I sign up?\", \"target\": \"sign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注册\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a bit drunk.\", \"target\": \"drunk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"醉的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am out of time.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"用完\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am out of time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't hear it.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't like it.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't mean it.\", \"target\": \"mean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"意​​思\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't see him.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't allow it.\", \"target\": \"allow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't do drugs.\", \"target\": \"drugs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"毒品\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't doubt it.\", \"target\": \"doubt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"怀疑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't hate you.\", \"target\": \"hate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"恨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't hate you.\", \"target\": \"hate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"恨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't know her.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like her.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like tea.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like tea.\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like you.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want you.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a flu shot.\", \"target\": \"flu\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"流感\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a flu shot.\", \"target\": \"shot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"注射\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a hard day.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"艰难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a hard day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a huge dog.\", \"target\": \"huge\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"巨大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a huge dog.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a new car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a new car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go now.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to say no.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know it's hard.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know it's hard.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I play in a band.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩; 演奏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I play in a band.\", \"target\": \"band\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐队\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'm lost.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'm lost.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"迷路的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to go.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't allow it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't allow it.\", \"target\": \"allow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll eat it here.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll eat it here.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm 30 years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm 30 years old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm Tom's father.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm Tom's father.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm able to swim.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm able to swim.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a doctor.\", \"target\": \"doctor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not busy now.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not like Tom.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not so brave.\", \"target\": \"brave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"勇敢的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not the boss.\", \"target\": \"boss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老板\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on the phone.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm proud of you.\", \"target\": \"proud\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"骄傲的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to die.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to die.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my key.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my key.\", \"target\": \"key\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钥匙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't a watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a clear day.\", \"target\": \"clear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晴朗的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a clear day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a clear day.\", \"target\": \"clear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晴朗的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a clear day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good deal.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good idea.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good idea.\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to say.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to say.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just a cold.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"感冒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not a watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not my size.\", \"target\": \"size\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"尺寸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's worth a try.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's worth a try.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's fly a kite.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's fly a kite.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's fly a kite.\", \"target\": \"fly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a bus.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a bus.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a bus.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's try it out.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's try it out.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's try it out.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is mad at me.\", \"target\": \"mad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is on a diet.\", \"target\": \"diet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节食\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is on a diet.\", \"target\": \"diet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节食\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's nice to me.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a fat man.\", \"target\": \"fat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"胖的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a fat man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't a fool.\", \"target\": \"fool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"傻瓜\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't a fool.\", \"target\": \"fool\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"傻瓜\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't a hero.\", \"target\": \"hero\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"英雄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're in a hurry.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're in my way.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"路\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got to go.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've got to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I have a bite?\", \"target\": \"bite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一口\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I try this on?\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come on, let's go.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"来吧\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come on, let's go.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come on, let's go.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come on, let's go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a car?\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a car?\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a map?\", \"target\": \"map\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地图\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat so fast.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let Tom die.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let Tom die.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't shout at me.\", \"target\": \"shout\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喊\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came to see me.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came to see me.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave me a cold.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave me a cold.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a few pens.\", \"target\": \"pens\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a big eater.\", \"target\": \"eater\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"吃货\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is at his desk.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is at his desk.\", \"target\": \"desk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"桌子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is but a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is just my age.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made me a suit.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He made me a suit.\", \"target\": \"suit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西装\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a bit lively.\", \"target\": \"lively\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"活泼的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's not an idiot.\", \"target\": \"idiot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白痴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's not here yet.\", \"target\": \"yet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His room's a mess.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His room's a mess.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His room's a mess.\", \"target\": \"mess\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"混乱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do we find it?\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I admit I'm wrong.\", \"target\": \"admit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"承认\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I admit I'm wrong.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am fond of cars.\", \"target\": \"fond\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"喜爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am fond of cars.\", \"target\": \"cars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am in the house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am on the right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't feel bad.\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't feel bad.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do all the work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't accept it.\", \"target\": \"accept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't blame you.\", \"target\": \"blame\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"责怪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't eat bread.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't eat bread.\", \"target\": \"bread\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"面包\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't feel well.\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't feel well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like dogs.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like dogs.\", \"target\": \"dogs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like eggs.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like eggs.\", \"target\": \"eggs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸡蛋\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like eggs.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like eggs.\", \"target\": \"eggs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸡蛋\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like kids.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like kids.\", \"target\": \"kids\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like that.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like this.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like wine.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like wine.\", \"target\": \"wine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"葡萄酒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't regret it.\", \"target\": \"regret\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"后悔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave you a book.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave you a book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a bee sting.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a bee sting.\", \"target\": \"bee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蜜蜂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got my hair cut.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got my hair cut.\", \"target\": \"hair\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头发\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got my hair cut.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"剪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got up at seven.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got up at seven.\", \"target\": \"seven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"七\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had lost my pen.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't met her.\", \"target\": \"met\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope to see you.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope to see you.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just don't know.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like snow a lot.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like snow a lot.\", \"target\": \"snow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like snow a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made Tom eat it.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made Tom eat it.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go home.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe you so much.\", \"target\": \"owe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe you so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sat by his side.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sat by his side.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sat next to him.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sent her a doll.\", \"target\": \"sent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发送\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'll stay.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'll stay.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'll stay.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'm right.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I'm right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's fine.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's fine.\", \"target\": \"fine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took off my wig.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"脱下\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want Tom to win.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want Tom to win.\", \"target\": \"win\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a lot more.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a lot more.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to do more.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go home.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to read it.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to read it.\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to see Tom.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to see Tom.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will do my best.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will do my best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could go.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could go.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I woke up at 2:30.\", \"target\": \"woke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"醒来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't be fooled.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't be fooled.\", \"target\": \"fooled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被愚弄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't leave you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't leave you.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work for a bank.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work for a bank.\", \"target\": \"bank\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"银行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to dance.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to dance.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to dance.\", \"target\": \"dance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跳舞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd wear a helmet.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd wear a helmet.\", \"target\": \"wear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿戴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd wear a helmet.\", \"target\": \"helmet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头盔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be back late.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be back late.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be back late.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll feed the dog.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll feed the dog.\", \"target\": \"feed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喂养\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll feed the dog.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go by myself.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll go by myself.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll pay the bill.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll pay the bill.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll pay the bill.\", \"target\": \"bill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"账单\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll tell my wife.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll tell my wife.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll tell my wife.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a good person.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a good person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a new student.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a new student.\", \"target\": \"student\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm able to speak.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm able to speak.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid to die.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid to die.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm an only child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm bad at sports.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm bad at sports.\", \"target\": \"sports\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运动\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad we agree.\", \"target\": \"glad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad we agree.\", \"target\": \"agree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"同意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to lose.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to lose.\", \"target\": \"lose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"输\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a student.\", \"target\": \"student\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not too smart.\", \"target\": \"smart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"聪明的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've done my best.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is not a watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a warm day.\", \"target\": \"warm\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"温暖的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a warm day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good start.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good start.\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a long story.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a long story.\", \"target\": \"story\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"故事\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's all my fault.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's already 7:00.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hot out here.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just a dream.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"梦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's just a dream.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"梦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's my brother's.\", \"target\": \"brother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"兄弟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not my fault.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not that far.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"远的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's only a dream.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"梦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's only a dream.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"梦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time for bed.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time for bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to talk.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to talk.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's too late now.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's warm in here.\", \"target\": \"warm\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"暖和\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to lie.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me have a try.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me have a try.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get to work.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get to work.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get to work.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get to work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a look.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a look.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a look.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a look.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a rest.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a rest.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a rest.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take a rest.\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I put it here?\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I put it here?\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She didn't go far.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She didn't go far.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's in the bath.\", \"target\": \"bath\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"浴缸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's not a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That isn't my job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's all I said.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's not my job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is Tom's car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This isn't my car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This isn't my key.\", \"target\": \"key\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钥匙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave me a pen.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave me a pen.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a bit pale.\", \"target\": \"pale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"苍白的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a good guy.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a good guy.\", \"target\": \"guy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a good guy.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a good guy.\", \"target\": \"guy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a true man.\", \"target\": \"true\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a true man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom made me do it.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wasn't in bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's face is red.\", \"target\": \"face\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's face is red.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Use it or lose it.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't think so.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We hope Tom is OK.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We hope Tom is OK.\", \"target\": \"ok\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're all at risk.\", \"target\": \"risk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风险\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're all at risk.\", \"target\": \"risk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风险\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are a bit fat.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are a bit fat.\", \"target\": \"fat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"胖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You won't need it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You won't need it.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll find a job.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll find a job.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll find a job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're free to go.\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自由的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're free to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've done a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of us like her.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All of us like her.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you mad at Tom?\", \"target\": \"mad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you out of bed?\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I call you Tom?\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I call you Tom?\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I see that one?\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I see this one?\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I use your pen?\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I use your pen?\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can we go back now?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can we go back now?\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come in, it's open.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you tell on me?\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do I sound in love?\", \"target\": \"sound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听起来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do I sound in love?\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a bike?\", \"target\": \"bike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"自行车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does it hurt a lot?\", \"target\": \"hurt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"疼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does it hurt a lot?\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat too much.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't make me wait.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't make me wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't miss the bus.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't miss the bus.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you feel hot?\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you feel hot?\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you think so?\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He called me a cab.\", \"target\": \"called\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can drive a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can't buy a car.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can't buy a car.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He can't buy a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He found me a taxi.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He found me a taxi.\", \"target\": \"taxi\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出租车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave him a book.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He gave him a book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He got off the bus.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He got off the bus.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a long neck.\", \"target\": \"neck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脖子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He hasn't come yet.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He hasn't come yet.\", \"target\": \"yet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a bad driver.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a bad driver.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at golf.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at golf.\", \"target\": \"golf\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"高尔夫球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lay on his back.\", \"target\": \"lay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"躺\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lay on his back.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lay on his back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"背部\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lied to my face.\", \"target\": \"lied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撒谎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He lied to my face.\", \"target\": \"face\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"脸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took a week off.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He took a week off.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll be done soon.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll be done soon.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll wait for you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll wait for you.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a fast walker.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"快的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a fast walker.\", \"target\": \"walker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"步行者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good fellow.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good fellow.\", \"target\": \"fellow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good fellow.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good fellow.\", \"target\": \"fellow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good person.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good person.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a good person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a little pale.\", \"target\": \"pale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"苍白的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a meth addict.\", \"target\": \"addict\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"瘾君子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's already a man.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's already a man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's my new friend.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's my new friend.\", \"target\": \"friend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did he find us?\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did he find us?\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do you like it?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do you like it?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a new student.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a new student.\", \"target\": \"student\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am an only child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am not a student.\", \"target\": \"student\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am not a teacher.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am six feet tall.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am six feet tall.\", \"target\": \"tall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bathe once a day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can help you out.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can wait for you.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't buy bread.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't buy bread.\", \"target\": \"bread\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"面包\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't mean that.\", \"target\": \"mean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"意指\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't tell them.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't want this.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't fear death.\", \"target\": \"fear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't fear death.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a cat.\", \"target\": \"cat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a dog.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like sushi.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't sleep well.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't sleep well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't smoke weed.\", \"target\": \"smoke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吸烟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't smoke weed.\", \"target\": \"weed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大麻\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't take drugs.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"服用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't take drugs.\", \"target\": \"drugs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"毒品\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feel like a rest.\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feel like a rest.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I feel like a rest.\", \"target\": \"rest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave Mary a book.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave Mary a book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave you my word.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I gave you my word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I give you my word.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I give you my word.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got up about six.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got up about six.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐趣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had him write it.\", \"target\": \"write\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my cap.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my cap.\", \"target\": \"cap\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帽子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my cap.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my cap.\", \"target\": \"cap\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帽子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my key.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my key.\", \"target\": \"key\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钥匙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to call Tom.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to paint it.\", \"target\": \"paint\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"油漆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to say this.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard him go out.\", \"target\": \"heard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard him go out.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard him go out.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope we find Tom.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope we find Tom.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know what he did.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know what to say.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know what to say.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lead a busy life.\", \"target\": \"lead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"领导; 引领\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lead a busy life.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙碌的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lead a busy life.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to eat meat.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to eat meat.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to eat meat.\", \"target\": \"meat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"肉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met an old woman.\", \"target\": \"met\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met an old woman.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I met an old woman.\", \"target\": \"woman\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss her so much.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss her so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you so much.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you so much.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I plan to go there.\", \"target\": \"plan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I plan to go there.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him run away.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him run away.\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw what Tom did.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw what Tom did.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I slept on the bus.\", \"target\": \"slept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I slept on the bus.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I still don't care.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I still don't care.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"在乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I swim once a week.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I swim once a week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I love you.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I love you.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think he'll come.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think he'll come.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think he'll come.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think he's happy.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think he's happy.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"快乐的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried not to cry.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried not to cry.\", \"target\": \"cry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"哭\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wake up at eight.\", \"target\": \"wake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"醒来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wake up at eight.\", \"target\": \"eight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"八\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want Tom to wait.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want Tom to wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go there.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go there.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to meet Tom.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to meet Tom.\", \"target\": \"meet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was at home then.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was born in 1988.\", \"target\": \"born\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I watch TV all day.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I watch TV all day.\", \"target\": \"tv\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电视\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I watch TV all day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will go on ahead.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will go on ahead.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will go on ahead.\", \"target\": \"ahead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I had a car.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I had a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I were rich.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I were rich.\", \"target\": \"rich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富有 (fùyǒu)\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd better go home.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd better go home.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd better go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd better go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like your help.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like your help.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like your help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be seeing you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be seeing you.\", \"target\": \"seeing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call Tom back.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you back.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you back.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll get some help.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll get some help.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll get some help.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have the same.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll just sit here.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll just sit here.\", \"target\": \"sit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll keep doing it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll keep doing it.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll miss you, too.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll miss you, too.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never make it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never make it.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never make it.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll ride with Tom.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll ride with Tom.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"骑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see you later.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see you later.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll see you later.\", \"target\": \"later\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍后\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll think it over.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll think it over.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"思考\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a little tired.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有点儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a little tired.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"累的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid of dogs.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid of dogs.\", \"target\": \"dogs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm as tall as you.\", \"target\": \"tall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm engaged to her.\", \"target\": \"engaged\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"订婚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad it's over.\", \"target\": \"glad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to check.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to check.\", \"target\": \"check\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"检查\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at skiing.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at skiing.\", \"target\": \"skiing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"滑雪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at soccer.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at soccer.\", \"target\": \"soccer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"足球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at tennis.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at tennis.\", \"target\": \"tennis\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"网球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm losing my grip.\", \"target\": \"losing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"失去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm making a movie.\", \"target\": \"making\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm making a movie.\", \"target\": \"movie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电影\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a dictator.\", \"target\": \"dictator\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"独裁者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not quite well.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not quite well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to leave.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm ready to leave.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm scared of dogs.\", \"target\": \"scared\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"害怕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm scared of dogs.\", \"target\": \"dogs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I'm late.\", \"target\": \"sorry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"对不起\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I'm late.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I'm late.\", \"target\": \"sorry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"对不起\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I'm late.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm too busy to go.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm too busy to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got to go now.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got to go now.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my watch.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never met her.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never met her.\", \"target\": \"met\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never met him.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never met him.\", \"target\": \"met\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is easy to swim.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is easy to swim.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was just a joke.\", \"target\": \"joke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玩笑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It wasn't my fault.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't cost much.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't cost much.\", \"target\": \"cost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't cost much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't take long.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't take long.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It won't take long.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a bad example.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a bad example.\", \"target\": \"example\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"例子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's about to rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's fun to travel.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有趣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's fun to travel.\", \"target\": \"travel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's fun to travel.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有趣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's fun to travel.\", \"target\": \"travel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's going to rain.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"将要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's going to rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to leave.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to leave.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to sleep.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's time to sleep.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me have a look.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me have a look.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get off here.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get off here.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's get off here.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's not watch TV.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's not watch TV.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's not watch TV.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's not watch TV.\", \"target\": \"tv\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电视\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take it easy.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take it easy.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take it easy.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take the bus.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take the bus.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's take the bus.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Look at my new car.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Look at my new car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Look at my new car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I open the box?\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I open the box?\", \"target\": \"box\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盒子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I pay by check?\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I pay by check?\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I run with you?\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I run with you?\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car isn't brown.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car isn't brown.\", \"target\": \"brown\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"棕色的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife is at home.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife is at home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one can help me.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one can help me.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one can help me.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one can help me.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one will see us.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one will see us.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one will see us.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No one will see us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Oh! That's too bad.\", \"target\": \"oh\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"哦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Oh! That's too bad.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made me a cake.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made me a cake.\", \"target\": \"cake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蛋糕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She put on her hat.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She put on her hat.\", \"target\": \"hat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帽子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She sat next to me.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She so wants to go.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She so wants to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's Tom's sister.\", \"target\": \"sister\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妹妹\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's Tom's sister.\", \"target\": \"sister\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妹妹\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's just a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's only a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tell Tom I'm sorry.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tell Tom I'm sorry.\", \"target\": \"sorry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"抱歉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tell me what to do.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That isn't my wife.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a good idea!\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a good idea!\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a good idea.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a good idea.\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a good plan.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a good plan.\", \"target\": \"plan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a nice coat.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a nice coat.\", \"target\": \"coat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"外套\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"deal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交易;协议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's not my wife.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's what I hope.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's what I like.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's what I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car hit a wall.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car hit a wall.\", \"target\": \"hit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"撞击\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The car hit a wall.\", \"target\": \"wall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"墙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lid won't open.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They didn't pay me.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They didn't see us.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They didn't see us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They don't like me.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They won't hurt us.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They won't hurt us.\", \"target\": \"hurt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伤害\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They won't hurt us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This boy is my son.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This boy is my son.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is Mary's dog.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is all I know.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is not my car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom has an old car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a good cook.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a good cook.\", \"target\": \"cook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't a racist.\", \"target\": \"racist\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"种族主义者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't an angel.\", \"target\": \"angel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't an idiot.\", \"target\": \"idiot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白痴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't an idiot.\", \"target\": \"idiot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白痴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom isn't done yet.\", \"target\": \"yet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom made fun of me.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he'd wait.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he'd wait.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he'd wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went to Mary's.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom won't be happy.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom won't be happy.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's door is open.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's door is open.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"打开的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't have time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like rain.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't trust Tom.\", \"target\": \"trust\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"信任\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We ran in the park.\", \"target\": \"ran\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We ran in the park.\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公园\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We want to go home.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We want to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We want to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We want to hear it.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We want to hear it.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're the same age.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What a lot of pens!\", \"target\": \"pens\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What an idiot I am!\", \"target\": \"idiot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白痴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's in this bag?\", \"target\": \"bag\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"包\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why are you so mad?\", \"target\": \"mad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why do I even care?\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"甚至\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why do I even care?\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why do you hate me?\", \"target\": \"hate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"恨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why do you love me?\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why do you need it?\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will I have a scar?\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Will I have a scar?\", \"target\": \"scar\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"伤疤\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to go.\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自由的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to go.\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"自由的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You are free to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You did a good job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You don't scare us.\", \"target\": \"scare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吓唬\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You don't scare us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You know I'm right.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You know I'm right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You owe me a favor.\", \"target\": \"owe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You owe me a favor.\", \"target\": \"favor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"恩惠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're a good cook.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're a good cook.\", \"target\": \"cook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Am I a good teacher?\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Am I a good teacher?\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ask Tom to help you.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ask Tom to help you.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Best of luck to you.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Best of luck to you.\", \"target\": \"luck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"But I don't want to.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"But I wasn't afraid.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"害怕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I have some tea?\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I still make it?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I still make it?\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you drive a car?\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you drive a car?\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you rub my back?\", \"target\": \"rub\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"擦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you rub my back?\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"背部\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I try this on?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I try this on?\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you tell on Tom?\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you go to church?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you go to church?\", \"target\": \"church\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教堂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a child?\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a cough?\", \"target\": \"cough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"咳嗽\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a fever?\", \"target\": \"fever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"发烧\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a knife?\", \"target\": \"knife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"刀\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you keep a diary?\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you keep a diary?\", \"target\": \"diary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"日记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know my name?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know my name?\", \"target\": \"name\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you like to read?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you like to read?\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阅读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you share a room?\", \"target\": \"share\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分享\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you share a room?\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you share a room?\", \"target\": \"share\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分享\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you share a room?\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you share a room?\", \"target\": \"share\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分享\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you share a room?\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want a drink?\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want a drink?\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"饮料\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to know?\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to know?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to wait?\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you want to wait?\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does Tom have a job?\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't drop this cup.\", \"target\": \"cup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"杯子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let Tom leave.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let Tom leave.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't listen to her.\", \"target\": \"listen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't stand near me.\", \"target\": \"stand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"站\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry so much.\", \"target\": \"worry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"担心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you feel cold?\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you feel cold?\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't you know that?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me, I'm lost.\", \"target\": \"excuse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"打扰一下\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Excuse me, I'm lost.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"迷路的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get out of my house.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Get out of my house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He did it for money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He didn't know that.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He does not like us.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He does not like us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has his own room.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has his own room.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has lost his job.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has lost his job.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has lost his job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is a learned man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is at home today.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is at home today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at rugby.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is good at rugby.\", \"target\": \"rugby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"橄榄球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is my old friend.\", \"target\": \"friend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is my old friend.\", \"target\": \"friend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is telling a lie.\", \"target\": \"telling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"讲述\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left an hour ago.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left an hour ago.\", \"target\": \"hour\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He left an hour ago.\", \"target\": \"ago\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"以前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may not be happy.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may not be happy.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"快乐的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sat on the bench.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He sat on the bench.\", \"target\": \"bench\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"长凳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems to be rich.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems to be rich.\", \"target\": \"rich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems to be sick.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems to be sick.\", \"target\": \"sick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was wet all over.\", \"target\": \"wet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"湿的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll never beat me.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll never beat me.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He'll never beat me.\", \"target\": \"beat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打败\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a Japanese boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's afraid of dogs.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"害怕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's afraid of dogs.\", \"target\": \"dogs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's doing his best.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"kitchen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨房\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's the oldest son.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's the oldest son.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her son is a genius.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her son is a genius.\", \"target\": \"genius\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天才\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How I've missed you!\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How can I get there?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How can I reach you?\", \"target\": \"reach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How can I reach you?\", \"target\": \"reach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How can we save Tom?\", \"target\": \"save\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拯救\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do you feel now?\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How far away are we?\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多远\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How far away are we?\", \"target\": \"away\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How is it at school?\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much will it be?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much will it be?\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much will it be?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much will it be?\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How old is this zoo?\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How old is your son?\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How old is your son?\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am afraid of dogs.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am afraid of dogs.\", \"target\": \"dogs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am engaged to her.\", \"target\": \"engaged\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"订婚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am in Tokyo today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ate a hasty lunch.\", \"target\": \"ate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ate a hasty lunch.\", \"target\": \"lunch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"午餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I built a new house.\", \"target\": \"built\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建造\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I built a new house.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I built a new house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can come at three.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can come at three.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can help you, too.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can see the light.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can see the light.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can win this time.\", \"target\": \"win\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can win this time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't find my bag.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't find my bag.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't find my bag.\", \"target\": \"bag\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"包\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't find my pen.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't find my pen.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't find my pen.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't swim at all.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't swim at all.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't hear you.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't hear you.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't order this.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"订购\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't see anyone.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't see anyone.\", \"target\": \"anyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not have a cat.\", \"target\": \"cat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not sleep well.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not sleep well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't eat oranges.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't eat oranges.\", \"target\": \"oranges\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"橙子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a bike.\", \"target\": \"bike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"自行车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like movies.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like movies.\", \"target\": \"movies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电影\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like school.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like summer.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like summer.\", \"target\": \"summer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夏天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like winter.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like winter.\", \"target\": \"winter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冬天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't need anyone.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't need anyone.\", \"target\": \"anyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't see why not.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to eat.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to eat.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to ask Tom.\", \"target\": \"forgot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to ask Tom.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to ask him.\", \"target\": \"forgot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to ask him.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to ask him.\", \"target\": \"forgot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to ask him.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I give you my heart.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I give you my heart.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got home at seven.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got home at seven.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got home at seven.\", \"target\": \"seven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"七\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I grew up in Boston.\", \"target\": \"grew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"长大\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a high fever.\", \"target\": \"fever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"发烧\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to leave now.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to stay home.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to stay home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope you can come.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope you can come.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just need a break.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just need a break.\", \"target\": \"break\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"休息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know Tom is tired.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know Tom is tired.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疲倦的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know none of them.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know none of them.\", \"target\": \"none\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know what you did.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know where she is.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you're upset.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you're upset.\", \"target\": \"upset\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"难过的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like each of them.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like movies a lot.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like movies a lot.\", \"target\": \"movies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电影\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like movies a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live in this area.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live in this area.\", \"target\": \"area\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区域\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live too far away.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need a bigger box.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need a bigger box.\", \"target\": \"box\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盒子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really don't care.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really don't care.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"在乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really don't sing.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really don't sing.\", \"target\": \"sing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"唱歌\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really have to go.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I really have to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him last week.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw him last week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I simply don't know.\", \"target\": \"simply\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仅仅\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I simply don't know.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I slept on the sofa.\", \"target\": \"slept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is good.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is good.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think we're ready.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think we're ready.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you're dumb.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you're dumb.\", \"target\": \"dumb\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"愚蠢的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told Tom I was OK.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I told Tom I was OK.\", \"target\": \"ok\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried to tell you.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I tried to tell you.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want Tom to do it.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to get drunk.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to get drunk.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to get drunk.\", \"target\": \"drunk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"醉的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go abroad.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go abroad.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go abroad.\", \"target\": \"abroad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"国外\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to live here.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to live here.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to take part.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to take part.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to take part.\", \"target\": \"part\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部分\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to relax.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want you to relax.\", \"target\": \"relax\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放松\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wasn't alone then.\", \"target\": \"alone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"独自的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will try it again.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will try it again.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could swim.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could swim.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could swim.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I were young.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I were young.\", \"target\": \"young\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年轻的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't abandon you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't abandon you.\", \"target\": \"abandon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放弃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't accept that.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't accept that.\", \"target\": \"accept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't do it again.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't stay silent.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't stay silent.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't stay silent.\", \"target\": \"silent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"沉默的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work in a factory.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work in a factory.\", \"target\": \"factory\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工厂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wrote it all down.\", \"target\": \"wrote\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to do more.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to do more.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd rather avoid it.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd rather avoid it.\", \"target\": \"rather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"宁愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd rather avoid it.\", \"target\": \"avoid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"避免\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be back at ten.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be back at ten.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be back at ten.\", \"target\": \"ten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be right there.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be right there.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"马上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you later.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you later.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll call you later.\", \"target\": \"later\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍后\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll do it tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll do it tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll drive you home.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll drive you home.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll drive you home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll join you later.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll join you later.\", \"target\": \"join\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"加入\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll join you later.\", \"target\": \"later\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍后\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll let you decide.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll let you decide.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll let you decide.\", \"target\": \"decide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"决定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll make you happy.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll make you happy.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll make you happy.\", \"target\": \"happy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"快乐的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll return at 6:30.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll return at 6:30.\", \"target\": \"return\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"返回\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm Tom's assistant.\", \"target\": \"assistant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"助手\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a social worker.\", \"target\": \"social\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"社会的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a social worker.\", \"target\": \"worker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm a stranger here.\", \"target\": \"stranger\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"陌生人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid of death.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid of death.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid of dying.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm afraid of dying.\", \"target\": \"dying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm as old as he is.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm counting on you.\", \"target\": \"counting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm crazy about you.\", \"target\": \"crazy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疯狂的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm crazy about you.\", \"target\": \"crazy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疯狂的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm dying of thirst.\", \"target\": \"thirst\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"口渴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm eating rice now.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm eating rice now.\", \"target\": \"rice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"米饭\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to school.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going to school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at singing.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm good at singing.\", \"target\": \"singing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"唱歌\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for you.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a bit tired.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"累的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a policeman.\", \"target\": \"policeman\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not well at all.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not your mother.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not your mother.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm on the roof now.\", \"target\": \"roof\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"屋顶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm poor at drawing.\", \"target\": \"poor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"差的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm poor at drawing.\", \"target\": \"drawing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绘画\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm prepared to die.\", \"target\": \"prepared\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm prepared to die.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm proud of my son.\", \"target\": \"proud\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"骄傲的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm proud of my son.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sad without you.\", \"target\": \"sad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"悲伤的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sick of English.\", \"target\": \"sick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的;恶心的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm stuck in my job.\", \"target\": \"stuck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"卡住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm stuck in my job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm to blame for it.\", \"target\": \"blame\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"责备\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm very busy today.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm very busy today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm very hungry now.\", \"target\": \"hungry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"饥饿的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm waiting for him.\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm watching TV now.\", \"target\": \"watching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm watching TV now.\", \"target\": \"tv\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电视\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been in prison.\", \"target\": \"prison\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"监狱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a headache.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a headache.\", \"target\": \"headache\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头痛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got no friends.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got no friends.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got work to do.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got work to do.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a busy day.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙碌的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a busy day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just had lunch.\", \"target\": \"lunch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"午餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my pencil.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my pencil.\", \"target\": \"pencil\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"铅笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my ticket.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my ticket.\", \"target\": \"ticket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"票\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've lost my wallet.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've made a mistake.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've made a mistake.\", \"target\": \"mistake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've made a mistake.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"犯了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've made a mistake.\", \"target\": \"mistake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've missed so much.\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've missed so much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've seen Tom naked.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've seen Tom naked.\", \"target\": \"naked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"裸体的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is it far from here?\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"远的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It hasn't been easy.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't spring yet.\", \"target\": \"spring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"春天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't spring yet.\", \"target\": \"yet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a cold night.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a cold night.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a lot of fun.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐趣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a nice story.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a nice story.\", \"target\": \"story\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"故事\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was just a dream.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"梦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was only a dream.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"梦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It wasn't that cold.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冷\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It'll rain for sure.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It'll rain for sure.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It'll rain for sure.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"肯定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a modern house.\", \"target\": \"modern\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"现代的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a modern house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a real bargain.\", \"target\": \"real\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a real bargain.\", \"target\": \"bargain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"便宜货\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's all your fault.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not bugging me.\", \"target\": \"bugging\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"烦扰\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not spring yet.\", \"target\": \"spring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"春天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not spring yet.\", \"target\": \"yet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not your style.\", \"target\": \"style\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"风格\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's safe to say so.\", \"target\": \"safe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"安全\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's safe to say so.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very hot today.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very hot today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's worth the wait.\", \"target\": \"worth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"值得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's worth the wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's call it a day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go over there.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go over there.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go over there.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go to a movie.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go to a movie.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go to a movie.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's go to a movie.\", \"target\": \"movie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电影\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let's keep in touch.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I eat that cake?\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I eat that cake?\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"May I eat that cake?\", \"target\": \"cake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蛋糕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My dad will kill me.\", \"target\": \"dad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爸爸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My dad will kill me.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My home is far away.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My home is far away.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"遥远\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My nose is so itchy.\", \"target\": \"nose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鼻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My room is a pigsty.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife is a doctor.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife is a doctor.\", \"target\": \"doctor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One of us has to go.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One of us has to go.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One of us has to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Roll the ball to me.\", \"target\": \"roll\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"滚动\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Roll the ball to me.\", \"target\": \"ball\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"See you in two days.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"See you in two days.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"See you in two days.\", \"target\": \"days\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She didn't like him.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She didn't think so.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave me a watch.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She gave me a watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She got in at 9 p.m.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is a mere child.\", \"target\": \"mere\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"仅仅的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is a mere child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is about my age.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is just a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is only a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is still a girl.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is still a girl.\", \"target\": \"girl\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made tea for me.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made tea for me.\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made tea for me.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She made tea for me.\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She went for a walk.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's wearing a hat.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's wearing a hat.\", \"target\": \"hat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帽子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sing a song with me.\", \"target\": \"sing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"唱歌\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sing a song with me.\", \"target\": \"song\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"歌曲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of my room.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stay out of my room.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop, or I'll shoot.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop, or I'll shoot.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Stop, or I'll shoot.\", \"target\": \"shoot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"射击\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That wasn't too bad.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's Tom's mother.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a great poem.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"伟大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a great poem.\", \"target\": \"poem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"诗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a small tree.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's a small tree.\", \"target\": \"tree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's true as well.\", \"target\": \"true\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That's true as well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The cat is not dead.\", \"target\": \"cat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The cat is not dead.\", \"target\": \"dead\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"死了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The door won't open.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The door won't open.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The soup is too hot.\", \"target\": \"soup\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汤\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The soup is too hot.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There's a book here.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They don't like Tom.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They don't like you.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They won't find Tom.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They won't find Tom.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a bad thing.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a bad thing.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a great day.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"伟大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a great day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is my father's.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is my own bike.\", \"target\": \"bike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"自行车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is what I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This won't help you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This won't help you.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tokyo is a big city.\", \"target\": \"big\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tokyo is a big city.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't tie a tie.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like me.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom found me a taxi.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom found me a taxi.\", \"target\": \"taxi\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出租车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom hid in the shed.\", \"target\": \"hid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"藏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is 30 years old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is Mary's uncle.\", \"target\": \"uncle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"叔叔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a bus driver.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a bus driver.\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a clever kid.\", \"target\": \"clever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"聪明的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a clever kid.\", \"target\": \"kid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a decent guy.\", \"target\": \"decent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"体面的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a decent guy.\", \"target\": \"guy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a little boy.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a little boy.\", \"target\": \"boy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a strong guy.\", \"target\": \"strong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"强壮的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is a strong guy.\", \"target\": \"guy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家伙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is in the house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is in the house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is not an idiot.\", \"target\": \"idiot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白痴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is not an idiot.\", \"target\": \"idiot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白痴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom knows it's over.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom lives in a slum.\", \"target\": \"lives\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"居住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom made me do that.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom owes us a favor.\", \"target\": \"owes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom owes us a favor.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom owes us a favor.\", \"target\": \"favor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"恩惠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he's tired.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he's tired.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疲倦的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to see us.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to see us.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to see us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was a real hero.\", \"target\": \"real\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was a real hero.\", \"target\": \"hero\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"英雄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was on the list.\", \"target\": \"list\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"列表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom won't be coming.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom won't be coming.\", \"target\": \"coming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's eyes are blue.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's eyes are blue.\", \"target\": \"blue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"蓝色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's room is dirty.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's room is dirty.\", \"target\": \"dirty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"脏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Try not to get lost.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Try not to get lost.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Try not to get lost.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"迷路的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Wake me up at seven.\", \"target\": \"wake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫醒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Wake me up at seven.\", \"target\": \"seven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"七\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We couldn't do that.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have seen no one.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have seen no one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We just need a plan.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We just need a plan.\", \"target\": \"plan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We swam in the lake.\", \"target\": \"swam\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We swam in the lake.\", \"target\": \"lake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"湖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were born to die.\", \"target\": \"born\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were born to die.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've not done well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What did he ask you?\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What if Tom says no?\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What is on the desk?\", \"target\": \"desk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"桌子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What made her do so?\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What time is it now?\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's Tom given us?\", \"target\": \"given\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's Tom given us?\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's Tom's excuse?\", \"target\": \"excuse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"借口\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's it made from?\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's the time now?\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's today's date?\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's today's date?\", \"target\": \"date\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"日期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When did you buy it?\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Where's Tom's stuff?\", \"target\": \"stuff\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who did you talk to?\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who do you work for?\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who is that old man?\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who is that old man?\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who's on duty today?\", \"target\": \"duty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"值班\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Who's on duty today?\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why am I still here?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why did you sell it?\", \"target\": \"sell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why do you say that?\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why is the sky blue?\", \"target\": \"sky\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天空\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why is the sky blue?\", \"target\": \"blue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"蓝色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why isn't that good?\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can rely on him.\", \"target\": \"rely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can shut up now.\", \"target\": \"shut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"闭嘴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have a good job.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to go home.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You have to go home.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may go home now.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may go home now.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may go home now.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may not come in.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may not come in.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better go now.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better go now.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better go now.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better not go.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better not go.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'd better not go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're not a doctor.\", \"target\": \"doctor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're not too late.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've gone too far.\", \"target\": \"gone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've gone too far.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太远\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A cup of tea, please.\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A cup of tea, please.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All we need is water.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All we need is water.\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"水\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are we going to lose?\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are we going to lose?\", \"target\": \"lose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"输\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you Tom's mother?\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you able to swim?\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you able to swim?\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you able to swim?\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you able to swim?\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you angry at Tom?\", \"target\": \"angry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you busy at work?\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you going or not?\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you good at math?\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Are you good at math?\", \"target\": \"math\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Be quiet, all of you.\", \"target\": \"quiet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"安静的 (ānjìng de)\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Bring me a dry towel.\", \"target\": \"bring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Bring me a dry towel.\", \"target\": \"dry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"干的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Bring me a dry towel.\", \"target\": \"towel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"毛巾\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I ask a question?\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I ask a question?\", \"target\": \"question\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I use your phone?\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can I use your phone?\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you guess my age?\", \"target\": \"guess\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"猜\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you guess my age?\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you ride a horse?\", \"target\": \"horse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you ride a horse?\", \"target\": \"horse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"马\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cats hate to get wet.\", \"target\": \"cats\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cats hate to get wet.\", \"target\": \"hate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"恨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cats hate to get wet.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cats hate to get wet.\", \"target\": \"wet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"湿的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Come and take a look.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I get some tea?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I get some tea?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I get some tea?\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I try to do it?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Could I try to do it?\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did I miss the party?\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did I miss the party?\", \"target\": \"party\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"派对\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did Tom talk to Mary?\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you buy cat food?\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you buy cat food?\", \"target\": \"cat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you buy cat food?\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you get up early?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you get up early?\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"早\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you go to school?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Did you go to school?\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Didn't I tell you so?\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you eat out often?\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you eat out often?\", \"target\": \"often\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"经常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you get up at six?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you get up at six?\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a camera?\", \"target\": \"camera\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"相机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a garage?\", \"target\": \"garage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车库\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you have a pencil?\", \"target\": \"pencil\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"铅笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know Tom well?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you run every day?\", \"target\": \"run\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you run every day?\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you run every day?\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you still like me?\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you still like me?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't be so careless!\", \"target\": \"careless\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"粗心大意的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't eat like a pig.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't go to extremes.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't leave the room.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let the dog in.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't let the dog in.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't open your book.\", \"target\": \"open\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't open your book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't try to stop me.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry about it.\", \"target\": \"worry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"担心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry about it.\", \"target\": \"worry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"担心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry about me.\", \"target\": \"worry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"担心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go back to your seat.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go back to your seat.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go back to your seat.\", \"target\": \"seat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"座位\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go on with your work.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go on with your work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have a nice day, Tom.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have a nice day, Tom.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He acted as my guide.\", \"target\": \"acted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扮演\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He acted as my guide.\", \"target\": \"guide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"向导\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I are friends.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I are friends.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I are friends.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came to my rescue.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He didn't fear death.\", \"target\": \"fear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He didn't fear death.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't like fish.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't like fish.\", \"target\": \"fish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鱼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't tell lies.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't tell lies.\", \"target\": \"lies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had a hungry look.\", \"target\": \"hungry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"饥饿的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He had a hungry look.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"表情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a nice income.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has a nice income.\", \"target\": \"income\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"收入\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has lots of money.\", \"target\": \"lots\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He has lots of money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is about your age.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is about your age.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is always with me.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is angry with you.\", \"target\": \"angry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is as tall as her.\", \"target\": \"tall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is full of energy.\", \"target\": \"energy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"能量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is in his library.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is in his library.\", \"target\": \"library\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图书馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He is in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"kitchen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨房\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows how to swim.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He knows how to swim.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He likes music a lot.\", \"target\": \"likes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He likes music a lot.\", \"target\": \"music\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"音乐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He likes music a lot.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He likes to watch TV.\", \"target\": \"likes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He likes to watch TV.\", \"target\": \"tv\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电视\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may have been ill.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He may have been ill.\", \"target\": \"ill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put away his toys.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put away his toys.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He put away his toys.\", \"target\": \"toys\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玩具\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ran into the room.\", \"target\": \"ran\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He ran into the room.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He reads a good deal.\", \"target\": \"reads\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He slipped me a note.\", \"target\": \"slipped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"滑倒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He slipped me a note.\", \"target\": \"note\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"便条\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He used to live here.\", \"target\": \"used\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He used to live here.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wants to kiss her.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wants to kiss her.\", \"target\": \"kiss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吻\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was an honest man.\", \"target\": \"honest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"诚实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was an honest man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was out of breath.\", \"target\": \"breath\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"呼吸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He went to the store.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He went to the store.\", \"target\": \"store\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"商店\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He will be back soon.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He will be back soon.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He will be back soon.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wrote me a letter.\", \"target\": \"wrote\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He wrote me a letter.\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a bit energetic.\", \"target\": \"energetic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"精力充沛的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a tennis player.\", \"target\": \"tennis\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"网球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a tennis player.\", \"target\": \"player\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"球员\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's bound to forget.\", \"target\": \"bound\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's bound to forget.\", \"target\": \"forget\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's crazy about you.\", \"target\": \"crazy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疯狂的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's eating an apple.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's eating an apple.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's washing his car.\", \"target\": \"washing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"洗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's washing his car.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's washing his car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hi! Do you work here?\", \"target\": \"hi\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"你好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hi! Do you work here?\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How can you say that?\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How deep is the hole?\", \"target\": \"deep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"深\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How deep is the hole?\", \"target\": \"hole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did you meet Tom?\", \"target\": \"meet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did your test go?\", \"target\": \"test\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"测试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How did your test go?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do I gain weight?\", \"target\": \"gain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"获得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How do I gain weight?\", \"target\": \"weight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"体重\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How high is Mt. Fuji?\", \"target\": \"high\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much did it cost?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much did it cost?\", \"target\": \"cost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much did you bid?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much did you bid?\", \"target\": \"bid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"竞价\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much did you pay?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much did you pay?\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is this hat?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is this hat?\", \"target\": \"hat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帽子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is this pen?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is this pen?\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is this pen?\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"多少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How much is this pen?\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How's your job going?\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How's your job going?\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进展\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How's your wife, Tom?\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am a stranger here.\", \"target\": \"stranger\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"陌生人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am afraid of death.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am afraid of death.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am afraid of dying.\", \"target\": \"afraid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am afraid of dying.\", \"target\": \"dying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am counting on you.\", \"target\": \"counting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依靠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am glad to see her.\", \"target\": \"glad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am glad to see her.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am leaving at four.\", \"target\": \"leaving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am leaving at four.\", \"target\": \"four\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"四\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I am to blame for it.\", \"target\": \"blame\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"责备\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I applied for a visa.\", \"target\": \"applied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"申请 (shēnqǐng)\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I applied for a visa.\", \"target\": \"visa\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"签证\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ate Tom's sandwich.\", \"target\": \"ate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I ate Tom's sandwich.\", \"target\": \"sandwich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"三明治\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought an old lamp.\", \"target\": \"bought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought an old lamp.\", \"target\": \"lamp\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought her a watch.\", \"target\": \"bought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I bought her a watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I broke my right leg.\", \"target\": \"broke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打破\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I broke my right leg.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"右边的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I broke my right leg.\", \"target\": \"leg\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"腿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I built this for you.\", \"target\": \"built\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建造\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can barely see you.\", \"target\": \"barely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can barely see you.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can do what I want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can sing and dance.\", \"target\": \"sing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"唱歌\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can sing and dance.\", \"target\": \"dance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跳舞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can swim very fast.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can swim very fast.\", \"target\": \"fast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't afford a car.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't afford a car.\", \"target\": \"afford\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"负担得起\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't afford a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't do it either.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't say for sure.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't say for sure.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't say for sure.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"确定地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't shut it down.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't sleep at all!\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't sleep at all!\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't sleep at all.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't sleep at all.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't tell you now.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't tell you now.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't wait for you.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't wait for you.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't leave Tom.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I couldn't leave Tom.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't do anything.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't see anybody.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't see anybody.\", \"target\": \"anybody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't get the joke.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't get the joke.\", \"target\": \"joke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笑话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't get the joke.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't get the joke.\", \"target\": \"joke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笑话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't go to school.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't go to school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like English.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like science.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't like science.\", \"target\": \"science\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"科学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't need anybody.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't need anybody.\", \"target\": \"anybody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to swim.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to swim.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to wait.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't want to wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I envy you your luck.\", \"target\": \"luck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to call him.\", \"target\": \"forgot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I forgot to call him.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I found it by chance.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I guess you're right.\", \"target\": \"guess\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"猜\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I guess you're right.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"正确\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had fun last night.\", \"target\": \"fun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐趣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had fun last night.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"昨晚的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had fun last night.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had no time to eat.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had no time to eat.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a job for you.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a lot of cats.\", \"target\": \"cats\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"猫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a new red car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a new red car.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色 (hóngsè)\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a new red car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have a sore throat.\", \"target\": \"throat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喉咙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my watch.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my watch.\", \"target\": \"watch\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手表\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many ideas.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many ideas.\", \"target\": \"ideas\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to work.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have to go to work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have what you need.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope you don't die.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope you don't die.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I intend to go there.\", \"target\": \"intend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打算\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I intend to go there.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just cut my finger.\", \"target\": \"cut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"切\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just cut my finger.\", \"target\": \"finger\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手指\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just don't like it.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just want to sleep.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just want to sleep.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom's brother.\", \"target\": \"knew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom's brother.\", \"target\": \"brother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"兄弟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know her very well.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know life is short.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know life is short.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生命\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know life is short.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know what you mean.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know what you mean.\", \"target\": \"mean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"意思\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know who likes Tom.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know who likes Tom.\", \"target\": \"likes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you hired Tom.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you hired Tom.\", \"target\": \"hired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"雇佣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I left the door open.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I left the door open.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lent Tom my camera.\", \"target\": \"lent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lent Tom my camera.\", \"target\": \"camera\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"相机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to eat apples.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to eat apples.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like to eat apples.\", \"target\": \"apples\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like you very much.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live in a big city.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I live in a big city.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I look forward to it.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"期待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I look forward to it.\", \"target\": \"forward\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"向前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I looked at my notes.\", \"target\": \"looked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I looked at my notes.\", \"target\": \"notes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笔记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made a few changes.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made a few changes.\", \"target\": \"changes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"改变\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made a paper plane.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made a paper plane.\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I made a paper plane.\", \"target\": \"plane\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I miss you very much.\", \"target\": \"miss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想念\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must sell my house.\", \"target\": \"must\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must sell my house.\", \"target\": \"sell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"卖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I must sell my house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to get to bed.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to get to bed.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to get to bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go to work.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go to work.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to go to work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to study math.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to study math.\", \"target\": \"study\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to study math.\", \"target\": \"math\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to take notes.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to take notes.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I need to take notes.\", \"target\": \"notes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"笔记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I no longer love Tom.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不再\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I no longer love Tom.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I no longer love him.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不再\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I no longer love him.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I no longer love you.\", \"target\": \"longer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不再\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I no longer love you.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I once lived in Rome.\", \"target\": \"lived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe Tom some money.\", \"target\": \"owe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe Tom some money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"owe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I owe a lot of money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I paid $200 in taxes.\", \"target\": \"taxes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"税\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I paid him the money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I promise I'll do it.\", \"target\": \"promise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"承诺\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I promise I'll do it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I said it might rain.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I said it might rain.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I said it might rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I said open the door.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a lot of buses.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a lot of buses.\", \"target\": \"buses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I slept on the couch.\", \"target\": \"slept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I study French a lot.\", \"target\": \"study\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is awake.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is lying.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is lying.\", \"target\": \"lying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it was wrong.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it was wrong.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that it's OK.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that it's OK.\", \"target\": \"ok\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that's awful.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that's awful.\", \"target\": \"awful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可怕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think this is true.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think this is true.\", \"target\": \"true\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you're lying.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you're lying.\", \"target\": \"lying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you're ready.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you're ready.\", \"target\": \"ready\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took a look around.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I took a look around.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I walked up the hill.\", \"target\": \"walked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I walked up the hill.\", \"target\": \"hill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"山丘\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want an MP3 player!\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want an MP3 player!\", \"target\": \"player\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"播放器\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want the other one.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want the other one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go skating.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to go skating.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to make a pie.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to make a pie.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to rent a car.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to rent a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to study math.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to study math.\", \"target\": \"study\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want to study math.\", \"target\": \"math\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to go there.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to go there.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to stop Tom.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to stop Tom.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was at the theater.\", \"target\": \"theater\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"剧院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was late to school.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晚的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was late to school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was stung by a bee.\", \"target\": \"bee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蜜蜂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I went into the navy.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I went into the navy.\", \"target\": \"navy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"海军\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will come with you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I will come with you.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I were taller.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"祝愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"luck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"祝愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"luck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"祝愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish you good luck.\", \"target\": \"luck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't say it again.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I won't say it again.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I work in Boston now.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll admit I'm wrong.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll admit I'm wrong.\", \"target\": \"admit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"承认\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll admit I'm wrong.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll ask Tom to wait.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll ask Tom to wait.\", \"target\": \"ask\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll ask Tom to wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be in my office.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be in my office.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be watching you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll be watching you.\", \"target\": \"watching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"观看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll dream about you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll dream about you.\", \"target\": \"dream\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"梦想\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a book.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a book.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ride.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ride.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ride.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅程\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ride.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ride.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ride.\", \"target\": \"ride\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅程\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ring.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll give you a ring.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll help you escape.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll help you escape.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll help you escape.\", \"target\": \"escape\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"逃跑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never come back.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never come back.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never come back.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never come back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never leave you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never leave you.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll never leave you.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll phone you later.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll phone you later.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll phone you later.\", \"target\": \"later\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍后\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll prove it to you.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll prove it to you.\", \"target\": \"prove\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"证明\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll take care of it.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll take care of it.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"处理\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll take care of it.\", \"target\": \"care\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"照顾\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm 30 years old now.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm 30 years old now.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm an honest person.\", \"target\": \"honest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"诚实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm an honest person.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm an office worker.\", \"target\": \"worker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm buying a new car.\", \"target\": \"buying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"购买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm buying a new car.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm buying a new car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm closing the door.\", \"target\": \"closing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"关闭\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm closing the door.\", \"target\": \"door\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"门\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm coming home, Tom.\", \"target\": \"coming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm coming home, Tom.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm folding my dress.\", \"target\": \"folding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"折叠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm folding my dress.\", \"target\": \"dress\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"连衣裙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad I was there.\", \"target\": \"glad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm here on business.\", \"target\": \"business\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm here to help you.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm in a hurry today.\", \"target\": \"hurry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"匆忙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm in a hurry today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm in love with her.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm just another man.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm just another man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for work.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not at all tired.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疲倦的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not feeling well.\", \"target\": \"feeling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not feeling well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not feeling well.\", \"target\": \"feeling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not feeling well.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not good at math.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not good at math.\", \"target\": \"math\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not tired at all.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"累的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not turning back.\", \"target\": \"turning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"转身\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not turning back.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm poor at swimming.\", \"target\": \"poor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"差的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm poor at swimming.\", \"target\": \"swimming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I hurt you.\", \"target\": \"sorry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"对不起\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry I hurt you.\", \"target\": \"hurt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伤害\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry to hear it.\", \"target\": \"sorry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"抱歉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sorry to hear it.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm still a beginner.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm still a beginner.\", \"target\": \"beginner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"初学者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure they'll win.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"确定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure they'll win.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure they'll win.\", \"target\": \"win\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure they'll win.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"确定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure they'll win.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm sure they'll win.\", \"target\": \"win\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the one you want.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the one you want.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm thirty years old.\", \"target\": \"thirty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"三十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm thirty years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm thirty years old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm tired of dancing.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"累\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm tired of dancing.\", \"target\": \"dancing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"跳舞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm tired of writing.\", \"target\": \"tired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"疲倦的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm tired of writing.\", \"target\": \"writing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm walking with her.\", \"target\": \"walking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走路\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm willing to share.\", \"target\": \"willing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"愿意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm willing to share.\", \"target\": \"share\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分享\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm working too much.\", \"target\": \"working\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm working too much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been busy today.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙碌的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've been busy today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've deleted the app.\", \"target\": \"deleted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"删除\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've deleted the app.\", \"target\": \"app\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"应用程序\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've eaten one apple.\", \"target\": \"eaten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've eaten one apple.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've eaten one apple.\", \"target\": \"apple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"苹果\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got Tom with me.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a flat tire.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a pacemaker.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got a toothache.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got one for you.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've got one for you.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've won first prize!\", \"target\": \"won\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've won first prize!\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've won first prize!\", \"target\": \"prize\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奖品\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is she a taxi driver?\", \"target\": \"taxi\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出租车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is she a taxi driver?\", \"target\": \"driver\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"司机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is the rain to blame?\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is the rain to blame?\", \"target\": \"blame\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"责备\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It belongs to me now.\", \"target\": \"belongs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"属于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is very hot today.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is very hot today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't at all easy.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It isn't that simple.\", \"target\": \"simple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"简单的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like a duck.\", \"target\": \"looks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like an egg.\", \"target\": \"looks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like an egg.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It looks like an egg.\", \"target\": \"egg\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸡蛋\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes me feel sad.\", \"target\": \"makes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes me feel sad.\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes me feel sad.\", \"target\": \"sad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"悲伤的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It only costs $10.00!\", \"target\": \"costs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It rained for a week.\", \"target\": \"rained\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It rained for a week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a long letter.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"长的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a long letter.\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a quiet night.\", \"target\": \"quiet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"安静的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was a quiet night.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was time to leave.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was time to leave.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It'll be spring soon.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It'll be spring soon.\", \"target\": \"spring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"春天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It'll be spring soon.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good question.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a good question.\", \"target\": \"question\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's a waste of time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's all Tom's fault.\", \"target\": \"fault\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's an easy victory.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's an easy victory.\", \"target\": \"victory\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"胜利\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long war.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's been a long war.\", \"target\": \"war\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"战争\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's good to see you.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's good to see you.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's me that's wrong.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's my CD, isn't it?\", \"target\": \"cd\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光盘\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not at all easy.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's not that simple.\", \"target\": \"simple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"简单的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's sort of strange.\", \"target\": \"sort\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分类\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's sort of strange.\", \"target\": \"strange\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"奇怪的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"fired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解雇\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got fired from the company, but since I have a little money saved up, for the time being, I won't have trouble with living expenses.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's very easy to sound natural in your own native language, and very easy to sound unnatural in your non-native language.\", \"target\": \"non\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"非本地的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"甚至\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"occasionally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"偶尔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even now, I occasionally think I'd like to see you. Not the you that you are today, but the you I remember from the past.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't want to put on sunscreen, that's your problem. Just don't come complaining to me when you get a sunburn.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't want to put on sunscreen, that's your problem. Just don't come complaining to me when you get a sunburn.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't want to put on sunscreen, that's your problem. Just don't come complaining to me when you get a sunburn.\", \"target\": \"problem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like to use the term \\\"a person of color\\\" because he thinks it implies that white people have no color.\", \"target\": \"thinks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"translate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻译\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"computer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计算机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know how to translate the word \\\"computer\\\" because the people he was talking to had never seen one.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother speaks French better than my father speaks English, so they usually speak to each other in French.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"calling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"yes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"是的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"calls\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Is that Tom calling again?\\\" \\\"Yes. He calls every evening these days. I shouldn't have given him my number.\\\"\", \"target\": \"number\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"号码\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"earthquakes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地震\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"tidal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"潮汐的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"resulted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"deaths\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last year in the Philippines, earthquakes and tidal waves resulted in the deaths of more than 6,000 people.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"conservationists\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"保护主义者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"fear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"害怕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"continuing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"持续的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"pushing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推动\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"animals\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"动物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many conservationists fear the continuing slaughter of whales is pushing these animals towards extinction.\", \"target\": \"towards\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"朝向\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"daughter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"pretended\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假装\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's daughter pretended not to know him when he came to pick her up from school in his battered old car.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"listen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"probably\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you'd listen a little more carefully to what the teacher says, you'd probably be able to understand.\", \"target\": \"understand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"crowd\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人群\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"approval\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"赞同\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"mark\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"proper noun\", \"zh\": \"马克\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"played\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"演奏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The large crowd roared in approval as Mark Knopfler played the first few bars of \\\"Money for Nothing\\\".\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you remember the time you and I went to the zoo together when you and I were in elementary school?\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"usually\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My parents usually speak to each other in French, even though my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"speaker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"应该\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"arrive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"twelve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"十二\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"noon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"中午\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The handyman was supposed to arrive at twelve noon, but got stuck in a traffic jam for a few hours.\", \"target\": \"hours\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"clung\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"branches\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树枝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"several\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"几个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"hours\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some people clung to tree branches for several hours to avoid being washed away by the floodwaters.\", \"target\": \"avoid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"避免\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"mad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"finds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"painting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绘画\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"fake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"假的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"depression\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大萧条\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"wealthy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富有的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"During the Depression in the 1930's, many wealthy people lost everything in the stock market crash.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to return the swimsuit for a larger size, but the clerk told him that wasn't allowed.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to return the swimsuit for a larger size, but the clerk told him that wasn't allowed.\", \"target\": \"return\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"退回\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom tried to return the swimsuit for a larger size, but the clerk told him that wasn't allowed.\", \"target\": \"clerk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"店员\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since the orbits are elliptical, the planets do not always have the same distance from the Sun.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"因为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since the orbits are elliptical, the planets do not always have the same distance from the Sun.\", \"target\": \"planets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"行星\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since the orbits are elliptical, the planets do not always have the same distance from the Sun.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since the orbits are elliptical, the planets do not always have the same distance from the Sun.\", \"target\": \"distance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"距离\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since the orbits are elliptical, the planets do not always have the same distance from the Sun.\", \"target\": \"sun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"太阳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"ecological\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生态的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"country\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"level\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"水平\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"economic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"经济的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ecological footprint of a country is closely related to its level of economic development.\", \"target\": \"development\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"发展\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"optimists\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐观主义者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Optimists see opportunities in disasters while pessimists find disasters in every opportunity.\", \"target\": \"disasters\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灾难\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"应该\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"listen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"将会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we were supposed to talk more than listen, we would have been given two mouths and one ear.\", \"target\": \"mouths\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"嘴巴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"mad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"finds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"painting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绘画\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think Tom is going to be pretty mad when he finds out that the painting he bought is a fake.\", \"target\": \"fake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"假的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe you are eating something the doctor has told you repeatedly you shouldn't eat.\", \"target\": \"doctor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For quantities of 20 or more, we can allow you a special discount of 10% on the prices quoted.\", \"target\": \"quantities\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Abraham Lincoln, the 16th president of the United States, was born in a log cabin in Kentucky.\", \"target\": \"president\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"总统\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Abraham Lincoln, the 16th president of the United States, was born in a log cabin in Kentucky.\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Abraham Lincoln, the 16th president of the United States, was born in a log cabin in Kentucky.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Abraham Lincoln, the 16th president of the United States, was born in a log cabin in Kentucky.\", \"target\": \"born\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"started\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"band\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乐队\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"cities\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we started out, our band could only find small clubs in small cities that would hire us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"throughout\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...期间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"five\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"五\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"painful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"痛苦的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"cancer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"癌症\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"treatments\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"治疗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Throughout the five years of painful cancer treatments, he managed to keep a stiff upper lip.\", \"target\": \"managed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"设法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Right now, we have blueberries, blackberries, cherries, strawberries, peaches and nectarines.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"现在\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"rains\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"season\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"季节\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"june\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"六月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Japan, it rains quite a bit during our rainy season which is from mid-June until mid-July.\", \"target\": \"july\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"七月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"There's an apostrophe missing. It's and its are different.\\\" \\\"I know. It was a typing error.\\\"\", \"target\": \"missing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"丢失的; 缺少的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"There's an apostrophe missing. It's and its are different.\\\" \\\"I know. It was a typing error.\\\"\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"There's an apostrophe missing. It's and its are different.\\\" \\\"I know. It was a typing error.\\\"\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"meet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"impressions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"印象\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"determine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"决定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"percent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百分比\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"whatever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"无论什么\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"happens\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When people meet, first impressions determine more than 50 percent of whatever happens next.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"接下来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"delicious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美味的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"prices\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"价格\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"That place's food is delicious and their prices are low. However, their location isn't good.\", \"target\": \"however\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"然而\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"lonely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"孤独的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"tend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"倾向于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"meeting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lonely people tend to be afraid of meeting others, which ensures they will always be lonely.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"million\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百万\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"either\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"或者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the other 600 million people, English is either a second language or a foreign language.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of its origins, Canadian English has features of both American and British English.\", \"target\": \"origins\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"起源\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of its origins, Canadian English has features of both American and British English.\", \"target\": \"features\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"特征\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Owing to its landmass, the Antarctic has an air temperature lower than that of the Arctic.\", \"target\": \"owing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"由于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Owing to its landmass, the Antarctic has an air temperature lower than that of the Arctic.\", \"target\": \"air\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"空气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Owing to its landmass, the Antarctic has an air temperature lower than that of the Arctic.\", \"target\": \"temperature\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"温度\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Owing to its landmass, the Antarctic has an air temperature lower than that of the Arctic.\", \"target\": \"lower\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"较低的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"women\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妇女\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"realize\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"意识到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One out of 455 women doesn't realize she's pregnant until the twentieth week of pregnancy.\", \"target\": \"pregnant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"怀孕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In theory, there is no difference between theory and practice. But, in practice, there is.\", \"target\": \"theory\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"理论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In theory, there is no difference between theory and practice. But, in practice, there is.\", \"target\": \"difference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区别\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like this picture, not just because it's famous, but because it really is a masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like this picture, not just because it's famous, but because it really is a masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"picture\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图片\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like this picture, not just because it's famous, but because it really is a masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"famous\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"著名的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I like this picture, not just because it's famous, but because it really is a masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真正地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which translation of this book do you think is better, the French one or the English one?\", \"target\": \"translation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"翻译\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which translation of this book do you think is better, the French one or the English one?\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Which translation of this book do you think is better, the French one or the English one?\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"computers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电脑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"certainly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"当然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"playing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扮演\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"role\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"角色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Computers are certainly playing an important role in our life, whether we like it or not.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"problem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"air\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"空气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"pollution\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"污染\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"bicycle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"自行车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the problem of air pollution, the bicycle may some day replace the automobile.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to change clothes because what I was wearing wasn't appropriate for the situation.\", \"target\": \"change\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"改变\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to change clothes because what I was wearing wasn't appropriate for the situation.\", \"target\": \"clothes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"衣服\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to change clothes because what I was wearing wasn't appropriate for the situation.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to change clothes because what I was wearing wasn't appropriate for the situation.\", \"target\": \"appropriate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"合适的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to change clothes because what I was wearing wasn't appropriate for the situation.\", \"target\": \"situation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"情况\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"likely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"truth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"真相\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't think that it's very likely that Tom will tell us the truth about what happened.\", \"target\": \"happened\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"frog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青蛙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"什么\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"happen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eat a live frog every morning, and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's mother is a nurse at the hospital that's across the street from where Mary lives.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's mother is a nurse at the hospital that's across the street from where Mary lives.\", \"target\": \"nurse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"护士\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's mother is a nurse at the hospital that's across the street from where Mary lives.\", \"target\": \"hospital\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom's mother is a nurse at the hospital that's across the street from where Mary lives.\", \"target\": \"lives\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"makes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is the head of the company in name only. His son makes all the important decisions.\", \"target\": \"decisions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"决定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"amount\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"produced\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生产\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"country\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"cultural\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"文化\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The amount of paper produced by a country is closely related to its cultural standards.\", \"target\": \"standards\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"标准\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At lunchtime today, our usual restaurant was closed because of a funeral in the family.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At lunchtime today, our usual restaurant was closed because of a funeral in the family.\", \"target\": \"usual\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"通常的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At lunchtime today, our usual restaurant was closed because of a funeral in the family.\", \"target\": \"restaurant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At lunchtime today, our usual restaurant was closed because of a funeral in the family.\", \"target\": \"funeral\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"葬礼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At lunchtime today, our usual restaurant was closed because of a funeral in the family.\", \"target\": \"family\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家庭\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"thank\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感谢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thank you very much for lending me $500 when I was having difficulty making ends meet.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you could go back and start your life again, from what age would you like to start?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Democracy is the worst form of government, except all the others that have been tried.\", \"target\": \"democracy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"民主\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Democracy is the worst form of government, except all the others that have been tried.\", \"target\": \"worst\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Democracy is the worst form of government, except all the others that have been tried.\", \"target\": \"government\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"政府\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"ladies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女士们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"due\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"由于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"airport\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机场\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"arrival\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ladies and gentlemen, due to an accident at the airport, our arrival will be delayed.\", \"target\": \"delayed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"延迟的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In London, the police are always worried about finding a bomb on the train or subway.\", \"target\": \"police\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In London, the police are always worried about finding a bomb on the train or subway.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In London, the police are always worried about finding a bomb on the train or subway.\", \"target\": \"worried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"担心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In London, the police are always worried about finding a bomb on the train or subway.\", \"target\": \"finding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In London, the police are always worried about finding a bomb on the train or subway.\", \"target\": \"bomb\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"炸弹\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In London, the police are always worried about finding a bomb on the train or subway.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"considered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"考虑到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All things considered, I think you should go back home and take care of your parents.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"growing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"成长的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"seem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"energy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"能量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"perhaps\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"也许\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"needs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"medical\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"医疗的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A growing child who doesn't seem to have much energy perhaps needs medical attention.\", \"target\": \"attention\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"关注\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't we stop arguing over these piddling matters and get to the issues at hand?\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't we stop arguing over these piddling matters and get to the issues at hand?\", \"target\": \"arguing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"争论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't we stop arguing over these piddling matters and get to the issues at hand?\", \"target\": \"matters\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Why don't we stop arguing over these piddling matters and get to the issues at hand?\", \"target\": \"issues\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"visitors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游客\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"usually\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被要求\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"shoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鞋子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"enter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进入\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Visitors are usually asked to remove their shoes before they enter a Japanese house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"competitive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"竞争性的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"system\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"系统\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"engineers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工程师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"continue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company's competitive edge will be eroded if system engineers continue to leave.\", \"target\": \"leave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want something to be done right, sometimes you've just got to do it yourself.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want something to be done right, sometimes you've just got to do it yourself.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某事\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want something to be done right, sometimes you've just got to do it yourself.\", \"target\": \"sometimes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"waiting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know you've been waiting a long time, but could you wait just a little bit longer?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可以\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came back not because he was homesick, but because he was running short of money.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came back not because he was homesick, but because he was running short of money.\", \"target\": \"back\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He came back not because he was homesick, but because he was running short of money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"studied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied French for three years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"agency\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机构\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"executive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"执行的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We'll need a head hunting agency to find the right man for this executive position.\", \"target\": \"position\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"职位\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just spoken to your French teacher and he says you're doing well in his class.\", \"target\": \"spoken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just spoken to your French teacher and he says you're doing well in his class.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've just spoken to your French teacher and he says you're doing well in his class.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His dress is that of a gentleman, but his speech and behavior are those of a clown.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His dress is that of a gentleman, but his speech and behavior are those of a clown.\", \"target\": \"dress\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"服装\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His dress is that of a gentleman, but his speech and behavior are those of a clown.\", \"target\": \"gentleman\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绅士\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His dress is that of a gentleman, but his speech and behavior are those of a clown.\", \"target\": \"speech\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"演讲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His dress is that of a gentleman, but his speech and behavior are those of a clown.\", \"target\": \"behavior\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"行为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A connection between personality and blood type has not been scientifically proven.\", \"target\": \"connection\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A connection between personality and blood type has not been scientifically proven.\", \"target\": \"personality\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"个性\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A connection between personality and blood type has not been scientifically proven.\", \"target\": \"blood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"血液\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A connection between personality and blood type has not been scientifically proven.\", \"target\": \"type\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"类型\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A connection between personality and blood type has not been scientifically proven.\", \"target\": \"scientifically\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"科学地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A connection between personality and blood type has not been scientifically proven.\", \"target\": \"proven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"证明\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to take an examination without preparing for it.\", \"target\": \"known\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to take an examination without preparing for it.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to take an examination without preparing for it.\", \"target\": \"examination\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"考试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should have known better than to take an examination without preparing for it.\", \"target\": \"preparing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"准备\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Manholes are round because that way they won't accidentally fall through the hole.\", \"target\": \"round\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"圆形\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Manholes are round because that way they won't accidentally fall through the hole.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Manholes are round because that way they won't accidentally fall through the hole.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Manholes are round because that way they won't accidentally fall through the hole.\", \"target\": \"accidentally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"意外地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Manholes are round because that way they won't accidentally fall through the hole.\", \"target\": \"hole\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Being a good conversationalist does not just mean being a good speaker of English.\", \"target\": \"conversationalist\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"对话者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Being a good conversationalist does not just mean being a good speaker of English.\", \"target\": \"speaker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"swimming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"river\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"河流\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went swimming in the river, but when he got out, his clothes had been stolen.\", \"target\": \"clothes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"衣服\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To the man who only has a hammer in the toolkit, every problem looks like a nail.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To the man who only has a hammer in the toolkit, every problem looks like a nail.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To the man who only has a hammer in the toolkit, every problem looks like a nail.\", \"target\": \"problem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To the man who only has a hammer in the toolkit, every problem looks like a nail.\", \"target\": \"looks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To the man who only has a hammer in the toolkit, every problem looks like a nail.\", \"target\": \"nail\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钉子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"kitchen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨房\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kitchen knife wasn't sharp enough to cut the meat, so I used my pocket knife.\", \"target\": \"meat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"肉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"ages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"两个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"equivalent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"等同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ages of the two children put together was equivalent to that of their father.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know the city, and what's more, I couldn't speak a word of the language.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know the city, and what's more, I couldn't speak a word of the language.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know the city, and what's more, I couldn't speak a word of the language.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know the city, and what's more, I couldn't speak a word of the language.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every now and then he drops in at this bookstore on his way home from the office.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every now and then he drops in at this bookstore on his way home from the office.\", \"target\": \"drops\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"掉落\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every now and then he drops in at this bookstore on his way home from the office.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every now and then he drops in at this bookstore on his way home from the office.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every now and then he drops in at this bookstore on his way home from the office.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"studied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I studied English for 6 years in school, I'm not good at speaking it.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"weekend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周末\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"speaks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"voice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"声音\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"understand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom always speaks in such a low voice that I can barely understand what he says.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"convince\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说服\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"son\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was asked to convince him to get his son or someone else to paint the house.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"accidents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"leading\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"主要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"teenagers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青少年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Car accidents are the leading cause of death for teenagers in the United States.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the time there were no native English speakers teaching in any public school.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the time there were no native English speakers teaching in any public school.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the time there were no native English speakers teaching in any public school.\", \"target\": \"speakers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the time there were no native English speakers teaching in any public school.\", \"target\": \"teaching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"教学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the time there were no native English speakers teaching in any public school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"whoever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"无论谁\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"happiness\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"幸福\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"simply\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仅仅\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Whoever said money can't buy happiness simply didn't know where to go shopping.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Those who use forks or chopsticks often think people who don't are uncivilized.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Those who use forks or chopsticks often think people who don't are uncivilized.\", \"target\": \"forks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"叉子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Those who use forks or chopsticks often think people who don't are uncivilized.\", \"target\": \"often\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"经常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Those who use forks or chopsticks often think people who don't are uncivilized.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Those who use forks or chopsticks often think people who don't are uncivilized.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They say you shouldn't take rumors seriously, but that's easier said than done.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They say you shouldn't take rumors seriously, but that's easier said than done.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"接受\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They say you shouldn't take rumors seriously, but that's easier said than done.\", \"target\": \"seriously\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"认真地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"telephone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"operator\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"接线员\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"询问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"caller\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"来电者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The telephone operator asked the caller to hold on until a connection was made.\", \"target\": \"connection\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"连接\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's popular, not because she's beautiful, but because she's kind to everyone.\", \"target\": \"popular\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"受欢迎的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's popular, not because she's beautiful, but because she's kind to everyone.\", \"target\": \"beautiful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美丽的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's popular, not because she's beautiful, but because she's kind to everyone.\", \"target\": \"kind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"善良的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She's popular, not because she's beautiful, but because she's kind to everyone.\", \"target\": \"everyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Publication of the article was timed to coincide with the professor's birthday.\", \"target\": \"publication\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"出版\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Publication of the article was timed to coincide with the professor's birthday.\", \"target\": \"article\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"文章\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Publication of the article was timed to coincide with the professor's birthday.\", \"target\": \"professor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教授\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Publication of the article was timed to coincide with the professor's birthday.\", \"target\": \"birthday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生日\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a native French speaker and my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a native French speaker and my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a native French speaker and my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"speaker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is a native French speaker and my mother is a native English speaker.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"returned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"归还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"books\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I returned the books I borrowed from the library, and I borrowed some new ones.\", \"target\": \"library\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图书馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a lot of work, but it's enough to keep me in the office this week.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a lot of work, but it's enough to keep me in the office this week.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a lot of work, but it's enough to keep me in the office this week.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a lot of work, but it's enough to keep me in the office this week.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't have a lot of work, but it's enough to keep me in the office this week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"scores\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分数\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"mine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His scores are always better than mine, even though he doesn't study very much.\", \"target\": \"study\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Charles Lindbergh made the first solo flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Charles Lindbergh made the first solo flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Charles Lindbergh made the first solo flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.\", \"target\": \"solo\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"单独的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Charles Lindbergh made the first solo flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.\", \"target\": \"flight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Charles Lindbergh made the first solo flight across the Atlantic Ocean in 1927.\", \"target\": \"ocean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"海洋\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As the train came to a halt, all of the passengers wondered what was happening.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As the train came to a halt, all of the passengers wondered what was happening.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As the train came to a halt, all of the passengers wondered what was happening.\", \"target\": \"halt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As the train came to a halt, all of the passengers wondered what was happening.\", \"target\": \"passengers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乘客\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As the train came to a halt, all of the passengers wondered what was happening.\", \"target\": \"wondered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As the train came to a halt, all of the passengers wondered what was happening.\", \"target\": \"happening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"正在发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did the best he could, but he wasn't able to get a higher grade than Mary.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom did the best he could, but he wasn't able to get a higher grade than Mary.\", \"target\": \"grade\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"成绩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"write\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"almost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"speaker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"pronunciation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"发音\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can write almost like a native speaker, but his pronunciation is terrible.\", \"target\": \"terrible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"糟糕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"became\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"popular\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"受欢迎的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"teenagers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"青少年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"made\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"debut\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"首次亮相\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom became popular among teenagers as soon as he made his debut on the screen.\", \"target\": \"screen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"屏幕\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"应该\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"study\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"library\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图书馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"woke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"醒来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Today, I was supposed to study at the library but I woke up around 12 o'clock.\", \"target\": \"clock\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The world is just like a book, and every step you take is like turning a page.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"looks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it looks like an apple and it tastes like an apple, it's probably an apple.\", \"target\": \"probably\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"scratchy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"沙哑的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"throat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喉咙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"wonder\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a scratchy throat since this morning. I wonder if I've caught a cold.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"感冒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"type\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"类型\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"gets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"nervous\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"紧张的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm the type who gets nervous in front of people, so I'm bad at speech making.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"perfect\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"完美的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"hiding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"藏身处\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"police\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought that we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eighty percent of all information on computers around the world is in English.\", \"target\": \"eighty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"八十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eighty percent of all information on computers around the world is in English.\", \"target\": \"percent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百分比\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eighty percent of all information on computers around the world is in English.\", \"target\": \"information\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eighty percent of all information on computers around the world is in English.\", \"target\": \"computers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计算机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Eighty percent of all information on computers around the world is in English.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom came to the conclusion that no matter what he did, Mary wouldn't like it.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom came to the conclusion that no matter what he did, Mary wouldn't like it.\", \"target\": \"conclusion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"结论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They consider it impolite to disagree with someone they don't know very well.\", \"target\": \"consider\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They consider it impolite to disagree with someone they don't know very well.\", \"target\": \"disagree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不同意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They consider it impolite to disagree with someone they don't know very well.\", \"target\": \"someone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They consider it impolite to disagree with someone they don't know very well.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The population of London is much greater than that of any other British city.\", \"target\": \"population\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人口\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The population of London is much greater than that of any other British city.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The population of London is much greater than that of any other British city.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"games\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比赛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"winning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"获胜\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The most important thing in the Olympic Games is not winning but taking part.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"differently\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不同地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"depending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"是否\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"rich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富有的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People look at things differently depending on whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"poor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"贫穷的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"tied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"系\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"oven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"烤箱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"tied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"系\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary tied an apron around her waist and then took the turkey out of the oven.\", \"target\": \"oven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"烤箱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel that order because we didn't have enough money to pay for it.\", \"target\": \"cancel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取消\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel that order because we didn't have enough money to pay for it.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"订单\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel that order because we didn't have enough money to pay for it.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel that order because we didn't have enough money to pay for it.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel that order because we didn't have enough money to pay for it.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"although\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"government\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"政府\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"refuses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拒绝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"admit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"承认\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"economic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"经济的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Although the government refuses to admit it, its economic policy is in ruins.\", \"target\": \"policy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"政策\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"views\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"differently\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不同地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"是否\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"rich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"poor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"贫穷的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"views\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"differently\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不同地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"是否\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"rich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A person views things differently according to whether they are rich or poor.\", \"target\": \"poor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"贫穷的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to your father for not getting home in time for dinner.\", \"target\": \"apologize\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"道歉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to your father for not getting home in time for dinner.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to your father for not getting home in time for dinner.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to your father for not getting home in time for dinner.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to your father for not getting home in time for dinner.\", \"target\": \"dinner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You said Mary was beautiful, but I didn't think she would be this beautiful.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You said Mary was beautiful, but I didn't think she would be this beautiful.\", \"target\": \"beautiful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美丽的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You said Mary was beautiful, but I didn't think she would be this beautiful.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You said Mary was beautiful, but I didn't think she would be this beautiful.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought that he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The statue of Hachiko, the faithful dog, stands in front of Shibuya Station.\", \"target\": \"statue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雕像\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The statue of Hachiko, the faithful dog, stands in front of Shibuya Station.\", \"target\": \"faithful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忠实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The statue of Hachiko, the faithful dog, stands in front of Shibuya Station.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The statue of Hachiko, the faithful dog, stands in front of Shibuya Station.\", \"target\": \"stands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"站立\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"importation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"进口\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"rare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"稀有的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"wild\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"野生的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"animals\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"动物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"country\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The importation of rare wild animals to this country is strictly prohibited.\", \"target\": \"prohibited\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"禁止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many parents think it's important for their children to eat before 8:00 p.m.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many parents think it's important for their children to eat before 8:00 p.m.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many parents think it's important for their children to eat before 8:00 p.m.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many parents think it's important for their children to eat before 8:00 p.m.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many parents think it's important for their children to eat before 8:00 p.m.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many parents think it's important for their children to eat before 8:00 p.m.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"explain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解释\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It would take me too much time to explain to you why it's not going to work.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"rains\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"game\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比赛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it rains on that day, the game will be postponed until the next fine day.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"sheep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"羊\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a man had 11 sheep and all but 9 died, how many sheep would he have left?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After he had graduated from the university, he taught English for two years.\", \"target\": \"graduated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"毕业\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After he had graduated from the university, he taught English for two years.\", \"target\": \"university\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After he had graduated from the university, he taught English for two years.\", \"target\": \"taught\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"教\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After he had graduated from the university, he taught English for two years.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After he had graduated from the university, he taught English for two years.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"according\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"newspaper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"报纸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"reports\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"报道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"airplane\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to newspaper reports, there was an airplane accident last evening.\", \"target\": \"evening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"晚上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We apologize for the delay and regret any inconvenience it may have caused.\", \"target\": \"apologize\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"道歉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We apologize for the delay and regret any inconvenience it may have caused.\", \"target\": \"delay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"延迟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We apologize for the delay and regret any inconvenience it may have caused.\", \"target\": \"regret\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遗憾\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We apologize for the delay and regret any inconvenience it may have caused.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said that Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"weekend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周末\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought that John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"weekend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周末\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave Mary a box of chocolates, and then ate all the chocolates himself.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom gave Mary a box of chocolates, and then ate all the chocolates himself.\", \"target\": \"box\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盒子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"lady\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女士\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"won\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"million\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百万\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The lady really flipped out when she learned she had won a million dollars.\", \"target\": \"dollars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"美元\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The good thing about this electronic dictionary is that it's easy to carry.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The good thing about this electronic dictionary is that it's easy to carry.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The good thing about this electronic dictionary is that it's easy to carry.\", \"target\": \"electronic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"电子的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The good thing about this electronic dictionary is that it's easy to carry.\", \"target\": \"dictionary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"字典\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The good thing about this electronic dictionary is that it's easy to carry.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"prime\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"主要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"minister\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"首相\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"speech\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"演讲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"calculated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"计算\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"opposition\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"反对派\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The Prime Minister's speech was calculated to anger the opposition parties.\", \"target\": \"parties\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"政党\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"outside\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"在...外面\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"homes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Outside the school, she saw people with no homes living in cardboard boxes.\", \"target\": \"living\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had been a little more careful, the accident would have been avoided.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had been a little more careful, the accident would have been avoided.\", \"target\": \"careful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had been a little more careful, the accident would have been avoided.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had been a little more careful, the accident would have been avoided.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"介意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"lending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"借\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't mind lending you the money provided you pay it back within a month.\", \"target\": \"month\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English has now become the common language of several nations in the world.\", \"target\": \"become\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English has now become the common language of several nations in the world.\", \"target\": \"common\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"共同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English has now become the common language of several nations in the world.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English has now become the common language of several nations in the world.\", \"target\": \"several\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"几个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English has now become the common language of several nations in the world.\", \"target\": \"nations\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English has now become the common language of several nations in the world.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"asking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"询问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"key\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钥匙\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"desk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"柜台\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"elevator\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电梯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After asking for my key at the front desk, I took the elevator to my floor.\", \"target\": \"floor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"楼层\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"不那么\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"likely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"position\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"职位\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're much less likely to get a good position if you don't speak English.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"must\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"wishes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"愿望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"family\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家庭\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We must take into account the wishes of all the family in planning a trip.\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"returned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"返回\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"visit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom returned to his hometown to visit his parents during the summer break.\", \"target\": \"summer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夏天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"attend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"meeting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please attend the meeting in the second floor conference room at 2:30 p.m.\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal number\", \"zh\": \"第二\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe that Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe that Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe that Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"aware\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"意识到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"sick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"folds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"折叠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"thousand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一千\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"paper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"纸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"愿望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"实现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If a sick person folds one thousand paper cranes, her wish will come true.\", \"target\": \"true\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"highly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"unlikely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不太可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"anyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that it is highly unlikely that anyone would be willing to help me.\", \"target\": \"willing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"愿意的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"everyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"持有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"breath\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"呼吸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"win\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"presidential\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"总统的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone held their breath to see who would win the presidential election.\", \"target\": \"election\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"选举\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At first, he thought English very difficult, but now he thinks it is easy.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At first, he thought English very difficult, but now he thinks it is easy.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At first, he thought English very difficult, but now he thinks it is easy.\", \"target\": \"difficult\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At first, he thought English very difficult, but now he thinks it is easy.\", \"target\": \"thinks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At first, he thought English very difficult, but now he thinks it is easy.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"according\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"forecast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"预报\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"rainy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"多雨的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"season\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"季节\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"next\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"下个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the weather forecast, the rainy season will set in next week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You seem to be prejudiced against ideas that come from foreign countries.\", \"target\": \"seem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You seem to be prejudiced against ideas that come from foreign countries.\", \"target\": \"prejudiced\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有偏见的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You seem to be prejudiced against ideas that come from foreign countries.\", \"target\": \"ideas\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You seem to be prejudiced against ideas that come from foreign countries.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You seem to be prejudiced against ideas that come from foreign countries.\", \"target\": \"countries\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"matters\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更糟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"甚至\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To make matters worse, he isn't even conscious of annoying his neighbors.\", \"target\": \"conscious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有意识的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visits the dentist on a regular basis, so she seldom gets toothaches.\", \"target\": \"visits\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visits the dentist on a regular basis, so she seldom gets toothaches.\", \"target\": \"dentist\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"牙医\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visits the dentist on a regular basis, so she seldom gets toothaches.\", \"target\": \"basis\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"基础\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visits the dentist on a regular basis, so she seldom gets toothaches.\", \"target\": \"seldom\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visits the dentist on a regular basis, so she seldom gets toothaches.\", \"target\": \"gets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"确定地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm pretty sure Tom is the only one who can tell us what we need to know.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"number\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to know the phone number of the nearest American Express office.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"perfect\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"完美的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"hiding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"藏身处\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"police\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I thought we had found the perfect hiding place, but the police found us.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"difficulty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"困难\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"license\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"执照\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"difficulty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"困难\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you'll have very little difficulty in getting a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"license\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"执照\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beer is taxed according to its malt content, so low-malt beer is cheaper.\", \"target\": \"beer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"啤酒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beer is taxed according to its malt content, so low-malt beer is cheaper.\", \"target\": \"taxed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"征税\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beer is taxed according to its malt content, so low-malt beer is cheaper.\", \"target\": \"according\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"失去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"started\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"gamble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赌博\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After Tom lost his job, he started to gamble to cope with his depression.\", \"target\": \"depression\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"抑郁症\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great warrior radiates strength. He doesn't have to fight to the death.\", \"target\": \"great\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"伟大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great warrior radiates strength. He doesn't have to fight to the death.\", \"target\": \"warrior\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"战士\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great warrior radiates strength. He doesn't have to fight to the death.\", \"target\": \"radiates\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"散发\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great warrior radiates strength. He doesn't have to fight to the death.\", \"target\": \"strength\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"力量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great warrior radiates strength. He doesn't have to fight to the death.\", \"target\": \"fight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"战斗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A great warrior radiates strength. He doesn't have to fight to the death.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't share too much private information on the social networks.\", \"target\": \"share\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分享\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't share too much private information on the social networks.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't share too much private information on the social networks.\", \"target\": \"private\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"私人的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't share too much private information on the social networks.\", \"target\": \"information\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信息\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't share too much private information on the social networks.\", \"target\": \"social\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"社交的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were talking about something at that time, but I don't remember what.\", \"target\": \"talking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"谈论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were talking about something at that time, but I don't remember what.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一些东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were talking about something at that time, but I don't remember what.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were talking about something at that time, but I don't remember what.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was able to make himself understood in French when he visited Paris.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was able to make himself understood in French when he visited Paris.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was able to make himself understood in French when he visited Paris.\", \"target\": \"understood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was able to make himself understood in French when he visited Paris.\", \"target\": \"visited\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"forgets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"给\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom never forgets to give his wife flowers on their wedding anniversary.\", \"target\": \"anniversary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周年纪念日\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't account for his whereabouts on the day that Mary was murdered.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't account for his whereabouts on the day that Mary was murdered.\", \"target\": \"account\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解释\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't account for his whereabouts on the day that Mary was murdered.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom can't account for his whereabouts on the day that Mary was murdered.\", \"target\": \"murdered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被谋杀\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"hill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"山丘\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"ancient\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"古老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"burial\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"埋葬\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The small hill turned out to be an ancient burial mound 2,000 years old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"public\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"公开的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The company went public and became listed on the stock exchange in 1990.\", \"target\": \"became\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sociopaths rarely display remorse or feelings of guilt for their crimes.\", \"target\": \"rarely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sociopaths rarely display remorse or feelings of guilt for their crimes.\", \"target\": \"display\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"展示\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sociopaths rarely display remorse or feelings of guilt for their crimes.\", \"target\": \"feelings\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sociopaths rarely display remorse or feelings of guilt for their crimes.\", \"target\": \"guilt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"内疚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Sociopaths rarely display remorse or feelings of guilt for their crimes.\", \"target\": \"crimes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"罪行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than cutting down on cigarettes, why don't you just give them up?\", \"target\": \"rather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"而不是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than cutting down on cigarettes, why don't you just give them up?\", \"target\": \"cutting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"减少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than cutting down on cigarettes, why don't you just give them up?\", \"target\": \"cigarettes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"香烟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than cutting down on cigarettes, why don't you just give them up?\", \"target\": \"give\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放弃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is the things that we do not possess which seem to us most desirable.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is the things that we do not possess which seem to us most desirable.\", \"target\": \"possess\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拥有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is the things that we do not possess which seem to us most desirable.\", \"target\": \"seem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is the things that we do not possess which seem to us most desirable.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is the things that we do not possess which seem to us most desirable.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is the things that we do not possess which seem to us most desirable.\", \"target\": \"desirable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"令人向往的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大多数\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"vote\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"投票\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"reach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"达到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"eighteen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"十八\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the U.S., most people can vote when they reach eighteen years of age.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you want to go, then go. If you don't want to, then it's no big deal.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"arrived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"ten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we'd arrived ten minutes earlier, we would've made it onto the plane.\", \"target\": \"plane\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we knew what we were doing, it wouldn't be called research, would it?\", \"target\": \"knew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If we knew what we were doing, it wouldn't be called research, would it?\", \"target\": \"research\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"研究\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"wonder\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"是否\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wonder whether we have enough money to buy Tom the painting he wanted.\", \"target\": \"painting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绘画\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was planning on going to the beach today, but then it started to rain.\", \"target\": \"planning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was planning on going to the beach today, but then it started to rain.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was planning on going to the beach today, but then it started to rain.\", \"target\": \"beach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"海滩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was planning on going to the beach today, but then it started to rain.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was planning on going to the beach today, but then it started to rain.\", \"target\": \"started\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was planning on going to the beach today, but then it started to rain.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car when I was eighteen and got a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car when I was eighteen and got a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car when I was eighteen and got a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"eighteen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"十八\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car when I was eighteen and got a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car when I was eighteen and got a driver's license.\", \"target\": \"license\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"执照\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car and got a driver's license when I was eighteen.\", \"target\": \"drive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car and got a driver's license when I was eighteen.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car and got a driver's license when I was eighteen.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car and got a driver's license when I was eighteen.\", \"target\": \"license\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"执照\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I learned to drive a car and got a driver's license when I was eighteen.\", \"target\": \"eighteen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"十八\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放置\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"palms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手掌\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"floor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地板\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"bending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弯曲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can place the palms of my hands on the floor without bending my knees.\", \"target\": \"knees\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"膝盖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her eyes shone with joy when she saw that her mother was not mad at her.\", \"target\": \"eyes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼睛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her eyes shone with joy when she saw that her mother was not mad at her.\", \"target\": \"shone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"闪耀\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her eyes shone with joy when she saw that her mother was not mad at her.\", \"target\": \"joy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"喜悦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her eyes shone with joy when she saw that her mother was not mad at her.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her eyes shone with joy when she saw that her mother was not mad at her.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Her eyes shone with joy when she saw that her mother was not mad at her.\", \"target\": \"mad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"顺便\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"umbrella\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨伞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the way, did you find the umbrella you said you'd lost the other day?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As I missed the train, I had to wait for the next one for about an hour.\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As I missed the train, I had to wait for the next one for about an hour.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As I missed the train, I had to wait for the next one for about an hour.\", \"target\": \"hour\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After I got married, my Japanese got better and I could understand more.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After I got married, my Japanese got better and I could understand more.\", \"target\": \"married\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结婚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After I got married, my Japanese got better and I could understand more.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After I got married, my Japanese got better and I could understand more.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After I got married, my Japanese got better and I could understand more.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After I got married, my Japanese got better and I could understand more.\", \"target\": \"understand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"reading\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阅读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"fell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡着\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While I was reading in bed last night, I fell asleep with the light on.\", \"target\": \"asleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"睡着的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"supply\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"供应\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"short\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"短的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When his food supply ran short, he had to look for a new place to live.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"居住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom thought he had a chance to make a lot of money on the stock market.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"college\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"family\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家庭\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't go to college because his family didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"began\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"sing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"唱歌\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom began to sing \\\"Happy Birthday\\\" and the entire restaurant joined in.\", \"target\": \"restaurant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐厅\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"feel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"感觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"服\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They told me that I would feel a little better if I took this medicine.\", \"target\": \"medicine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"药物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police have been searching for the stolen goods for almost a month.\", \"target\": \"police\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police have been searching for the stolen goods for almost a month.\", \"target\": \"searching\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"搜索\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police have been searching for the stolen goods for almost a month.\", \"target\": \"stolen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"被盗的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police have been searching for the stolen goods for almost a month.\", \"target\": \"goods\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"商品\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police have been searching for the stolen goods for almost a month.\", \"target\": \"almost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"几乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police have been searching for the stolen goods for almost a month.\", \"target\": \"month\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People show up bright on an infrared camera because of their body heat.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People show up bright on an infrared camera because of their body heat.\", \"target\": \"show\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People show up bright on an infrared camera because of their body heat.\", \"target\": \"bright\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"明亮的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People show up bright on an infrared camera because of their body heat.\", \"target\": \"camera\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"相机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"decide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"决定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"是否\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真正地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Now's the time to decide whether you really want to get married or not.\", \"target\": \"married\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"已婚的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father was no less affectionate and tender to me than my mother was.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father was no less affectionate and tender to me than my mother was.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary came home from school in tears because her friends had teased her.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary came home from school in tears because her friends had teased her.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"到家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary came home from school in tears because her friends had teased her.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary came home from school in tears because her friends had teased her.\", \"target\": \"tears\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼泪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Mary came home from school in tears because her friends had teased her.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.\", \"target\": \"kindness\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"善良\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.\", \"target\": \"blind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"盲人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was not until I had a baby myself that I knew what mother's love is.\", \"target\": \"baby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婴儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was not until I had a baby myself that I knew what mother's love is.\", \"target\": \"knew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was not until I had a baby myself that I knew what mother's love is.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was not until I had a baby myself that I knew what mother's love is.\", \"target\": \"love\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you enjoy the work you do, you have something worth more than money.\", \"target\": \"enjoy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"享受\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you enjoy the work you do, you have something worth more than money.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you enjoy the work you do, you have something worth more than money.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you enjoy the work you do, you have something worth more than money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"possible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可能的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it's at all possible, I'd like you to take part in the next meeting.\", \"target\": \"meeting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"nine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"九\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"mom\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妈妈\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was nine years old when I asked my mom if Santa Claus really existed.\", \"target\": \"existed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"存在\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary probably won't want to do that anymore.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary probably won't want to do that anymore.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary probably won't want to do that anymore.\", \"target\": \"probably\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary knows that she doesn't have to do that.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I know that Tom knows that Mary knows that she doesn't have to do that.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"enjoy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"享受\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"listening\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"classical\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"古典的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"music\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"音乐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"free\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"空闲的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I always enjoy listening to classical music when I have some free time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"helps\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"prepare\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"准备\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"breakfast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every morning she helps her mother to prepare breakfast in the kitchen.\", \"target\": \"kitchen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨房\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Does any other country fan the flames of patriotism as much as America?\", \"target\": \"country\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because it is written in simple English even a child can understand it.\", \"target\": \"written\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because it is written in simple English even a child can understand it.\", \"target\": \"simple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"简单的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because it is written in simple English even a child can understand it.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"甚至\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because it is written in simple English even a child can understand it.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because it is written in simple English even a child can understand it.\", \"target\": \"understand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As is evident from the data, smoking is not decreasing among the young.\", \"target\": \"evident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"明显的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As is evident from the data, smoking is not decreasing among the young.\", \"target\": \"data\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数据\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As is evident from the data, smoking is not decreasing among the young.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"吸烟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As is evident from the data, smoking is not decreasing among the young.\", \"target\": \"decreasing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"减少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As is evident from the data, smoking is not decreasing among the young.\", \"target\": \"young\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年轻的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's this song? I've heard it before, but I can't remember the name.\", \"target\": \"song\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"歌曲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's this song? I've heard it before, but I can't remember the name.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What's this song? I've heard it before, but I can't remember the name.\", \"target\": \"name\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"relax\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放松\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted to stay home and relax instead of hiking with his children.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said Mary thought John might be permitted to do that next weekend.\", \"target\": \"weekend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周末\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a sprinkling of foreigners among the visitors in the museum.\", \"target\": \"foreigners\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"外国人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a sprinkling of foreigners among the visitors in the museum.\", \"target\": \"visitors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"参观者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a sprinkling of foreigners among the visitors in the museum.\", \"target\": \"museum\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"博物馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She recognized the brooch as the one she had lost a few months before.\", \"target\": \"recognized\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认出\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"rather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"与其\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"hundred\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一百\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Rather than live a hundred years as a rabbit, live one day as a tiger.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Preventive measures are much more effective than the actual treatment.\", \"target\": \"preventive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"预防性的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Preventive measures are much more effective than the actual treatment.\", \"target\": \"measures\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"措施\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Preventive measures are much more effective than the actual treatment.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Preventive measures are much more effective than the actual treatment.\", \"target\": \"effective\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有效的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Preventive measures are much more effective than the actual treatment.\", \"target\": \"actual\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"实际的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Preventive measures are much more effective than the actual treatment.\", \"target\": \"treatment\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"治疗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Laser printers are generally cheaper to maintain than inkjet printers.\", \"target\": \"laser\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"激光\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Laser printers are generally cheaper to maintain than inkjet printers.\", \"target\": \"printers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"打印机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Laser printers are generally cheaper to maintain than inkjet printers.\", \"target\": \"generally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Laser printers are generally cheaper to maintain than inkjet printers.\", \"target\": \"maintain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"维护\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to tell Englishmen from Americans just by the way they look.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to tell Englishmen from Americans just by the way they look.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"辨别\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was raining when we left, but by the time we arrived, it was sunny.\", \"target\": \"raining\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was raining when we left, but by the time we arrived, it was sunny.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was raining when we left, but by the time we arrived, it was sunny.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was raining when we left, but by the time we arrived, it was sunny.\", \"target\": \"arrived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"known\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I'd known that it would come to this, I would have never consented.\", \"target\": \"consented\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"同意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've something interesting to tell you that you might find surprising.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一些事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've something interesting to tell you that you might find surprising.\", \"target\": \"interesting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有趣的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've something interesting to tell you that you might find surprising.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've something interesting to tell you that you might find surprising.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've something interesting to tell you that you might find surprising.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've something interesting to tell you that you might find surprising.\", \"target\": \"surprising\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"令人惊讶的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"looking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"寻找\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"speaker\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"说话者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"correct\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"纠正\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm looking for a native speaker who could help me correct this essay.\", \"target\": \"essay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"文章\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"cellular\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"细胞的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want a cellular phone, but I don't have enough money to pay for one.\", \"target\": \"pay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"find\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"convenient\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"方便的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放置\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you will find it convenient to put a short-cut on the desktop.\", \"target\": \"desktop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"桌面\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I understood everything Tom said, but I'm not absolutely sure.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I understood everything Tom said, but I'm not absolutely sure.\", \"target\": \"understood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I understood everything Tom said, but I'm not absolutely sure.\", \"target\": \"everything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一切\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I understood everything Tom said, but I'm not absolutely sure.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think I understood everything Tom said, but I'm not absolutely sure.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"确定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Having missed the train, I had to wait about an hour for the next one.\", \"target\": \"missed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"错过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Having missed the train, I had to wait about an hour for the next one.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Having missed the train, I had to wait about an hour for the next one.\", \"target\": \"hour\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Had he known what was about to happen, he would have changed his plan.\", \"target\": \"known\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Had he known what was about to happen, he would have changed his plan.\", \"target\": \"happen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Had he known what was about to happen, he would have changed his plan.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Had he known what was about to happen, he would have changed his plan.\", \"target\": \"changed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"改变\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Had he known what was about to happen, he would have changed his plan.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Had he known what was about to happen, he would have changed his plan.\", \"target\": \"plan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry! Even if I drink, it doesn't have an effect on my driving.\", \"target\": \"worry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"担心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry! Even if I drink, it doesn't have an effect on my driving.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"甚至\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry! Even if I drink, it doesn't have an effect on my driving.\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Don't worry! Even if I drink, it doesn't have an effect on my driving.\", \"target\": \"driving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you describe to me the difference between black tea and green tea?\", \"target\": \"describe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"描述\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you describe to me the difference between black tea and green tea?\", \"target\": \"black\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you describe to me the difference between black tea and green tea?\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you describe to me the difference between black tea and green tea?\", \"target\": \"green\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"绿色的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of heavy snow, the plane from Beijing arrived 20 minutes late.\", \"target\": \"heavy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of heavy snow, the plane from Beijing arrived 20 minutes late.\", \"target\": \"snow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of heavy snow, the plane from Beijing arrived 20 minutes late.\", \"target\": \"plane\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of heavy snow, the plane from Beijing arrived 20 minutes late.\", \"target\": \"arrived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of heavy snow, the plane from Beijing arrived 20 minutes late.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of heavy snow, the plane from Beijing arrived 20 minutes late.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've received a lot of applications in answer to our advertisements.\", \"target\": \"received\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"收到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've received a lot of applications in answer to our advertisements.\", \"target\": \"applications\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"申请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've received a lot of applications in answer to our advertisements.\", \"target\": \"answer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"回答\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We've received a lot of applications in answer to our advertisements.\", \"target\": \"advertisements\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"广告\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom got to the station in time to catch the train he wanted to catch.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I sat on a bench in the park and talked while we fed pigeons.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I sat on a bench in the park and talked while we fed pigeons.\", \"target\": \"bench\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"长凳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I sat on a bench in the park and talked while we fed pigeons.\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公园\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom and I sat on a bench in the park and talked while we fed pigeons.\", \"target\": \"talked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"谈话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is nothing worse than doing something in a half-hearted manner.\", \"target\": \"nothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"什么\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is nothing worse than doing something in a half-hearted manner.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更糟的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is nothing worse than doing something in a half-hearted manner.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某事\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There is nothing worse than doing something in a half-hearted manner.\", \"target\": \"manner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方式\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The taller the tree, the more likely it is to be struck by lightning.\", \"target\": \"tree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rescuers searched the surroundings in hopes of finding the child.\", \"target\": \"rescuers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"救援人员\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rescuers searched the surroundings in hopes of finding the child.\", \"target\": \"searched\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"搜索\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rescuers searched the surroundings in hopes of finding the child.\", \"target\": \"surroundings\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rescuers searched the surroundings in hopes of finding the child.\", \"target\": \"hopes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rescuers searched the surroundings in hopes of finding the child.\", \"target\": \"finding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The rescuers searched the surroundings in hopes of finding the child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took full advantage of her stay in London to improve her English.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"利用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She took full advantage of her stay in London to improve her English.\", \"target\": \"improve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"提高\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"nobody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"tears\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"眼泪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"building\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"建筑物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody's going to shed any tears if that old building gets torn down.\", \"target\": \"gets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被拆毁\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most Americans do not object to my calling them by their first names.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大多数\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most Americans do not object to my calling them by their first names.\", \"target\": \"object\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"反对\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most Americans do not object to my calling them by their first names.\", \"target\": \"calling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most Americans do not object to my calling them by their first names.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Most Americans do not object to my calling them by their first names.\", \"target\": \"names\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to believe Tom wasn't aware that Mary was in love with him.\", \"target\": \"aware\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"意识到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's clear that there's a rather strong disagreement between the two.\", \"target\": \"clear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"清楚的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's clear that there's a rather strong disagreement between the two.\", \"target\": \"rather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's clear that there's a rather strong disagreement between the two.\", \"target\": \"disagreement\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分歧\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's clear that there's a rather strong disagreement between the two.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"numeral\", \"zh\": \"二\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"teach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"教\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"someone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's better to teach someone how to fish than to give someone a fish.\", \"target\": \"someone\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a few minutes we'll be landing at New Tokyo International Airport.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a few minutes we'll be landing at New Tokyo International Airport.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a few minutes we'll be landing at New Tokyo International Airport.\", \"target\": \"landing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"降落\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a few minutes we'll be landing at New Tokyo International Airport.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In a few minutes we'll be landing at New Tokyo International Airport.\", \"target\": \"airport\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机场\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for your help, I couldn't have completed the work.\", \"target\": \"help\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for your help, I couldn't have completed the work.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for your help, I couldn't have completed the work.\", \"target\": \"completed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for your help, I couldn't have completed the work.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"earn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"worked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wanted to earn some money, so I worked part time three days a week.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's dangerous to climb a mountain on a day when it's stormy.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's dangerous to climb a mountain on a day when it's stormy.\", \"target\": \"dangerous\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"危险的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's dangerous to climb a mountain on a day when it's stormy.\", \"target\": \"climb\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"攀登\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's dangerous to climb a mountain on a day when it's stormy.\", \"target\": \"mountain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"山\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's dangerous to climb a mountain on a day when it's stormy.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think it's dangerous to climb a mountain on a day when it's stormy.\", \"target\": \"stormy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"暴风雨的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't think of any other way of getting him to accept our proposal.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't think of any other way of getting him to accept our proposal.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't think of any other way of getting him to accept our proposal.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't think of any other way of getting him to accept our proposal.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't think of any other way of getting him to accept our proposal.\", \"target\": \"proposal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"提议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I agree on an emotional level, but on the pragmatic level I disagree.\", \"target\": \"agree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"同意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I agree on an emotional level, but on the pragmatic level I disagree.\", \"target\": \"emotional\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"情绪上的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I agree on an emotional level, but on the pragmatic level I disagree.\", \"target\": \"pragmatic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"务实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I agree on an emotional level, but on the pragmatic level I disagree.\", \"target\": \"disagree\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不同意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His intelligence and experience enabled him to deal with the trouble.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His intelligence and experience enabled him to deal with the trouble.\", \"target\": \"intelligence\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"智力\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His intelligence and experience enabled him to deal with the trouble.\", \"target\": \"experience\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"经验\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His intelligence and experience enabled him to deal with the trouble.\", \"target\": \"enabled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His intelligence and experience enabled him to deal with the trouble.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't seem to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"seem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't seem to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"aware\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"意识到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't seem to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"conflict\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冲突\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He doesn't seem to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I were inseparable friends during our time together in school.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and I were inseparable friends during our time together in school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody talks about the weather, but nobody does anything about it.\", \"target\": \"everybody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody talks about the weather, but nobody does anything about it.\", \"target\": \"talks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"谈论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody talks about the weather, but nobody does anything about it.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody talks about the weather, but nobody does anything about it.\", \"target\": \"nobody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody talks about the weather, but nobody does anything about it.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"sun\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"太阳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"rise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"升起\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"west\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"西边\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"change\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"改变\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even if the sun were to rise in the west, I would not change my mind.\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.\", \"target\": \"right\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"正确地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Always do right. This will gratify some people and astonish the rest.\", \"target\": \"astonish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使惊讶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Do you know when they will arrive?\\\" \\\"At eleven-thirty this evening.\\\"\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Do you know when they will arrive?\\\" \\\"At eleven-thirty this evening.\\\"\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Do you know when they will arrive?\\\" \\\"At eleven-thirty this evening.\\\"\", \"target\": \"arrive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Do you know when they will arrive?\\\" \\\"At eleven-thirty this evening.\\\"\", \"target\": \"eleven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"十一点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Do you know when they will arrive?\\\" \\\"At eleven-thirty this evening.\\\"\", \"target\": \"thirty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"三十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"learn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"boxing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"拳击\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"thinks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wants to learn boxing, but his mother thinks it's too dangerous.\", \"target\": \"dangerous\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"危险的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary not to waste her time trying to convince John to help.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom started as a janitor, but he's now the president of the company.\", \"target\": \"started\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom started as a janitor, but he's now the president of the company.\", \"target\": \"president\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"总统\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom started as a janitor, but he's now the president of the company.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't have enough time to answer all the questions on the test.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't have enough time to answer all the questions on the test.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't have enough time to answer all the questions on the test.\", \"target\": \"answer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回答\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't have enough time to answer all the questions on the test.\", \"target\": \"questions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't have enough time to answer all the questions on the test.\", \"target\": \"test\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"测试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked me to tell you he didn't plan on going to Boston with you.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"要求\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked me to tell you he didn't plan on going to Boston with you.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked me to tell you he didn't plan on going to Boston with you.\", \"target\": \"plan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The unemployment rate in Japan was 3.4 percent in September of 2015.\", \"target\": \"unemployment\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"失业率\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The unemployment rate in Japan was 3.4 percent in September of 2015.\", \"target\": \"rate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比率\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The unemployment rate in Japan was 3.4 percent in September of 2015.\", \"target\": \"percent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百分比\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The unemployment rate in Japan was 3.4 percent in September of 2015.\", \"target\": \"september\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"九月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only difference between a bad cook and a poisoner is the intent.\", \"target\": \"difference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"差异\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only difference between a bad cook and a poisoner is the intent.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only difference between a bad cook and a poisoner is the intent.\", \"target\": \"cook\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only difference between a bad cook and a poisoner is the intent.\", \"target\": \"poisoner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"毒药师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The only difference between a bad cook and a poisoner is the intent.\", \"target\": \"intent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"意图\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flash wasn't working, so he couldn't take a picture in the dark.\", \"target\": \"flash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"闪光灯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flash wasn't working, so he couldn't take a picture in the dark.\", \"target\": \"working\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flash wasn't working, so he couldn't take a picture in the dark.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flash wasn't working, so he couldn't take a picture in the dark.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拍摄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flash wasn't working, so he couldn't take a picture in the dark.\", \"target\": \"picture\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"照片\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The flash wasn't working, so he couldn't take a picture in the dark.\", \"target\": \"dark\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"黑暗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The death penalty had been done away with in many states in the USA.\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The death penalty had been done away with in many states in the USA.\", \"target\": \"penalty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"刑罚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The death penalty had been done away with in many states in the USA.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The death penalty had been done away with in many states in the USA.\", \"target\": \"states\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"州\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our task has been easy so far, but it will be difficult from now on.\", \"target\": \"task\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"任务\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our task has been easy so far, but it will be difficult from now on.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our task has been easy so far, but it will be difficult from now on.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Our task has been easy so far, but it will be difficult from now on.\", \"target\": \"difficult\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"island\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"岛屿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"towns\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城镇\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"On this small island are two large towns and many small settlements.\", \"target\": \"settlements\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"定居点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in the habit of reading the newspaper before breakfast.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in the habit of reading the newspaper before breakfast.\", \"target\": \"habit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in the habit of reading the newspaper before breakfast.\", \"target\": \"newspaper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"报纸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father is in the habit of reading the newspaper before breakfast.\", \"target\": \"breakfast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father had already finished breakfast when I got up this morning.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father had already finished breakfast when I got up this morning.\", \"target\": \"already\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"已经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father had already finished breakfast when I got up this morning.\", \"target\": \"finished\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father had already finished breakfast when I got up this morning.\", \"target\": \"breakfast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father had already finished breakfast when I got up this morning.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father had already finished breakfast when I got up this morning.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's difficult for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"difficult\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's difficult for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"understand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's difficult for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"spoken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"口语的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's difficult for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"quickly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"迅速地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the light of what you told us, I think we should revise our plan.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the light of what you told us, I think we should revise our plan.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the light of what you told us, I think we should revise our plan.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the light of what you told us, I think we should revise our plan.\", \"target\": \"revise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修改\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In the light of what you told us, I think we should revise our plan.\", \"target\": \"plan\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In some countries, the punishment for treason can be life in prison.\", \"target\": \"countries\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In some countries, the punishment for treason can be life in prison.\", \"target\": \"punishment\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"惩罚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In some countries, the punishment for treason can be life in prison.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生命\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In some countries, the punishment for treason can be life in prison.\", \"target\": \"prison\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"监狱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If two men always have the same opinion, one of them is unnecessary.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"两个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If two men always have the same opinion, one of them is unnecessary.\", \"target\": \"men\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If two men always have the same opinion, one of them is unnecessary.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If two men always have the same opinion, one of them is unnecessary.\", \"target\": \"opinion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"意见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If two men always have the same opinion, one of them is unnecessary.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If two men always have the same opinion, one of them is unnecessary.\", \"target\": \"unnecessary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不必要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never lived on a farm, but both of my parents grew up on farms.\", \"target\": \"never\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"从不\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never lived on a farm, but both of my parents grew up on farms.\", \"target\": \"lived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never lived on a farm, but both of my parents grew up on farms.\", \"target\": \"farm\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"农场\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never lived on a farm, but both of my parents grew up on farms.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never lived on a farm, but both of my parents grew up on farms.\", \"target\": \"grew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've never lived on a farm, but both of my parents grew up on farms.\", \"target\": \"farms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"农场\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"finished\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"VBD\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"reading\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阅读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"novel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll have finished reading this novel by the time you come tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that Liszt's \\\"Forgotten Waltz No.3\\\" is a hidden masterpiece.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom would be a good basketball coach. That's why I hired him.\", \"target\": \"knew\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom would be a good basketball coach. That's why I hired him.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom would be a good basketball coach. That's why I hired him.\", \"target\": \"basketball\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"篮球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom would be a good basketball coach. That's why I hired him.\", \"target\": \"coach\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教练\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I knew Tom would be a good basketball coach. That's why I hired him.\", \"target\": \"hired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"雇用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't remember the meaning of the word that I looked up yesterday.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't remember the meaning of the word that I looked up yesterday.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't remember the meaning of the word that I looked up yesterday.\", \"target\": \"meaning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"意思\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't remember the meaning of the word that I looked up yesterday.\", \"target\": \"word\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"词\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't remember the meaning of the word that I looked up yesterday.\", \"target\": \"looked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"查找\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't remember the meaning of the word that I looked up yesterday.\", \"target\": \"yesterday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father makes sure that all the lights are off before he goes to bed.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father makes sure that all the lights are off before he goes to bed.\", \"target\": \"makes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"确保\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father makes sure that all the lights are off before he goes to bed.\", \"target\": \"lights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"灯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father makes sure that all the lights are off before he goes to bed.\", \"target\": \"goes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Father makes sure that all the lights are off before he goes to bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"starve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"挨饿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"death\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"死亡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know how many people in the world starve to death every year?\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the guidebook, this is the best restaurant around here.\", \"target\": \"according\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the guidebook, this is the best restaurant around here.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"According to the guidebook, this is the best restaurant around here.\", \"target\": \"restaurant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're going to wreck your eyesight if you play games all the time.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"将要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're going to wreck your eyesight if you play games all the time.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're going to wreck your eyesight if you play games all the time.\", \"target\": \"games\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游戏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You're going to wreck your eyesight if you play games all the time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to Dad for not coming home in time for supper.\", \"target\": \"apologize\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"道歉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to Dad for not coming home in time for supper.\", \"target\": \"dad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爸爸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to Dad for not coming home in time for supper.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"回家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should apologize to Dad for not coming home in time for supper.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This problem is too difficult for primary school children to solve.\", \"target\": \"problem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This problem is too difficult for primary school children to solve.\", \"target\": \"difficult\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This problem is too difficult for primary school children to solve.\", \"target\": \"primary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"主要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This problem is too difficult for primary school children to solve.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This problem is too difficult for primary school children to solve.\", \"target\": \"solve\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is a secret just between you and me, so don't let it slip out.\", \"target\": \"secret\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"秘密\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a minute of silence and then everybody started screaming.\", \"target\": \"minute\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a minute of silence and then everybody started screaming.\", \"target\": \"silence\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"沉默\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a minute of silence and then everybody started screaming.\", \"target\": \"everybody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a minute of silence and then everybody started screaming.\", \"target\": \"started\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There was a minute of silence and then everybody started screaming.\", \"target\": \"screaming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尖叫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are many more students in the classroom today than yesterday.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are many more students in the classroom today than yesterday.\", \"target\": \"students\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are many more students in the classroom today than yesterday.\", \"target\": \"classroom\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are many more students in the classroom today than yesterday.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are many more students in the classroom today than yesterday.\", \"target\": \"yesterday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"昨天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the painting was estimated at several million dollars.\", \"target\": \"value\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"价值\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the painting was estimated at several million dollars.\", \"target\": \"painting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绘画\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the painting was estimated at several million dollars.\", \"target\": \"estimated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"估计\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the painting was estimated at several million dollars.\", \"target\": \"several\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"几个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the painting was estimated at several million dollars.\", \"target\": \"dollars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"美元\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The traveler was delighted at the sight of a light in the distance.\", \"target\": \"traveler\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The traveler was delighted at the sight of a light in the distance.\", \"target\": \"delighted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The traveler was delighted at the sight of a light in the distance.\", \"target\": \"sight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"景象\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The traveler was delighted at the sight of a light in the distance.\", \"target\": \"light\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"光\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The traveler was delighted at the sight of a light in the distance.\", \"target\": \"distance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"距离\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher pointed her finger at me and asked me to come with her.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher pointed her finger at me and asked me to come with her.\", \"target\": \"finger\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手指\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher pointed her finger at me and asked me to come with her.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The teacher pointed her finger at me and asked me to come with her.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Switzerland is situated between France, Italy, Austria and Germany.\", \"target\": \"situated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"位于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She told me once and for all that she did not want to see me again.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She told me once and for all that she did not want to see me again.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She told me once and for all that she did not want to see me again.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't forget to put a stamp on the letter before mailing it.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't forget to put a stamp on the letter before mailing it.\", \"target\": \"forget\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't forget to put a stamp on the letter before mailing it.\", \"target\": \"stamp\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邮票\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't forget to put a stamp on the letter before mailing it.\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please don't forget to put a stamp on the letter before mailing it.\", \"target\": \"mailing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"邮寄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"None of this would've been necessary if we'd followed Tom's advice.\", \"target\": \"none\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"None of this would've been necessary if we'd followed Tom's advice.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"None of this would've been necessary if we'd followed Tom's advice.\", \"target\": \"necessary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"必要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"None of this would've been necessary if we'd followed Tom's advice.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"None of this would've been necessary if we'd followed Tom's advice.\", \"target\": \"followed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遵循\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"None of this would've been necessary if we'd followed Tom's advice.\", \"target\": \"advice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"建议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was through his influence that she became interested in ecology.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was through his influence that she became interested in ecology.\", \"target\": \"influence\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"影响\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was through his influence that she became interested in ecology.\", \"target\": \"became\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was through his influence that she became interested in ecology.\", \"target\": \"interested\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"感兴趣的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was through his influence that she became interested in ecology.\", \"target\": \"ecology\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生态学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me more than two hours to translate a few pages of English.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me more than two hours to translate a few pages of English.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me more than two hours to translate a few pages of English.\", \"target\": \"hours\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me more than two hours to translate a few pages of English.\", \"target\": \"translate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻译\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took me more than two hours to translate a few pages of English.\", \"target\": \"pages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"页\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"kind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In this kind of weather, it's best to stay home and not go outside.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you heard her speak English, you would take her for an American.\", \"target\": \"heard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you heard her speak English, you would take her for an American.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you heard her speak English, you would take her for an American.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a child, but sometimes you talk to me as if I were a child.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm not a child, but sometimes you talk to me as if I were a child.\", \"target\": \"sometimes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lost my father to a subarachnoid haemorrhage when I was fourteen.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"失去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lost my father to a subarachnoid haemorrhage when I was fourteen.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I lost my father to a subarachnoid haemorrhage when I was fourteen.\", \"target\": \"fourteen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"十四\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have so many things to tell you that I don't know where to start.\", \"target\": \"start\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His wife is in the hospital because she was injured in a car crash.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His wife is in the hospital because she was injured in a car crash.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His wife is in the hospital because she was injured in a car crash.\", \"target\": \"hospital\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His wife is in the hospital because she was injured in a car crash.\", \"target\": \"injured\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"受伤\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His wife is in the hospital because she was injured in a car crash.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His wife is in the hospital because she was injured in a car crash.\", \"target\": \"crash\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"碰撞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"annoyed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"烦恼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was always annoyed in the city by noises of one sort or another.\", \"target\": \"noises\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"噪音\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"devoted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"奉献\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生命\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He devoted the last years of his life to writing his autobiography.\", \"target\": \"writing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He announced that he would come at once and investigate the matter.\", \"target\": \"announced\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"宣布\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He announced that he would come at once and investigate the matter.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He announced that he would come at once and investigate the matter.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He announced that he would come at once and investigate the matter.\", \"target\": \"investigate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"调查\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He announced that he would come at once and investigate the matter.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"留下\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"problem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"education\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教育\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He always left the problem of his children's education to his wife.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First off, I'd like you to come with me to a department store sale.\", \"target\": \"department\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"部门\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone is anxious to know what has become of the former champion.\", \"target\": \"everyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone is anxious to know what has become of the former champion.\", \"target\": \"anxious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"焦虑的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone is anxious to know what has become of the former champion.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone is anxious to know what has become of the former champion.\", \"target\": \"become\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everyone is anxious to know what has become of the former champion.\", \"target\": \"champion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冠军\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of his wealth, he was able to become a member of that club.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of his wealth, he was able to become a member of that club.\", \"target\": \"wealth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"财富\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of his wealth, he was able to become a member of that club.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有能力的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of his wealth, he was able to become a member of that club.\", \"target\": \"become\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of his wealth, he was able to become a member of that club.\", \"target\": \"club\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"俱乐部\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A year has passed, but it's as if we saw each other only yesterday.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A year has passed, but it's as if we saw each other only yesterday.\", \"target\": \"passed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"经过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A year has passed, but it's as if we saw each other only yesterday.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bookstore in that location wouldn't make enough money to survive.\", \"target\": \"location\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"位置\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bookstore in that location wouldn't make enough money to survive.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bookstore in that location wouldn't make enough money to survive.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bookstore in that location wouldn't make enough money to survive.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"足够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bookstore in that location wouldn't make enough money to survive.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A bookstore in that location wouldn't make enough money to survive.\", \"target\": \"survive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生存\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"die\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去世\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"young\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年轻的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"saying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谚语\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"The good die young\\\" is an old saying which may or may not be true.\", \"target\": \"true\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've worked hard for months and have certainly earned a holiday.\", \"target\": \"worked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've worked hard for months and have certainly earned a holiday.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"努力地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've worked hard for months and have certainly earned a holiday.\", \"target\": \"months\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"几个月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've worked hard for months and have certainly earned a holiday.\", \"target\": \"certainly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"当然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've worked hard for months and have certainly earned a holiday.\", \"target\": \"earned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赚到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You've worked hard for months and have certainly earned a holiday.\", \"target\": \"holiday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"假期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We found it very hard going back to our base camp in the blizzard.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We found it very hard going back to our base camp in the blizzard.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We found it very hard going back to our base camp in the blizzard.\", \"target\": \"base\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"基地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was wearing a bulletproof vest, so the bullet didn't kill him.\", \"target\": \"wearing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿着\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was wearing a bulletproof vest, so the bullet didn't kill him.\", \"target\": \"bullet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"子弹\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was wearing a bulletproof vest, so the bullet didn't kill him.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was admiring my new car at the time the truck crashed into it.\", \"target\": \"admiring\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欣赏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was admiring my new car at the time the truck crashed into it.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was admiring my new car at the time the truck crashed into it.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was admiring my new car at the time the truck crashed into it.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was admiring my new car at the time the truck crashed into it.\", \"target\": \"truck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卡车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted Mary's phone number, but she refused to give it to him.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted Mary's phone number, but she refused to give it to him.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted Mary's phone number, but she refused to give it to him.\", \"target\": \"number\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom wanted Mary's phone number, but she refused to give it to him.\", \"target\": \"refused\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拒绝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put the large picnic basket on the passenger seat next to him.\", \"target\": \"put\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"放\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put the large picnic basket on the passenger seat next to him.\", \"target\": \"basket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"篮子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom put the large picnic basket on the passenger seat next to him.\", \"target\": \"passenger\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乘客\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"recent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最近的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"shortage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"短缺\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"coffee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"咖啡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"recent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最近的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"shortage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"短缺\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"coffee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"咖啡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The recent shortage of coffee has given rise to a lot of problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dolphin and trainer communicated much better than we expected.\", \"target\": \"trainer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"训练员\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dolphin and trainer communicated much better than we expected.\", \"target\": \"communicated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"沟通\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dolphin and trainer communicated much better than we expected.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"非常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dolphin and trainer communicated much better than we expected.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The dolphin and trainer communicated much better than we expected.\", \"target\": \"expected\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"期望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The average height of girls in this class is over 155 centimeters.\", \"target\": \"average\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"平均的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The average height of girls in this class is over 155 centimeters.\", \"target\": \"height\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"身高\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The average height of girls in this class is over 155 centimeters.\", \"target\": \"girls\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女孩们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how often I tell her, she keeps making the same mistake.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how often I tell her, she keeps making the same mistake.\", \"target\": \"often\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"经常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how often I tell her, she keeps making the same mistake.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how often I tell her, she keeps making the same mistake.\", \"target\": \"keeps\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how often I tell her, she keeps making the same mistake.\", \"target\": \"mistake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"错误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife often telephones me when I'm traveling in another country.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife often telephones me when I'm traveling in another country.\", \"target\": \"often\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"经常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife often telephones me when I'm traveling in another country.\", \"target\": \"telephones\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife often telephones me when I'm traveling in another country.\", \"target\": \"traveling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My wife often telephones me when I'm traveling in another country.\", \"target\": \"country\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always said that heaven helps those who help themselves.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always said that heaven helps those who help themselves.\", \"target\": \"always\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"总是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always said that heaven helps those who help themselves.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always said that heaven helps those who help themselves.\", \"target\": \"heaven\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天堂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father always said that heaven helps those who help themselves.\", \"target\": \"helps\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car broke down this morning and won't be repaired until Friday.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car broke down this morning and won't be repaired until Friday.\", \"target\": \"broke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坏了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car broke down this morning and won't be repaired until Friday.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car broke down this morning and won't be repaired until Friday.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car broke down this morning and won't be repaired until Friday.\", \"target\": \"repaired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My car broke down this morning and won't be repaired until Friday.\", \"target\": \"friday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期五\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"上个月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"month\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"twenty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"二十岁的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"daughter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"gave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"birth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"分娩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"baby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婴儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Last month our twenty-year-old daughter gave birth to a baby girl.\", \"target\": \"girl\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女孩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"plans\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's one thing to make plans, but quite another to carry them out.\", \"target\": \"plans\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems that the only time he isn't eating is when he's sleeping.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems that the only time he isn't eating is when he's sleeping.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems that the only time he isn't eating is when he's sleeping.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems that the only time he isn't eating is when he's sleeping.\", \"target\": \"sleeping\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"spite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"尽管\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"heavy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"visited\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"friend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In spite of the heavy rain, he visited his friend in the hospital.\", \"target\": \"hospital\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you had left home a little earlier you would have been in time.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you had left home a little earlier you would have been in time.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you had left home a little earlier you would have been in time.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you had left home a little earlier you would have been in time.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you had left home a little earlier you would have been in time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't have anything nice to say, don't say anything at all.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you don't have anything nice to say, don't say anything at all.\", \"target\": \"nice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If the lion is the king of beasts, the eagle is the king of birds.\", \"target\": \"lion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狮子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If the lion is the king of beasts, the eagle is the king of birds.\", \"target\": \"king\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国王\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If the lion is the king of beasts, the eagle is the king of birds.\", \"target\": \"beasts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"野兽\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If the lion is the king of beasts, the eagle is the king of birds.\", \"target\": \"birds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鸟类\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going over to Tom's house now to tell him about what happened.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going over to Tom's house now to tell him about what happened.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going over to Tom's house now to tell him about what happened.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm going over to Tom's house now to tell him about what happened.\", \"target\": \"happened\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad that they fixed the heating system, but now it's too hot.\", \"target\": \"glad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"高兴的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad that they fixed the heating system, but now it's too hot.\", \"target\": \"fixed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad that they fixed the heating system, but now it's too hot.\", \"target\": \"heating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"供暖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad that they fixed the heating system, but now it's too hot.\", \"target\": \"system\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"系统\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'm glad that they fixed the heating system, but now it's too hot.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"continue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"poisoning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物中毒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"hot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"热的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"continue\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"继续\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Hot weather will continue, so please watch out for food poisoning.\", \"target\": \"poisoning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物中毒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was an excellent scientist, and what is more, was a great poet.\", \"target\": \"excellent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"优秀的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was an excellent scientist, and what is more, was a great poet.\", \"target\": \"scientist\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"科学家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was an excellent scientist, and what is more, was a great poet.\", \"target\": \"poet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"诗人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems not to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems not to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"aware\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"意识到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He seems not to be aware of the conflict between my father and me.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"four\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"四\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"hundred\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一百\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"million\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"百万\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Four hundred million people speak English as their first language.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the typhoon, my parents ended their trip one day early.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the typhoon, my parents ended their trip one day early.\", \"target\": \"ended\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Because of the typhoon, my parents ended their trip one day early.\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we are told not to come, we become all the more eager to go.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被告知\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we are told not to come, we become all the more eager to go.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we are told not to come, we become all the more eager to go.\", \"target\": \"become\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we are told not to come, we become all the more eager to go.\", \"target\": \"eager\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"渴望的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When we are told not to come, we become all the more eager to go.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When she was in Los Angeles, she had at least six different jobs.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When she was in Los Angeles, she had at least six different jobs.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When she was in Los Angeles, she had at least six different jobs.\", \"target\": \"jobs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What Tom really wanted was enough money to buy Mary some flowers.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真正地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What Tom really wanted was enough money to buy Mary some flowers.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What Tom really wanted was enough money to buy Mary some flowers.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What Tom really wanted was enough money to buy Mary some flowers.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What Tom really wanted was enough money to buy Mary some flowers.\", \"target\": \"flowers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"adult\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"成人的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"tickets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"票\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿童\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Two adult tickets and three children's tickets to London, please.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows where we can get something to eat around here.\", \"target\": \"probably\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows where we can get something to eat around here.\", \"target\": \"knows\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably knows where we can get something to eat around here.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to tell Mary what time the meeting was going to start.\", \"target\": \"forgot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"忘记\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to tell Mary what time the meeting was going to start.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom forgot to tell Mary what time the meeting was going to start.\", \"target\": \"meeting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This will be a good souvenir of my trip around the United States.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This will be a good souvenir of my trip around the United States.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This will be a good souvenir of my trip around the United States.\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This will be a good souvenir of my trip around the United States.\", \"target\": \"united\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"联合的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was so crowded that I had to keep standing all the way.\", \"target\": \"train\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was so crowded that I had to keep standing all the way.\", \"target\": \"crowded\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"拥挤的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The train was so crowded that I had to keep standing all the way.\", \"target\": \"standing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"站立\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The leaves of the trees in the garden have turned completely red.\", \"target\": \"leaves\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树叶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The leaves of the trees in the garden have turned completely red.\", \"target\": \"trees\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The leaves of the trees in the garden have turned completely red.\", \"target\": \"garden\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花园\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The leaves of the trees in the garden have turned completely red.\", \"target\": \"completely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The leaves of the trees in the garden have turned completely red.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby caught sight of my ballpoint pen and reached out for it.\", \"target\": \"baby\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婴儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby caught sight of my ballpoint pen and reached out for it.\", \"target\": \"caught\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"抓住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby caught sight of my ballpoint pen and reached out for it.\", \"target\": \"sight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"视线\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The baby caught sight of my ballpoint pen and reached out for it.\", \"target\": \"pen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢笔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Students generally like a teacher who understands their problems.\", \"target\": \"students\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Students generally like a teacher who understands their problems.\", \"target\": \"generally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Students generally like a teacher who understands their problems.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Students generally like a teacher who understands their problems.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Students generally like a teacher who understands their problems.\", \"target\": \"understands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Students generally like a teacher who understands their problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the roses in my garden are white, and the others are red.\", \"target\": \"roses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"玫瑰\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the roses in my garden are white, and the others are red.\", \"target\": \"garden\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"花园\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the roses in my garden are white, and the others are red.\", \"target\": \"white\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"白色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the roses in my garden are white, and the others are red.\", \"target\": \"red\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"红色\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"formed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"形成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"habit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you have formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"easily\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"容易地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"office\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"办公室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"fourth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal number\", \"zh\": \"第四\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"floor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"楼层\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My office is on the fourth floor of that gray six-story building.\", \"target\": \"building\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"建筑物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"takes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Money takes a long time to earn, but you can spend it in no time.\", \"target\": \"earn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans.\", \"target\": \"happens\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙碌的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans.\", \"target\": \"making\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"制作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans.\", \"target\": \"plans\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"计划\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was an advantage having learned Chinese while I was in school.\", \"target\": \"advantage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was an advantage having learned Chinese while I was in school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is out of the question for you to go to New York this weekend.\", \"target\": \"question\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is out of the question for you to go to New York this weekend.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is out of the question for you to go to New York this weekend.\", \"target\": \"weekend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周末\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case the shipment is delayed, we have special delay insurance.\", \"target\": \"shipment\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"货物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In case the shipment is delayed, we have special delay insurance.\", \"target\": \"insurance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"保险\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"another\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"另一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"weeks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"able\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In another two weeks you will be able to get out of the hospital.\", \"target\": \"hospital\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Canada, there are many areas where it is illegal to log trees.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Canada, there are many areas where it is illegal to log trees.\", \"target\": \"areas\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"区域\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Canada, there are many areas where it is illegal to log trees.\", \"target\": \"illegal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"非法的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In Canada, there are many areas where it is illegal to log trees.\", \"target\": \"trees\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"树\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to make a call to Tokyo, Japan. The number is 3202-5625.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to make a call to Tokyo, Japan. The number is 3202-5625.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to make a call to Tokyo, Japan. The number is 3202-5625.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"做\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to make a call to Tokyo, Japan. The number is 3202-5625.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'd like to make a call to Tokyo, Japan. The number is 3202-5625.\", \"target\": \"number\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was busy packing, because I was leaving for France in two days.\", \"target\": \"busy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"忙碌的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was busy packing, because I was leaving for France in two days.\", \"target\": \"packing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打包\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was busy packing, because I was leaving for France in two days.\", \"target\": \"leaving\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was busy packing, because I was leaving for France in two days.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"两\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I was busy packing, because I was leaving for France in two days.\", \"target\": \"days\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"chance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I hope I will have a chance to see you next time I'm in New York.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't seen you for ages. Do you remember when I saw you last?\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"见过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my umbrella somewhere in the park. I have to buy one.\", \"target\": \"lost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"丢失\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my umbrella somewhere in the park. I have to buy one.\", \"target\": \"umbrella\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雨伞\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my umbrella somewhere in the park. I have to buy one.\", \"target\": \"somewhere\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"某处\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my umbrella somewhere in the park. I have to buy one.\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公园\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my umbrella somewhere in the park. I have to buy one.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have lost my umbrella somewhere in the park. I have to buy one.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I crossed the equator for the first time on my trip to Australia.\", \"target\": \"crossed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"穿过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I crossed the equator for the first time on my trip to Australia.\", \"target\": \"equator\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"赤道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I crossed the equator for the first time on my trip to Australia.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I crossed the equator for the first time on my trip to Australia.\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His name was on the tip of my tongue, but I couldn't remember it.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His name was on the tip of my tongue, but I couldn't remember it.\", \"target\": \"name\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His name was on the tip of my tongue, but I couldn't remember it.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His name was on the tip of my tongue, but I couldn't remember it.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you spare me a few minutes? I'd like to have a word with you.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you spare me a few minutes? I'd like to have a word with you.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Can you spare me a few minutes? I'd like to have a word with you.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Austria is one of the largest producers of electricity in Europe.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Austria is one of the largest producers of electricity in Europe.\", \"target\": \"producers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生产商\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Austria is one of the largest producers of electricity in Europe.\", \"target\": \"electricity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As a matter of fact, I haven't eaten anything since this morning.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As a matter of fact, I haven't eaten anything since this morning.\", \"target\": \"fact\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事实\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As a matter of fact, I haven't eaten anything since this morning.\", \"target\": \"eaten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As a matter of fact, I haven't eaten anything since this morning.\", \"target\": \"anything\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"任何东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As a matter of fact, I haven't eaten anything since this morning.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure.\", \"target\": \"ignorance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"无知\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure.\", \"target\": \"confidence\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"自信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure.\", \"target\": \"success\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"成功\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"确定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A considerable amount of time and effort have been spent already.\", \"target\": \"considerable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"相当大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A considerable amount of time and effort have been spent already.\", \"target\": \"amount\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A considerable amount of time and effort have been spent already.\", \"target\": \"effort\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"努力\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you be at my party tomorrow night?\\\" \\\"I'll try to be there.\\\"\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you be at my party tomorrow night?\\\" \\\"I'll try to be there.\\\"\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you be at my party tomorrow night?\\\" \\\"I'll try to be there.\\\"\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 2}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you be at my party tomorrow night?\\\" \\\"I'll try to be there.\\\"\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"We haven't seen each other since 2009.\\\" \\\"Has it been that long?\\\"\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"见过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should do that as often as you can while you're still young.\", \"target\": \"often\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"经常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should do that as often as you can while you're still young.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should do that as often as you can while you're still young.\", \"target\": \"young\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年轻的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must've been surprised to meet your teacher in such a place.\", \"target\": \"must\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must've been surprised to meet your teacher in such a place.\", \"target\": \"surprised\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"惊讶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must've been surprised to meet your teacher in such a place.\", \"target\": \"meet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must've been surprised to meet your teacher in such a place.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must've been surprised to meet your teacher in such a place.\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Dad finds out what you've done, he's going to hit the roof.\", \"target\": \"dad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"爸爸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Dad finds out what you've done, he's going to hit the roof.\", \"target\": \"finds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Dad finds out what you've done, he's going to hit the roof.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"出来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When Dad finds out what you've done, he's going to hit the roof.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"将要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going to eat a lot tonight so I hope you're not on a diet.\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going to eat a lot tonight so I hope you're not on a diet.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going to eat a lot tonight so I hope you're not on a diet.\", \"target\": \"lot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going to eat a lot tonight so I hope you're not on a diet.\", \"target\": \"tonight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going to eat a lot tonight so I hope you're not on a diet.\", \"target\": \"hope\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're going to eat a lot tonight so I hope you're not on a diet.\", \"target\": \"diet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"节食\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were faced with an unusual situation because of the accident.\", \"target\": \"unusual\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不寻常的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were faced with an unusual situation because of the accident.\", \"target\": \"situation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"情况\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were faced with an unusual situation because of the accident.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"moved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"移动\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"bags\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"行李\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"elderly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"lady\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女士\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We moved our bags to make room for the elderly lady to sit down.\", \"target\": \"sit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told us this morning that he and Mary were moving to Boston.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told us this morning that he and Mary were moving to Boston.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told us this morning that he and Mary were moving to Boston.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary that she should stop pretending to be intoxicated.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary that she should stop pretending to be intoxicated.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary that she should quit pretending to be intoxicated.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told Mary that she should quit pretending to be intoxicated.\", \"target\": \"quit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he isn't sure if he can do that, but he says he'll try.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he isn't sure if he can do that, but he says he'll try.\", \"target\": \"sure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"确定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom says he isn't sure if he can do that, but he says he'll try.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he thought he might be the only one who had to do that.\", \"target\": \"said\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he thought he might be the only one who had to do that.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he thought he might be the only one who had to do that.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom said he thought he might be the only one who had to do that.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"intends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打算\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"tennis\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"网球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"summer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夏天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom intends to play tennis every day during his summer vacation.\", \"target\": \"vacation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"假期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't want Mary to know that he didn't know how to do that.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't want Mary to know that he didn't know how to do that.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thousands of candles illuminated the church during the ceremony.\", \"target\": \"thousands\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"数千\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thousands of candles illuminated the church during the ceremony.\", \"target\": \"candles\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"蜡烛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thousands of candles illuminated the church during the ceremony.\", \"target\": \"church\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教堂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Thousands of candles illuminated the church during the ceremony.\", \"target\": \"ceremony\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"仪式\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is by far the best novel that has been published this year.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远远地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is by far the best novel that has been published this year.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is by far the best novel that has been published this year.\", \"target\": \"novel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is by far the best novel that has been published this year.\", \"target\": \"published\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"出版\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is by far the best novel that has been published this year.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is for students whose native language is not Japanese.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is for students whose native language is not Japanese.\", \"target\": \"students\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is for students whose native language is not Japanese.\", \"target\": \"whose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"谁的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is for students whose native language is not Japanese.\", \"target\": \"native\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"本地的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book is for students whose native language is not Japanese.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the coins depended on the weight of the metal used.\", \"target\": \"value\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"价值\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the coins depended on the weight of the metal used.\", \"target\": \"coins\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"硬币\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the coins depended on the weight of the metal used.\", \"target\": \"depended\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取决于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The value of the coins depended on the weight of the metal used.\", \"target\": \"metal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"金属\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people suffering from heart disease has increased.\", \"target\": \"number\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people suffering from heart disease has increased.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people suffering from heart disease has increased.\", \"target\": \"suffering\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"受苦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people suffering from heart disease has increased.\", \"target\": \"heart\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心脏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people suffering from heart disease has increased.\", \"target\": \"disease\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"疾病\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of people suffering from heart disease has increased.\", \"target\": \"increased\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"增加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conflict between blacks and whites in the city became worse.\", \"target\": \"conflict\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"冲突\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conflict between blacks and whites in the city became worse.\", \"target\": \"blacks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"黑人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conflict between blacks and whites in the city became worse.\", \"target\": \"whites\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"白人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conflict between blacks and whites in the city became worse.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conflict between blacks and whites in the city became worse.\", \"target\": \"became\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conflict between blacks and whites in the city became worse.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更糟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The accident seemed to have something to do with the heavy snow.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The accident seemed to have something to do with the heavy snow.\", \"target\": \"seemed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The accident seemed to have something to do with the heavy snow.\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某事\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The accident seemed to have something to do with the heavy snow.\", \"target\": \"snow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"雪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some scientists believe that the greenhouse effect is imaginary.\", \"target\": \"scientists\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"科学家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some scientists believe that the greenhouse effect is imaginary.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some scientists believe that the greenhouse effect is imaginary.\", \"target\": \"greenhouse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"温室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some scientists believe that the greenhouse effect is imaginary.\", \"target\": \"effect\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"效应\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some scientists believe that the greenhouse effect is imaginary.\", \"target\": \"imaginary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"虚构的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wouldn't let up until I agreed to go to the movies with her.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"不会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wouldn't let up until I agreed to go to the movies with her.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"允许\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wouldn't let up until I agreed to go to the movies with her.\", \"target\": \"agreed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"同意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She wouldn't let up until I agreed to go to the movies with her.\", \"target\": \"movies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电影\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was very embarrassed when her child behaved badly in public.\", \"target\": \"embarrassed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"尴尬的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was very embarrassed when her child behaved badly in public.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was very embarrassed when her child behaved badly in public.\", \"target\": \"behaved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"表现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was very embarrassed when her child behaved badly in public.\", \"target\": \"badly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"糟糕地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She was very embarrassed when her child behaved badly in public.\", \"target\": \"public\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"公开的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She employed a private detective to keep a watch on her husband.\", \"target\": \"employed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"雇佣\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She employed a private detective to keep a watch on her husband.\", \"target\": \"private\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"私人的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She employed a private detective to keep a watch on her husband.\", \"target\": \"detective\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"侦探\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She employed a private detective to keep a watch on her husband.\", \"target\": \"husband\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"丈夫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"mail\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"邮寄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Please mail this letter the next time you go to the post office.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody understood why the elephant suddenly turned on its owner.\", \"target\": \"nobody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody understood why the elephant suddenly turned on its owner.\", \"target\": \"understood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody understood why the elephant suddenly turned on its owner.\", \"target\": \"elephant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大象\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody understood why the elephant suddenly turned on its owner.\", \"target\": \"suddenly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"突然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody understood why the elephant suddenly turned on its owner.\", \"target\": \"turned\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"转过身\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody understood why the elephant suddenly turned on its owner.\", \"target\": \"owner\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"主人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody noticed that she was absent until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"nobody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"没有人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody noticed that she was absent until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"noticed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注意到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody noticed that she was absent until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"absent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"缺席的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Nobody noticed that she was absent until the end of the meeting.\", \"target\": \"meeting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how hard I try, I can't do it any better than she can.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"无论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how hard I try, I can't do it any better than she can.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"努力地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how hard I try, I can't do it any better than she can.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"No matter how hard I try, I can't do it any better than she can.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father died of a subarachnoid hemorrhage when I was fourteen.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father died of a subarachnoid hemorrhage when I was fourteen.\", \"target\": \"died\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去世\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father died of a subarachnoid hemorrhage when I was fourteen.\", \"target\": \"fourteen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"十四\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is sometimes difficult to make yourself understood in public.\", \"target\": \"sometimes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is sometimes difficult to make yourself understood in public.\", \"target\": \"difficult\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is sometimes difficult to make yourself understood in public.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is sometimes difficult to make yourself understood in public.\", \"target\": \"understood\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is sometimes difficult to make yourself understood in public.\", \"target\": \"public\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"公开的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It hasn't been easy for Tom to deal with Mary's health problems.\", \"target\": \"easy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"容易\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It hasn't been easy for Tom to deal with Mary's health problems.\", \"target\": \"health\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"健康\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It hasn't been easy for Tom to deal with Mary's health problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"look\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"around\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"周围\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you look around, you'll see many people doing the same thing.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think that I now have enough money to buy the car that I want.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I may be unsociable, but it doesn't mean I don't talk to people.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I may be unsociable, but it doesn't mean I don't talk to people.\", \"target\": \"mean\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"意思是\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I may be unsociable, but it doesn't mean I don't talk to people.\", \"target\": \"talk\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I may be unsociable, but it doesn't mean I don't talk to people.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know that Tom talked about me like that behind my back.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I didn't know that Tom talked about me like that behind my back.\", \"target\": \"talked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"谈论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can still remember the time when we went on a picnic together.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can still remember the time when we went on a picnic together.\", \"target\": \"remember\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can still remember the time when we went on a picnic together.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"谎言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"boss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老板\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"discovered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"His lie got him into trouble when his boss discovered the truth.\", \"target\": \"truth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"真相\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a very romantic boyfriend who brings me flowers each night.\", \"target\": \"romantic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"浪漫的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a very romantic boyfriend who brings me flowers each night.\", \"target\": \"boyfriend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He's a very romantic boyfriend who brings me flowers each night.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you ever seen Mt. Fuji? It is beautiful beyond description.\", \"target\": \"ever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you ever seen Mt. Fuji? It is beautiful beyond description.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"见过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you ever seen Mt. Fuji? It is beautiful beyond description.\", \"target\": \"beautiful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"美丽的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Have you ever seen Mt. Fuji? It is beautiful beyond description.\", \"target\": \"description\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"描述\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, I'm studying French at this language school.\", \"target\": \"studying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, I'm studying French at this language school.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody is supposed to know the law, but few people really do.\", \"target\": \"everybody\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody is supposed to know the law, but few people really do.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"应该\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody is supposed to know the law, but few people really do.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody is supposed to know the law, but few people really do.\", \"target\": \"law\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"法律\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody is supposed to know the law, but few people really do.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Everybody is supposed to know the law, but few people really do.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真正地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the difference between a microscope and a telescope?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children depend on their parents for food, clothing and shelter.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children depend on their parents for food, clothing and shelter.\", \"target\": \"depend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"依赖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children depend on their parents for food, clothing and shelter.\", \"target\": \"parents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父母\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children depend on their parents for food, clothing and shelter.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children depend on their parents for food, clothing and shelter.\", \"target\": \"clothing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"衣服\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children depend on their parents for food, clothing and shelter.\", \"target\": \"shelter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"庇护所\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you have some more coffee?\\\" \\\"No, thanks. I've had enough.\\\"\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you have some more coffee?\\\" \\\"No, thanks. I've had enough.\\\"\", \"target\": \"coffee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"咖啡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you have some more coffee?\\\" \\\"No, thanks. I've had enough.\\\"\", \"target\": \"thanks\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"谢谢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Will you have some more coffee?\\\" \\\"No, thanks. I've had enough.\\\"\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Why are you going to Japan?\\\" \\\"To attend a conference in Tokyo.\\\"\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Why are you going to Japan?\\\" \\\"To attend a conference in Tokyo.\\\"\", \"target\": \"attend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Why are you going to Japan?\\\" \\\"To attend a conference in Tokyo.\\\"\", \"target\": \"conference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"陷入\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"trouble\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"麻烦\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"girlfriend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"finds\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You'll get into trouble if your girlfriend finds out the truth.\", \"target\": \"truth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"真相\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were unable to make contact with them until it was too late.\", \"target\": \"unable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were unable to make contact with them until it was too late.\", \"target\": \"make\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"建立\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were unable to make contact with them until it was too late.\", \"target\": \"contact\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"联系\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We were unable to make contact with them until it was too late.\", \"target\": \"late\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"太晚了\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know exactly what it was that Mary wanted him to do.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom didn't know exactly what it was that Mary wanted him to do.\", \"target\": \"exactly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"确切地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To have doubts about oneself is the first sign of intelligence.\", \"target\": \"doubts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"怀疑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To have doubts about oneself is the first sign of intelligence.\", \"target\": \"sign\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"迹象\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"To have doubts about oneself is the first sign of intelligence.\", \"target\": \"intelligence\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"智力\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This year's fashions are completely different from last year's.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This year's fashions are completely different from last year's.\", \"target\": \"fashions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时尚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This year's fashions are completely different from last year's.\", \"target\": \"completely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This year's fashions are completely different from last year's.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would have been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would have been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"killed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would have been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would have been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"gone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would have been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"cliff\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"悬崖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are three empty rooms. However, we can't use any of them.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are three empty rooms. However, we can't use any of them.\", \"target\": \"empty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"空的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are three empty rooms. However, we can't use any of them.\", \"target\": \"rooms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are three empty rooms. However, we can't use any of them.\", \"target\": \"however\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"然而\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There are three empty rooms. However, we can't use any of them.\", \"target\": \"use\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The warrior is conscious of both his strength and his weakness.\", \"target\": \"warrior\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"战士\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The warrior is conscious of both his strength and his weakness.\", \"target\": \"conscious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有意识的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The warrior is conscious of both his strength and his weakness.\", \"target\": \"strength\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"力量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The warrior is conscious of both his strength and his weakness.\", \"target\": \"weakness\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"弱点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The third quarter GNP growth was 1% over the preceding quarter.\", \"target\": \"third\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ordinal number\", \"zh\": \"第三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The third quarter GNP growth was 1% over the preceding quarter.\", \"target\": \"quarter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"季度\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The third quarter GNP growth was 1% over the preceding quarter.\", \"target\": \"growth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"增长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The third quarter GNP growth was 1% over the preceding quarter.\", \"target\": \"preceding\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"先前的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The senator was censured by the congressional ethics committee.\", \"target\": \"senator\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"参议员\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The senator was censured by the congressional ethics committee.\", \"target\": \"ethics\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"伦理\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The senator was censured by the congressional ethics committee.\", \"target\": \"committee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"委员会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"located\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"位于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"five\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"五\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The school is located within five minutes' walk of the station.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police think the burglar entered through a basement window.\", \"target\": \"police\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police think the burglar entered through a basement window.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police think the burglar entered through a basement window.\", \"target\": \"entered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进入\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The police think the burglar entered through a basement window.\", \"target\": \"basement\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地下室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The economy of the island is dependent on the fishing industry.\", \"target\": \"economy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"经济\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The economy of the island is dependent on the fishing industry.\", \"target\": \"island\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"岛屿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The economy of the island is dependent on the fishing industry.\", \"target\": \"dependent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"依赖的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The economy of the island is dependent on the fishing industry.\", \"target\": \"fishing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"捕鱼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The economy of the island is dependent on the fishing industry.\", \"target\": \"industry\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工业\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Six people applied for the job, but none of them were employed.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Six people applied for the job, but none of them were employed.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Six people applied for the job, but none of them were employed.\", \"target\": \"applied\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"申请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Six people applied for the job, but none of them were employed.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Six people applied for the job, but none of them were employed.\", \"target\": \"employed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被雇用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"thousand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一千\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"dollars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"美元\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"expenses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"费用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"One thousand dollars will cover all the expenses for the party.\", \"target\": \"party\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"派对\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"bad\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"坏的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"habit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Once you've formed a bad habit, you can't get rid of it easily.\", \"target\": \"easily\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"容易地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"keep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"marriage\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婚姻\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Keep your eyes wide open before marriage, half shut afterwards.\", \"target\": \"afterwards\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"之后\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"understand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"spoken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"口语的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard for me to understand French when it's spoken quickly.\", \"target\": \"quickly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"迅速地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"makes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"使...有意义; 使...合理\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"sense\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"意义\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"credit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"card\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"balance\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"余额\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It makes sense to pay off your credit card balance every month.\", \"target\": \"month\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"月\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me ten thousand yen to have my television set repaired.\", \"target\": \"cost\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me ten thousand yen to have my television set repaired.\", \"target\": \"ten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一万\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me ten thousand yen to have my television set repaired.\", \"target\": \"television\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电视机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me ten thousand yen to have my television set repaired.\", \"target\": \"set\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"装置\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It cost me ten thousand yen to have my television set repaired.\", \"target\": \"repaired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"修理\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Immediately after it caught fire, the chemical factory blew up.\", \"target\": \"immediately\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立即\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Immediately after it caught fire, the chemical factory blew up.\", \"target\": \"caught\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"着火\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Immediately after it caught fire, the chemical factory blew up.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Immediately after it caught fire, the chemical factory blew up.\", \"target\": \"chemical\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"化学的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Immediately after it caught fire, the chemical factory blew up.\", \"target\": \"factory\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工厂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he were a little younger, he would be eligible for the post.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he were a little younger, he would be eligible for the post.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he were a little younger, he would be eligible for the post.\", \"target\": \"eligible\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有资格的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he were a little younger, he would be eligible for the post.\", \"target\": \"post\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"职位\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If Tom doesn't do what he's supposed to do, please let me know.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If Tom doesn't do what he's supposed to do, please let me know.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no objection to paying a special fee if it is necessary.\", \"target\": \"objection\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"反对\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no objection to paying a special fee if it is necessary.\", \"target\": \"paying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"支付\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no objection to paying a special fee if it is necessary.\", \"target\": \"fee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"费用\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I have no objection to paying a special fee if it is necessary.\", \"target\": \"necessary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"必要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't recommend eating in that restaurant. The food is awful.\", \"target\": \"recommend\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"推荐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't recommend eating in that restaurant. The food is awful.\", \"target\": \"eating\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't recommend eating in that restaurant. The food is awful.\", \"target\": \"restaurant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐厅\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't recommend eating in that restaurant. The food is awful.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't recommend eating in that restaurant. The food is awful.\", \"target\": \"awful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"可怕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that I looked pale and asked me what the matter was.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that I looked pale and asked me what the matter was.\", \"target\": \"looked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看起来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that I looked pale and asked me what the matter was.\", \"target\": \"pale\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"苍白\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that I looked pale and asked me what the matter was.\", \"target\": \"matter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He survived an accident last year, but still drives recklessly.\", \"target\": \"survived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"幸存\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He survived an accident last year, but still drives recklessly.\", \"target\": \"accident\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He survived an accident last year, but still drives recklessly.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"去年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He survived an accident last year, but still drives recklessly.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He survived an accident last year, but still drives recklessly.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He survived an accident last year, but still drives recklessly.\", \"target\": \"drives\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"驾驶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"remembers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"day\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He still remembers the day his mother found out he was smoking.\", \"target\": \"smoking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吸烟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He crept out of the room very carefully to avoid waking her up.\", \"target\": \"crept\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"蹑手蹑脚地走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He crept out of the room very carefully to avoid waking her up.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"出去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He crept out of the room very carefully to avoid waking her up.\", \"target\": \"room\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"wife\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He and his wife tried to work out their problems, but couldn't.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"走\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"straight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"直地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Go straight down this street and turn right at the third light.\", \"target\": \"street\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"街道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, my sister is an assistant in a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"sister\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"妹妹\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, my sister is an assistant in a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"assistant\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"助手\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"For the time being, my sister is an assistant in a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"supermarket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"超市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Environmental pollution is causing abnormal weather conditions.\", \"target\": \"environmental\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"环境的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Environmental pollution is causing abnormal weather conditions.\", \"target\": \"pollution\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"污染\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Environmental pollution is causing abnormal weather conditions.\", \"target\": \"causing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Environmental pollution is causing abnormal weather conditions.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Environmental pollution is causing abnormal weather conditions.\", \"target\": \"conditions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"条件\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is just one of over 2,700 languages in the world today.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is just one of over 2,700 languages in the world today.\", \"target\": \"languages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is just one of over 2,700 languages in the world today.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is just one of over 2,700 languages in the world today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is by far the most widely-spoken language in the world.\", \"target\": \"far\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"远远地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is by far the most widely-spoken language in the world.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is by far the most widely-spoken language in the world.\", \"target\": \"widely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"广泛地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is by far the most widely-spoken language in the world.\", \"target\": \"spoken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"口语的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is by far the most widely-spoken language in the world.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is by far the most widely-spoken language in the world.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is a universal language and is used all over the world.\", \"target\": \"universal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"普遍的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is a universal language and is used all over the world.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"English is a universal language and is used all over the world.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Declarations of variables are extremely important in C and C++.\", \"target\": \"declarations\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"声明\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Declarations of variables are extremely important in C and C++.\", \"target\": \"variables\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"变量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Declarations of variables are extremely important in C and C++.\", \"target\": \"extremely\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"极其\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Declarations of variables are extremely important in C and C++.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the year 2020, the population of our city will have doubled.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the year 2020, the population of our city will have doubled.\", \"target\": \"population\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人口\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the year 2020, the population of our city will have doubled.\", \"target\": \"city\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the year 2020, the population of our city will have doubled.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"By the year 2020, the population of our city will have doubled.\", \"target\": \"doubled\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻倍\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As time went on, rules were added to the game to make it safer.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As time went on, rules were added to the game to make it safer.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"过去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As time went on, rules were added to the game to make it safer.\", \"target\": \"rules\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"规则\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As time went on, rules were added to the game to make it safer.\", \"target\": \"added\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"添加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As time went on, rules were added to the game to make it safer.\", \"target\": \"game\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游戏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she heard the bell ring, she answered the telephone.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she heard the bell ring, she answered the telephone.\", \"target\": \"heard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she heard the bell ring, she answered the telephone.\", \"target\": \"bell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"铃声\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she heard the bell ring, she answered the telephone.\", \"target\": \"answered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"回答\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as she heard the bell ring, she answered the telephone.\", \"target\": \"telephone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You told her that you had finished the work three days before.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You told her that you had finished the work three days before.\", \"target\": \"finished\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You told her that you had finished the work three days before.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You told her that you had finished the work three days before.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't say that kind of thing when children are around.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't say that kind of thing when children are around.\", \"target\": \"kind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't say that kind of thing when children are around.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You shouldn't say that kind of thing when children are around.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must get this homework finished by the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"must\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must get this homework finished by the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must get this homework finished by the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"homework\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"作业\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must get this homework finished by the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"finished\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must get this homework finished by the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You might not like this beer at first. It's an acquired taste.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You might not like this beer at first. It's an acquired taste.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You might not like this beer at first. It's an acquired taste.\", \"target\": \"beer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"啤酒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You might not like this beer at first. It's an acquired taste.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You might not like this beer at first. It's an acquired taste.\", \"target\": \"acquired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"习得的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You might not like this beer at first. It's an acquired taste.\", \"target\": \"taste\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"味道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may injure yourself if you don't follow safety procedures.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may injure yourself if you don't follow safety procedures.\", \"target\": \"injure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"伤害\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may injure yourself if you don't follow safety procedures.\", \"target\": \"safety\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"安全\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You may injure yourself if you don't follow safety procedures.\", \"target\": \"procedures\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"程序\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What I hate most of all is having to recite texts from memory.\", \"target\": \"hate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"恨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What I hate most of all is having to recite texts from memory.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What I hate most of all is having to recite texts from memory.\", \"target\": \"texts\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"文本\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What I hate most of all is having to recite texts from memory.\", \"target\": \"memory\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"记忆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"strike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"罢工\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"improved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"改善\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"wages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工资\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"strike\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"罢工\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"company\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"improved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"改善\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We're on strike because the company hasn't improved our wages.\", \"target\": \"wages\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工资\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We probably don't have enough time to finish doing that today.\", \"target\": \"probably\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We probably don't have enough time to finish doing that today.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We probably don't have enough time to finish doing that today.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We probably don't have enough time to finish doing that today.\", \"target\": \"finish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We probably don't have enough time to finish doing that today.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have less than five minutes to evacuate the whole building.\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"少于\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have less than five minutes to evacuate the whole building.\", \"target\": \"five\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"五\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have less than five minutes to evacuate the whole building.\", \"target\": \"minutes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"分钟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have less than five minutes to evacuate the whole building.\", \"target\": \"evacuate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"疏散\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We have less than five minutes to evacuate the whole building.\", \"target\": \"building\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"建筑物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom would still be alive if he had been wearing his seat belt.\", \"target\": \"alive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"活着的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably doesn't know how to do that as well as Mary does.\", \"target\": \"probably\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom probably doesn't know how to do that as well as Mary does.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom left early this morning, so he should be in Boston by now.\", \"target\": \"left\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"离开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom left early this morning, so he should be in Boston by now.\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"早\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom left early this morning, so he should be in Boston by now.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like it when people cuss in front of his children.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like it when people cuss in front of his children.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't like it when people cuss in front of his children.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked Mary some questions, but she refused to answer them.\", \"target\": \"asked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked Mary some questions, but she refused to answer them.\", \"target\": \"questions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom asked Mary some questions, but she refused to answer them.\", \"target\": \"refused\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拒绝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"helped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"帮助\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They helped one another to make the school festival a success.\", \"target\": \"success\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"成功\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were three uniformed police officers at the crime scene.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were three uniformed police officers at the crime scene.\", \"target\": \"uniformed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"制服的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were three uniformed police officers at the crime scene.\", \"target\": \"police\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警察\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were three uniformed police officers at the crime scene.\", \"target\": \"officers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"警官\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were three uniformed police officers at the crime scene.\", \"target\": \"crime\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"犯罪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were three uniformed police officers at the crime scene.\", \"target\": \"scene\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"现场\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"poet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"诗人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"expressed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"表达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"burning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"燃烧的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"passion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"激情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"woman\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"女人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The poet expressed his burning passion for the woman he loved.\", \"target\": \"loved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kidnapper told me he'd kill Tom if I didn't show up alone.\", \"target\": \"kidnapper\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"绑架者\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kidnapper told me he'd kill Tom if I didn't show up alone.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kidnapper told me he'd kill Tom if I didn't show up alone.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The kidnapper told me he'd kill Tom if I didn't show up alone.\", \"target\": \"kill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"杀死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"sales\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"销售\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"staff\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"员工\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"worked\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The entire sales staff has worked around the clock for a week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"周\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Suppose you had a thousand dollars, what would you do with it?\", \"target\": \"suppose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"假设\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Suppose you had a thousand dollars, what would you do with it?\", \"target\": \"thousand\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一千\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Suppose you had a thousand dollars, what would you do with it?\", \"target\": \"dollars\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"美元\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Suppose you had a thousand dollars, what would you do with it?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the bluest water in the world is found in Crater Lake.\", \"target\": \"water\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"水\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the bluest water in the world is found in Crater Lake.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some of the bluest water in the world is found in Crater Lake.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"找到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She doesn't have any friends or relatives to take care of her.\", \"target\": \"friends\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"朋友\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She doesn't have any friends or relatives to take care of her.\", \"target\": \"relatives\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"亲戚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who drink alcoholic beverages are not allowed to enter.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who drink alcoholic beverages are not allowed to enter.\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who drink alcoholic beverages are not allowed to enter.\", \"target\": \"alcoholic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"酒精的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who drink alcoholic beverages are not allowed to enter.\", \"target\": \"allowed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被允许\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"People who drink alcoholic beverages are not allowed to enter.\", \"target\": \"enter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"进入\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Needless to say, fundamental human rights should be respected.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Needless to say, fundamental human rights should be respected.\", \"target\": \"fundamental\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"基本的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Needless to say, fundamental human rights should be respected.\", \"target\": \"human\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"人类的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Needless to say, fundamental human rights should be respected.\", \"target\": \"rights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"权利\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Needless to say, fundamental human rights should be respected.\", \"target\": \"respected\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尊重\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother has a driver's license, but she doesn't drive a car.\", \"target\": \"mother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"母亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother has a driver's license, but she doesn't drive a car.\", \"target\": \"license\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"执照\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My mother has a driver's license, but she doesn't drive a car.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father participated in a cooking contest and came in first.\", \"target\": \"father\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"父亲\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father participated in a cooking contest and came in first.\", \"target\": \"participated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father participated in a cooking contest and came in first.\", \"target\": \"cooking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"烹饪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father participated in a cooking contest and came in first.\", \"target\": \"contest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"比赛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father participated in a cooking contest and came in first.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My father participated in a cooking contest and came in first.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"London was very important for economical and cultural reasons.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"London was very important for economical and cultural reasons.\", \"target\": \"economical\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"经济上的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"London was very important for economical and cultural reasons.\", \"target\": \"cultural\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"文化上的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"London was very important for economical and cultural reasons.\", \"target\": \"reasons\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"原因\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me stop you right there. We don't want to hear about that.\", \"target\": \"let\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"让\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me stop you right there. We don't want to hear about that.\", \"target\": \"stop\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阻止\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Let me stop you right there. We don't want to hear about that.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Language is the means by which people communicate with others.\", \"target\": \"language\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"语言\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Language is the means by which people communicate with others.\", \"target\": \"means\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手段\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Language is the means by which people communicate with others.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"twenty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"二十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"ago\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"以前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"twenty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"二十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Japan is now very different from what it was twenty years ago.\", \"target\": \"ago\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"以前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is becoming important for us to know how to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"becoming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"变得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is becoming important for us to know how to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is becoming important for us to know how to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is becoming important for us to know how to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It is becoming important for us to know how to use a computer.\", \"target\": \"computer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电脑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Islam first reached China about the middle of the 7th century.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Islam first reached China about the middle of the 7th century.\", \"target\": \"reached\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Islam first reached China about the middle of the 7th century.\", \"target\": \"century\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世纪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If they hadn't noticed, there wouldn't have been any problems.\", \"target\": \"noticed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"注意到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If they hadn't noticed, there wouldn't have been any problems.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If they hadn't noticed, there wouldn't have been any problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If someone irritates you, it is best not to react immediately.\", \"target\": \"someone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If someone irritates you, it is best not to react immediately.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If someone irritates you, it is best not to react immediately.\", \"target\": \"react\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"反应\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If someone irritates you, it is best not to react immediately.\", \"target\": \"immediately\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"立即\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll sauté a few sweet potatoes and sprinkle them with sugar.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll sauté a few sweet potatoes and sprinkle them with sugar.\", \"target\": \"sweet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"甜的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I'll sauté a few sweet potatoes and sprinkle them with sugar.\", \"target\": \"potatoes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"土豆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"宁愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"rather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"宁愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"art\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"艺术\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"museum\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"博物馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather go to the art museum than to the movie theater.\", \"target\": \"theater\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"剧院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you need to spend a little more time on your homework.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you need to spend a little more time on your homework.\", \"target\": \"need\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you need to spend a little more time on your homework.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you need to spend a little more time on your homework.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think you need to spend a little more time on your homework.\", \"target\": \"homework\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家庭作业\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think to clearly distinguish opinion from fact is important.\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think to clearly distinguish opinion from fact is important.\", \"target\": \"clearly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"清楚地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think to clearly distinguish opinion from fact is important.\", \"target\": \"distinguish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"区分\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think to clearly distinguish opinion from fact is important.\", \"target\": \"opinion\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"观点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think to clearly distinguish opinion from fact is important.\", \"target\": \"fact\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事实\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I think to clearly distinguish opinion from fact is important.\", \"target\": \"important\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"重要的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I should have tried out this electric shaver before buying it.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I should have tried out this electric shaver before buying it.\", \"target\": \"buying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"购买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"heard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"someone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"某人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"crowd\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人群\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"station\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"车站\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"叫\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I heard someone in the crowd outside the station call my name.\", \"target\": \"name\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"名字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel the order because we didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"cancel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"取消\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel the order because we didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"order\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"订单\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel the order because we didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"enough\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I had to cancel the order because we didn't have enough money.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I doubt that Tom will ever learn how to speak French properly.\", \"target\": \"doubt\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"怀疑\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I doubt that Tom will ever learn how to speak French properly.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I doubt that Tom will ever learn how to speak French properly.\", \"target\": \"ever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I doubt that Tom will ever learn how to speak French properly.\", \"target\": \"learn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I doubt that Tom will ever learn how to speak French properly.\", \"target\": \"properly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"正确地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't know about the past, but now we have faxes and emails.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't know about the past, but now we have faxes and emails.\", \"target\": \"past\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"过去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I don't know about the past, but now we have faxes and emails.\", \"target\": \"emails\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电子邮件\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was disappointed that things didn't turn out as he'd hoped.\", \"target\": \"disappointed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"失望的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was disappointed that things didn't turn out as he'd hoped.\", \"target\": \"things\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was disappointed that things didn't turn out as he'd hoped.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He was disappointed that things didn't turn out as he'd hoped.\", \"target\": \"hoped\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that whatever might happen, he was prepared for it.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that whatever might happen, he was prepared for it.\", \"target\": \"whatever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"无论什么\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that whatever might happen, he was prepared for it.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that whatever might happen, he was prepared for it.\", \"target\": \"happen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He told me that whatever might happen, he was prepared for it.\", \"target\": \"prepared\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"准备好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ever since she fell in the kitchen, she hasn't been all there.\", \"target\": \"ever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ever since she fell in the kitchen, she hasn't been all there.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"自从\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ever since she fell in the kitchen, she hasn't been all there.\", \"target\": \"fell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"摔倒\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Ever since she fell in the kitchen, she hasn't been all there.\", \"target\": \"kitchen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨房\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the concert schedule of London Symphony Orchestra?\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the concert schedule of London Symphony Orchestra?\", \"target\": \"concert\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"音乐会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Do you know the concert schedule of London Symphony Orchestra?\", \"target\": \"orchestra\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"管弦乐队\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children generally have a higher body temperature than adults.\", \"target\": \"children\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"儿童\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children generally have a higher body temperature than adults.\", \"target\": \"generally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children generally have a higher body temperature than adults.\", \"target\": \"body\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"身体\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children generally have a higher body temperature than adults.\", \"target\": \"temperature\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"温度\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Children generally have a higher body temperature than adults.\", \"target\": \"adults\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"成年人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Burj Khalifa is currently the tallest skyscraper in the world.\", \"target\": \"currently\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"目前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Burj Khalifa is currently the tallest skyscraper in the world.\", \"target\": \"world\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世界\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Between you and me, Tom's idea doesn't appeal to me very much.\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Between you and me, Tom's idea doesn't appeal to me very much.\", \"target\": \"appeal\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吸引\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Between you and me, Tom's idea doesn't appeal to me very much.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the age of six, I was taken to a circus for the first time.\", \"target\": \"age\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年龄\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the age of six, I was taken to a circus for the first time.\", \"target\": \"six\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"number\", \"zh\": \"六\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"At the age of six, I was taken to a circus for the first time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as the bell rang, the teacher came into the classroom.\", \"target\": \"soon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很快\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as the bell rang, the teacher came into the classroom.\", \"target\": \"bell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"铃声\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as the bell rang, the teacher came into the classroom.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as the bell rang, the teacher came into the classroom.\", \"target\": \"came\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"As soon as the bell rang, the teacher came into the classroom.\", \"target\": \"classroom\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"aging\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老龄化的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"population\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人口\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"require\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"需要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"spending\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"支出\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An aging population will require more spending on health care.\", \"target\": \"health\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"健康\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After winning the Nobel prize, she remained as modest as ever.\", \"target\": \"winning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"赢得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After winning the Nobel prize, she remained as modest as ever.\", \"target\": \"prize\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"奖品\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After winning the Nobel prize, she remained as modest as ever.\", \"target\": \"remained\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"保持\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After winning the Nobel prize, she remained as modest as ever.\", \"target\": \"modest\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"谦虚的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After winning the Nobel prize, she remained as modest as ever.\", \"target\": \"ever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After they argued, they didn't speak to each other for a week.\", \"target\": \"argued\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"争论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After they argued, they didn't speak to each other for a week.\", \"target\": \"speak\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After they argued, they didn't speak to each other for a week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A trip to America was equivalent to a two-year salary for her.\", \"target\": \"trip\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"旅行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A trip to America was equivalent to a two-year salary for her.\", \"target\": \"equivalent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"等同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A trip to America was equivalent to a two-year salary for her.\", \"target\": \"salary\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工资\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"一点儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"bit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"一点点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"luck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"运气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"sometimes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"leads\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"unexpected\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"意想不到的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A little bit of luck sometimes leads to an unexpected success.\", \"target\": \"success\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"成功\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A couple of flights were delayed on account of the earthquake.\", \"target\": \"couple\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一对\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A couple of flights were delayed on account of the earthquake.\", \"target\": \"flights\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"航班\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A couple of flights were delayed on account of the earthquake.\", \"target\": \"delayed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"延误\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A couple of flights were delayed on account of the earthquake.\", \"target\": \"earthquake\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地震\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What do you think of the election for mayor?\\\" \\\"I don't know.\\\"\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What do you think of the election for mayor?\\\" \\\"I don't know.\\\"\", \"target\": \"election\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"选举\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What do you think of the election for mayor?\\\" \\\"I don't know.\\\"\", \"target\": \"mayor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"市长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What do you think of the election for mayor?\\\" \\\"I don't know.\\\"\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How long does it take to get to Vienna on foot?\\\" he inquired.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"How long does it take to get to Vienna on foot?\\\" he inquired.\", \"target\": \"inquired\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"询问\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must be careful of the traffic when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"must\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"必须\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must be careful of the traffic when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"careful\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must be careful of the traffic when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"traffic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交通\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You must be careful of the traffic when you cross the street.\", \"target\": \"street\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"街道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With the T.V. on, how can you keep your mind on your studies?\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心智\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"With the T.V. on, how can you keep your mind on your studies?\", \"target\": \"studies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While we were discussing the problem, I hit upon a good idea.\", \"target\": \"discussing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"讨论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While we were discussing the problem, I hit upon a good idea.\", \"target\": \"problem\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"While we were discussing the problem, I hit upon a good idea.\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think would happen if the earth stopped spinning?\", \"target\": \"think\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think would happen if the earth stopped spinning?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think would happen if the earth stopped spinning?\", \"target\": \"happen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think would happen if the earth stopped spinning?\", \"target\": \"earth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What do you think would happen if the earth stopped spinning?\", \"target\": \"spinning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"旋转\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the volume up so that the students at the back can hear.\", \"target\": \"turn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"打开\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the volume up so that the students at the back can hear.\", \"target\": \"volume\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"音量\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the volume up so that the students at the back can hear.\", \"target\": \"students\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Turn the volume up so that the students at the back can hear.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went into the kitchen and poured himself a cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went into the kitchen and poured himself a cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"kitchen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"厨房\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom went into the kitchen and poured himself a cup of coffee.\", \"target\": \"coffee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"咖啡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the last person Mary expected to see at John's party.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最后的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the last person Mary expected to see at John's party.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the last person Mary expected to see at John's party.\", \"target\": \"expected\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"期望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the last person Mary expected to see at John's party.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom was the last person Mary expected to see at John's party.\", \"target\": \"party\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"派对\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he thought that Mary used to live in Boston.\", \"target\": \"told\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he thought that Mary used to live in Boston.\", \"target\": \"thought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom told me that he thought that Mary used to live in Boston.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"住\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is still uncertain about whether to go to college or not.\", \"target\": \"still\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"仍然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is still uncertain about whether to go to college or not.\", \"target\": \"whether\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"是否\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom is still uncertain about whether to go to college or not.\", \"target\": \"college\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大学\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This novel is more interesting than the one I read last week.\", \"target\": \"novel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"小说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This novel is more interesting than the one I read last week.\", \"target\": \"interesting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有趣的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This novel is more interesting than the one I read last week.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"一个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This novel is more interesting than the one I read last week.\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This novel is more interesting than the one I read last week.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my entire life.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my entire life.\", \"target\": \"ever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my entire life.\", \"target\": \"seen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my entire life.\", \"target\": \"entire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"整个的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my entire life.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This airplane is capable of carrying 40 passengers at a time.\", \"target\": \"airplane\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"飞机\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This airplane is capable of carrying 40 passengers at a time.\", \"target\": \"capable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有能力的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This airplane is capable of carrying 40 passengers at a time.\", \"target\": \"carrying\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"携带\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This airplane is capable of carrying 40 passengers at a time.\", \"target\": \"passengers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乘客\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would've been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would've been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"killed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"被杀死\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would've been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"car\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would've been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"gone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They would've been killed if the car had gone over the cliff.\", \"target\": \"cliff\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"悬崖\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They fine you in Singapore if you throw trash in the streets.\", \"target\": \"fine\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"罚款\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They fine you in Singapore if you throw trash in the streets.\", \"target\": \"streets\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"街道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These scissors are suitable for left and right-handed people.\", \"target\": \"suitable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"合适的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"These scissors are suitable for left and right-handed people.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were only three passengers on the bus when it exploded.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were only three passengers on the bus when it exploded.\", \"target\": \"passengers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"乘客\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were only three passengers on the bus when it exploded.\", \"target\": \"bus\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公共汽车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"There were only three passengers on the bus when it exploded.\", \"target\": \"exploded\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆炸\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The skin of a shark is much rougher than that of a tuna fish.\", \"target\": \"skin\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"皮肤\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The skin of a shark is much rougher than that of a tuna fish.\", \"target\": \"much\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The skin of a shark is much rougher than that of a tuna fish.\", \"target\": \"fish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鱼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old houses were torn down to make room for a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old houses were torn down to make room for a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"houses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old houses were torn down to make room for a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"torn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拆毁\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old houses were torn down to make room for a supermarket.\", \"target\": \"supermarket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"超市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old church on the hill dates back to the twelfth century.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"旧的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old church on the hill dates back to the twelfth century.\", \"target\": \"church\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"教堂\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old church on the hill dates back to the twelfth century.\", \"target\": \"hill\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"山丘\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old church on the hill dates back to the twelfth century.\", \"target\": \"dates\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"追溯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The old church on the hill dates back to the twelfth century.\", \"target\": \"century\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"世纪\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house burned to the ground before the fire truck arrived.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house burned to the ground before the fire truck arrived.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house burned to the ground before the fire truck arrived.\", \"target\": \"truck\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卡车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The house burned to the ground before the fire truck arrived.\", \"target\": \"arrived\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conference is to be held in Tokyo the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"conference\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"会议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conference is to be held in Tokyo the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"held\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"举行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The conference is to be held in Tokyo the day after tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"way\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"方法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"lose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"减肥\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"weight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"体重\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"eat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"less\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"更少\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The best way to lose weight is to eat less and exercise more.\", \"target\": \"exercise\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"锻炼\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Small businesses will have to tighten their belts to survive.\", \"target\": \"small\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"小的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Small businesses will have to tighten their belts to survive.\", \"target\": \"businesses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"企业\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Small businesses will have to tighten their belts to survive.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Small businesses will have to tighten their belts to survive.\", \"target\": \"survive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生存\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since I had met him once before, I recognized him right away.\", \"target\": \"since\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"因为\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since I had met him once before, I recognized him right away.\", \"target\": \"met\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"遇见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Since I had met him once before, I recognized him right away.\", \"target\": \"recognized\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认出\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"visited\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"拜访\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"男人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"hospital\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She visited the old man in the hospital every day but Sunday.\", \"target\": \"sunday\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tossed me grapes and I tried to catch them with my mouth.\", \"target\": \"tossed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"扔\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tossed me grapes and I tried to catch them with my mouth.\", \"target\": \"tried\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"试图\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She tossed me grapes and I tried to catch them with my mouth.\", \"target\": \"mouth\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"嘴巴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is better at speaking English than any of her classmates.\", \"target\": \"better\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She is better at speaking English than any of her classmates.\", \"target\": \"speaking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a real knack for getting people to do what she wants.\", \"target\": \"real\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a real knack for getting people to do what she wants.\", \"target\": \"getting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a real knack for getting people to do what she wants.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"She has a real knack for getting people to do what she wants.\", \"target\": \"wants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Several dozen young people participated in the demonstration.\", \"target\": \"several\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"几个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Several dozen young people participated in the demonstration.\", \"target\": \"young\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"年轻的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Several dozen young people participated in the demonstration.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Several dozen young people participated in the demonstration.\", \"target\": \"participated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"参与\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Several dozen young people participated in the demonstration.\", \"target\": \"demonstration\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"示威游行\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Problems that can be solved with money are not real problems.\", \"target\": \"problems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"问题\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Problems that can be solved with money are not real problems.\", \"target\": \"solved\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解决\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Problems that can be solved with money are not real problems.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Problems that can be solved with money are not real problems.\", \"target\": \"real\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"真实的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Plastics have taken the place of many conventional materials.\", \"target\": \"plastics\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"塑料\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Plastics have taken the place of many conventional materials.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Plastics have taken the place of many conventional materials.\", \"target\": \"conventional\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"传统的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Plastics have taken the place of many conventional materials.\", \"target\": \"materials\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"材料\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My grandfather is fond of taking a walk early in the morning.\", \"target\": \"grandfather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"祖父\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My grandfather is fond of taking a walk early in the morning.\", \"target\": \"fond\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"喜爱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My grandfather is fond of taking a walk early in the morning.\", \"target\": \"taking\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"采取\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My grandfather is fond of taking a walk early in the morning.\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"早\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My grandfather is fond of taking a walk early in the morning.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My fingers are so numb with cold that I can't play the piano.\", \"target\": \"fingers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"手指\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My fingers are so numb with cold that I can't play the piano.\", \"target\": \"cold\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"寒冷\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My fingers are so numb with cold that I can't play the piano.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My fingers are so numb with cold that I can't play the piano.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩;演奏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My fingers are so numb with cold that I can't play the piano.\", \"target\": \"piano\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢琴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play the ocarina.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play the ocarina.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play the ocarina.\", \"target\": \"resolution\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"决心\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play the ocarina.\", \"target\": \"learn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My New Year's resolution is to learn how to play the ocarina.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"玩\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"lots\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"很多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"companies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公司\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Lots of companies have implemented an eight-hour working day.\", \"target\": \"implemented\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"实施\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Long time, no see. I hear that you've changed your job again.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长久的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Long time, no see. I hear that you've changed your job again.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Long time, no see. I hear that you've changed your job again.\", \"target\": \"see\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Long time, no see. I hear that you've changed your job again.\", \"target\": \"hear\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"听到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Long time, no see. I hear that you've changed your job again.\", \"target\": \"changed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"改变\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Long time, no see. I hear that you've changed your job again.\", \"target\": \"job\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Judging from the look of the sky, it may rain this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"judging\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"根据\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Judging from the look of the sky, it may rain this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"sky\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天空\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Judging from the look of the sky, it may rain this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"may\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Judging from the look of the sky, it may rain this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"rain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"下雨\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Judging from the look of the sky, it may rain this afternoon.\", \"target\": \"afternoon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"下午\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"decide\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"决定\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真正地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It took us a long time to decide what we really wanted to do.\", \"target\": \"wanted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Is there a place where I can charge my cellphone around here?\", \"target\": \"place\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"地方\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"India ink produces an interesting pattern when used as a dye.\", \"target\": \"ink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"墨水\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"India ink produces an interesting pattern when used as a dye.\", \"target\": \"produces\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生产\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"India ink produces an interesting pattern when used as a dye.\", \"target\": \"interesting\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有趣的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"India ink produces an interesting pattern when used as a dye.\", \"target\": \"pattern\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图案\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"India ink produces an interesting pattern when used as a dye.\", \"target\": \"dye\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"染料\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In 1978 a peace treaty was concluded between Japan and China.\", \"target\": \"peace\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"和平\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In 1978 a peace treaty was concluded between Japan and China.\", \"target\": \"treaty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"条约\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"In 1978 a peace treaty was concluded between Japan and China.\", \"target\": \"concluded\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"结束\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you feed your dog properly, you can increase his lifespan.\", \"target\": \"feed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喂养\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you feed your dog properly, you can increase his lifespan.\", \"target\": \"dog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"狗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you feed your dog properly, you can increase his lifespan.\", \"target\": \"properly\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"正确地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you feed your dog properly, you can increase his lifespan.\", \"target\": \"increase\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"增加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If her nose were a little shorter, she would be quite pretty.\", \"target\": \"nose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"鼻子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If her nose were a little shorter, she would be quite pretty.\", \"target\": \"little\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"稍微\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If her nose were a little shorter, she would be quite pretty.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If her nose were a little shorter, she would be quite pretty.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If her nose were a little shorter, she would be quite pretty.\", \"target\": \"pretty\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"漂亮的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"taken\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"采取\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"doctor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"advice\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"建议\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"might\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"可能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If he had taken his doctor's advice, he might still be alive.\", \"target\": \"alive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"活着的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason they come early, please tell them to wait.\", \"target\": \"reason\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"原因\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason they come early, please tell them to wait.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason they come early, please tell them to wait.\", \"target\": \"early\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"早\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason they come early, please tell them to wait.\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason they come early, please tell them to wait.\", \"target\": \"tell\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"告诉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If for some reason they come early, please tell them to wait.\", \"target\": \"wait\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"等待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I had known that you were here, I would have come at once.\", \"target\": \"known\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I had known that you were here, I would have come at once.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I had known that you were here, I would have come at once.\", \"target\": \"come\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a headache for three days and I can't get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"headache\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"头痛\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a headache for three days and I can't get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a headache for three days and I can't get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"days\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I've had a headache for three days and I can't get rid of it.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"wish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"希望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"figure\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"弄清楚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"comments\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"评论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I wish I could figure out how to disable comments on my blog.\", \"target\": \"blog\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"博客\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"work\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"工作\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"completed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"two\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"二\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I want this work completed by two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.\", \"target\": \"afternoon\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"下午\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sometimes just don't want to get out of bed in the morning.\", \"target\": \"sometimes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"有时\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sometimes just don't want to get out of bed in the morning.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sometimes just don't want to get out of bed in the morning.\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"起床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sometimes just don't want to get out of bed in the morning.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I sometimes just don't want to get out of bed in the morning.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a group of foreigners on my way to school this morning.\", \"target\": \"saw\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"看见\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a group of foreigners on my way to school this morning.\", \"target\": \"group\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"群体\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a group of foreigners on my way to school this morning.\", \"target\": \"foreigners\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"外国人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a group of foreigners on my way to school this morning.\", \"target\": \"school\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学校\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I saw a group of foreigners on my way to school this morning.\", \"target\": \"morning\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早上\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just remembered that I was supposed to buy a loaf of bread.\", \"target\": \"remembered\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"记得\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just remembered that I was supposed to buy a loaf of bread.\", \"target\": \"supposed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"应该\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I just remembered that I was supposed to buy a loaf of bread.\", \"target\": \"buy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't yet collected sufficient materials to write a book.\", \"target\": \"yet\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"还\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't yet collected sufficient materials to write a book.\", \"target\": \"collected\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"收集\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't yet collected sufficient materials to write a book.\", \"target\": \"sufficient\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"足够的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't yet collected sufficient materials to write a book.\", \"target\": \"materials\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"材料\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't yet collected sufficient materials to write a book.\", \"target\": \"write\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"写\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I haven't yet collected sufficient materials to write a book.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a phone call from him just as I was about to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"got\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a phone call from him just as I was about to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"phone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a phone call from him just as I was about to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"call\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"电话\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I got a phone call from him just as I was about to go to bed.\", \"target\": \"bed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"床\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not like tea, so I generally drink coffee for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not like tea, so I generally drink coffee for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"tea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"茶\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not like tea, so I generally drink coffee for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"generally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"通常\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not like tea, so I generally drink coffee for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"drink\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喝\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not like tea, so I generally drink coffee for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"coffee\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"咖啡\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I do not like tea, so I generally drink coffee for breakfast.\", \"target\": \"breakfast\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"早餐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe that you were the smartest kid in your class.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe that you were the smartest kid in your class.\", \"target\": \"believe\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"相信\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I can't believe that you were the smartest kid in your class.\", \"target\": \"kid\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"长\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"到达\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"How long does it take to get from here to your house on foot?\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"bought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"购买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"land\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"土地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"purpose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"目的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"bought\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"购买\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"land\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"土地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"purpose\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"目的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He bought the land for the purpose of building a house on it.\", \"target\": \"house\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"anonymously\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"匿名地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"donated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"捐赠\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"large\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"大的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"sum\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"总和\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"He anonymously donated a large sum of money to the Red Cross.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First, I don't have any money. Second, I don't have the time.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First, I don't have any money. Second, I don't have the time.\", \"target\": \"money\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钱\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First, I don't have any money. Second, I don't have the time.\", \"target\": \"second\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"首先\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"First, I don't have any money. Second, I don't have the time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every nation, rich or poor, has its strengths and weaknesses.\", \"target\": \"every\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"每个\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every nation, rich or poor, has its strengths and weaknesses.\", \"target\": \"nation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"国家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every nation, rich or poor, has its strengths and weaknesses.\", \"target\": \"rich\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富裕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every nation, rich or poor, has its strengths and weaknesses.\", \"target\": \"poor\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"贫穷的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every nation, rich or poor, has its strengths and weaknesses.\", \"target\": \"strengths\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"优势\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Every nation, rich or poor, has its strengths and weaknesses.\", \"target\": \"weaknesses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"弱点\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"即使\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"though\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"虽然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"enjoy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"享受\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"bowling\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"保龄球\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"gone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Even though I enjoy bowling, I haven't gone bowling recently.\", \"target\": \"recently\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最近\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cancer can be cured easily if it is found in its first phase.\", \"target\": \"cancer\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"癌症\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cancer can be cured easily if it is found in its first phase.\", \"target\": \"cured\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"治愈\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cancer can be cured easily if it is found in its first phase.\", \"target\": \"easily\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"容易地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cancer can be cured easily if it is found in its first phase.\", \"target\": \"found\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发现\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Cancer can be cured easily if it is found in its first phase.\", \"target\": \"phase\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"阶段\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beethoven went over to the piano, sat down and began to play.\", \"target\": \"went\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beethoven went over to the piano, sat down and began to play.\", \"target\": \"piano\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"钢琴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beethoven went over to the piano, sat down and began to play.\", \"target\": \"sat\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"坐\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beethoven went over to the piano, sat down and began to play.\", \"target\": \"began\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"开始\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Beethoven went over to the piano, sat down and began to play.\", \"target\": \"play\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"演奏\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An opportunity like this only comes along once in a lifetime.\", \"target\": \"opportunity\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"机会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An opportunity like this only comes along once in a lifetime.\", \"target\": \"comes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"来临\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"An opportunity like this only comes along once in a lifetime.\", \"target\": \"lifetime\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"一生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a long argument, I finally persuaded her to go camping.\", \"target\": \"long\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"ADJ\", \"zh\": \"漫长的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a long argument, I finally persuaded her to go camping.\", \"target\": \"argument\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"争论\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a long argument, I finally persuaded her to go camping.\", \"target\": \"finally\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最终\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a long argument, I finally persuaded her to go camping.\", \"target\": \"persuaded\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说服\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"After a long argument, I finally persuaded her to go camping.\", \"target\": \"camping\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"露营\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"new\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"新的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"team\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"团队\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A new team was formed in order to take part in the boat race.\", \"target\": \"formed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"组建\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"fire\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"火\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"broke\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"out\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"爆发\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"last\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"昨晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"night\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"夜晚\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"three\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"A fire broke out last night and three houses were burnt down.\", \"target\": \"houses\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"房子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"cave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞穴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"curious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好奇的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"going\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"发生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"cave\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"洞穴\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"curious\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好奇的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"What's going on in the cave? I'm curious.\\\" \\\"I have no idea.\\\"\", \"target\": \"idea\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"想法\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Shall I have him call you when he gets back?\\\" \\\"Yes, please.\\\"\", \"target\": \"shall\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Shall I have him call you when he gets back?\\\" \\\"Yes, please.\\\"\", \"target\": \"yes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"是的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"\\\"Shall I have him call you when he gets back?\\\" \\\"Yes, please.\\\"\", \"target\": \"please\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"interjection\", \"zh\": \"请\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should try to form the habit of using your dictionaries.\", \"target\": \"try\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"尝试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should try to form the habit of using your dictionaries.\", \"target\": \"habit\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"习惯\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You should try to form the habit of using your dictionaries.\", \"target\": \"dictionaries\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"字典\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't fight a good fight with such a defeatist attitude.\", \"target\": \"cannot\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't fight a good fight with such a defeatist attitude.\", \"target\": \"fight\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"战斗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't fight a good fight with such a defeatist attitude.\", \"target\": \"good\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"好的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't fight a good fight with such a defeatist attitude.\", \"target\": \"defeatist\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"失败主义的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can't fight a good fight with such a defeatist attitude.\", \"target\": \"attitude\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"态度\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can lie to everyone else, but you can't lie to yourself.\", \"target\": \"lie\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说谎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can lie to everyone else, but you can't lie to yourself.\", \"target\": \"everyone\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"每个人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"You can lie to everyone else, but you can't lie to yourself.\", \"target\": \"else\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"conjunction\", \"zh\": \"否则\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like me to get you something from the supermarket?\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like me to get you something from the supermarket?\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like me to get you something from the supermarket?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"得到\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like me to get you something from the supermarket?\", \"target\": \"something\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Would you like me to get you something from the supermarket?\", \"target\": \"supermarket\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"超市\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I was a child, I spent most of my time indoors reading.\", \"target\": \"child\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"孩子\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I was a child, I spent most of my time indoors reading.\", \"target\": \"spent\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"花费\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I was a child, I spent most of my time indoors reading.\", \"target\": \"most\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"最\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I was a child, I spent most of my time indoors reading.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I was a child, I spent most of my time indoors reading.\", \"target\": \"indoors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"在室内\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"When I was a child, I spent most of my time indoors reading.\", \"target\": \"reading\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"阅读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What image did you have in mind as you painted this picture?\", \"target\": \"image\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图像\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What image did you have in mind as you painted this picture?\", \"target\": \"mind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"心智\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What image did you have in mind as you painted this picture?\", \"target\": \"painted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"画\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"What image did you have in mind as you painted this picture?\", \"target\": \"picture\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"图片\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We take it for granted that he will succeed in his business.\", \"target\": \"take\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"认为...理所当然\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We take it for granted that he will succeed in his business.\", \"target\": \"granted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"理所当然地\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We take it for granted that he will succeed in his business.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We take it for granted that he will succeed in his business.\", \"target\": \"succeed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"成功\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We take it for granted that he will succeed in his business.\", \"target\": \"his\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"possessive pronoun\", \"zh\": \"他的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We take it for granted that he will succeed in his business.\", \"target\": \"business\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生意\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like our neighbors, and they don't like us, either.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like our neighbors, and they don't like us, either.\", \"target\": \"neighbors\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"邻居\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We don't like our neighbors, and they don't like us, either.\", \"target\": \"us\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"pronoun\", \"zh\": \"我们\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We did not expect him to finish the task in so short a time.\", \"target\": \"expect\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"期望\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We did not expect him to finish the task in so short a time.\", \"target\": \"finish\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"完成\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"We did not expect him to finish the task in so short a time.\", \"target\": \"task\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"任务\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom translated a letter from French to English for his boss.\", \"target\": \"translated\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"翻译\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom translated a letter from French to English for his boss.\", \"target\": \"letter\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"信件\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom translated a letter from French to English for his boss.\", \"target\": \"boss\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老板\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took Mary to the hospital on the back of his motorcycle.\", \"target\": \"took\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"带\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took Mary to the hospital on the back of his motorcycle.\", \"target\": \"hospital\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"医院\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom took Mary to the hospital on the back of his motorcycle.\", \"target\": \"motorcycle\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"摩托车\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't quite get it. Could you explain it to him again?\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"完全\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't quite get it. Could you explain it to him again?\", \"target\": \"get\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"理解\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't quite get it. Could you explain it to him again?\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"modal verb\", \"zh\": \"能够\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom doesn't quite get it. Could you explain it to him again?\", \"target\": \"explain\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"解释\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't read very well until he was thirteen years old.\", \"target\": \"could\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"不能\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't read very well until he was thirteen years old.\", \"target\": \"read\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"读\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't read very well until he was thirteen years old.\", \"target\": \"well\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't read very well until he was thirteen years old.\", \"target\": \"thirteen\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"十三\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't read very well until he was thirteen years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Tom couldn't read very well until he was thirteen years old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This week the cherry blossoms in the park are in full bloom.\", \"target\": \"week\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"星期\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This week the cherry blossoms in the park are in full bloom.\", \"target\": \"park\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"公园\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This town is quite different from what it was ten years ago.\", \"target\": \"town\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"城镇\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This town is quite different from what it was ten years ago.\", \"target\": \"quite\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"相当\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This town is quite different from what it was ten years ago.\", \"target\": \"different\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"不同的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This town is quite different from what it was ten years ago.\", \"target\": \"ten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"十\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This town is quite different from what it was ten years ago.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This town is quite different from what it was ten years ago.\", \"target\": \"ago\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"以前\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is one of the best restaurants that I've ever eaten in.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"num\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is one of the best restaurants that I've ever eaten in.\", \"target\": \"best\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"最好\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is one of the best restaurants that I've ever eaten in.\", \"target\": \"restaurants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"餐馆\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is one of the best restaurants that I've ever eaten in.\", \"target\": \"ever\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"曾经\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This is one of the best restaurants that I've ever eaten in.\", \"target\": \"eaten\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吃过\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book says that elephants live to be over 100 years old.\", \"target\": \"book\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"书\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book says that elephants live to be over 100 years old.\", \"target\": \"says\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book says that elephants live to be over 100 years old.\", \"target\": \"elephants\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"大象\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book says that elephants live to be over 100 years old.\", \"target\": \"live\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book says that elephants live to be over 100 years old.\", \"target\": \"years\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"This book says that elephants live to be over 100 years old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sleep in separate bedrooms even though they're married.\", \"target\": \"sleep\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"睡觉\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sleep in separate bedrooms even though they're married.\", \"target\": \"separate\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"分开的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sleep in separate bedrooms even though they're married.\", \"target\": \"bedrooms\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"卧室\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"They sleep in separate bedrooms even though they're married.\", \"target\": \"married\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"已婚的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The student handed the examination papers in to the teacher.\", \"target\": \"student\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"学生\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The student handed the examination papers in to the teacher.\", \"target\": \"handed\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"递交\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The student handed the examination papers in to the teacher.\", \"target\": \"examination\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"考试\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The student handed the examination papers in to the teacher.\", \"target\": \"papers\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"试卷\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The student handed the examination papers in to the teacher.\", \"target\": \"teacher\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"老师\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ozone in the stratosphere absorbs ultraviolet radiation.\", \"target\": \"absorbs\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"吸收\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The ozone in the stratosphere absorbs ultraviolet radiation.\", \"target\": \"radiation\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"辐射\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of traffic accidents seems to be on the increase.\", \"target\": \"number\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"数字\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of traffic accidents seems to be on the increase.\", \"target\": \"traffic\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"交通\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of traffic accidents seems to be on the increase.\", \"target\": \"accidents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of traffic accidents seems to be on the increase.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The number of traffic accidents seems to be on the increase.\", \"target\": \"increase\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"增加\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The first thing you have to take into consideration is time.\", \"target\": \"first\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"第一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The first thing you have to take into consideration is time.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"东西\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"The first thing you have to take into consideration is time.\", \"target\": \"time\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"时间\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"babies\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"婴儿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"learn\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"学习\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"swim\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"even\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"甚至\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"one\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"cardinal number\", \"zh\": \"一\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"year\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"年\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Some babies learn to swim even before they are one year old.\", \"target\": \"old\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"老的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pizza is the kind of food that fits into today's life style.\", \"target\": \"kind\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"种类\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pizza is the kind of food that fits into today's life style.\", \"target\": \"food\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"食物\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pizza is the kind of food that fits into today's life style.\", \"target\": \"fits\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"适合\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pizza is the kind of food that fits into today's life style.\", \"target\": \"today\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"今天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Pizza is the kind of food that fits into today's life style.\", \"target\": \"life\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"生活\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My younger brother really likes to take photos of mountains.\", \"target\": \"brother\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"兄弟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My younger brother really likes to take photos of mountains.\", \"target\": \"really\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"真的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My younger brother really likes to take photos of mountains.\", \"target\": \"likes\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"喜欢\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My younger brother really likes to take photos of mountains.\", \"target\": \"photos\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"照片\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"My younger brother really likes to take photos of mountains.\", \"target\": \"mountains\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"山\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many accidents resulted from the icy conditions of the road.\", \"target\": \"many\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"determiner\", \"zh\": \"许多\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many accidents resulted from the icy conditions of the road.\", \"target\": \"accidents\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事故\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many accidents resulted from the icy conditions of the road.\", \"target\": \"resulted\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"导致\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many accidents resulted from the icy conditions of the road.\", \"target\": \"icy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"冰冷的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many accidents resulted from the icy conditions of the road.\", \"target\": \"conditions\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"条件\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"Many accidents resulted from the icy conditions of the road.\", \"target\": \"road\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"道路\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to deceive people, but worse to deceive yourself.\", \"target\": \"wrong\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"错误的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to deceive people, but worse to deceive yourself.\", \"target\": \"deceive\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"欺骗\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to deceive people, but worse to deceive yourself.\", \"target\": \"people\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's wrong to deceive people, but worse to deceive yourself.\", \"target\": \"worse\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"更糟\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to predict what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"hard\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"困难的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to predict what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"predict\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"预测\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to predict what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to predict what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"will\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"将\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to predict what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"like\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"preposition\", \"zh\": \"像\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It's hard to predict what the weather will be like tomorrow.\", \"target\": \"tomorrow\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"明天\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was heartless of him to say such a thing to the sick man.\", \"target\": \"say\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"说\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was heartless of him to say such a thing to the sick man.\", \"target\": \"thing\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"事情\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was heartless of him to say such a thing to the sick man.\", \"target\": \"sick\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"生病的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It was heartless of him to say such a thing to the sick man.\", \"target\": \"man\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems as if I'm the only person here capable of doing it.\", \"target\": \"seems\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"似乎\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems as if I'm the only person here capable of doing it.\", \"target\": \"person\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"人\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"It seems as if I'm the only person here capable of doing it.\", \"target\": \"capable\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"有能力的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you stay at a big hotel, you can use their swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"停留\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you stay at a big hotel, you can use their swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"hotel\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"酒店\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If you stay at a big hotel, you can use their swimming pool.\", \"target\": \"swimming\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"游泳\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for civil war, they would be wealthy now.\", \"target\": \"civil\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"内战的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for civil war, they would be wealthy now.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If it had not been for civil war, they would be wealthy now.\", \"target\": \"wealthy\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adjective\", \"zh\": \"富裕的\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I were you, I'd want to know what Tom is doing right now.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I were you, I'd want to know what Tom is doing right now.\", \"target\": \"want\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"想要\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"If I were you, I'd want to know what Tom is doing right now.\", \"target\": \"know\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"知道\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"宁愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"rather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"adverb\", \"zh\": \"宁愿\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"stay\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"待\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"home\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"家\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"go\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"verb\", \"zh\": \"去\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would rather stay at home than go out in this hot weather.\", \"target\": \"weather\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"noun\", \"zh\": \"天气\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
{"prompt": "{\"context\": \"I would have liked to come with you, but I didn't have time.\", \"target\": \"would\", \"idx\": 1}", "response": "{\"class\": \"auxiliary verb\", \"zh\": \"会\", \"phrase\": \"\"}"}
